Chapter 1143: Plot 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Mars planet ring.

The oversized red planet ring wrapped around like a belt and hung around the crimson Mars, spinning slowly.

A large group of figures in red long robes were flying out a hidden leaping black hole on the planet ring in a tidy order.

The figures that flew out landed on the planet ring. Large amounts of universe debris and various elements camouflaged them.

Each leaping figures triggered force field ripples enough to tremor anyone of an Inherited Level.

One of a red figure was the last to fly out and within this group of over a hundred, he stood in the highest position to distinguish his aristocracy.

“Chinande, hopefully, this time your intel isn’t lacking,” the red figure was heard in a low voice.

Hiss…

A black crack was ripped out of space and a white figure walked out of it. It was Chinande with a pair of pale emotionless of eyes.

“You think I would lie to you?” He asked solemnly.

“My Scarlet Mourning Hall is now out of your control. Hehe, you think that by wiping out the Energy Machinists, it will clear you of suspicion? What a joke. With your capabilities yet you allow this huge tumor of a Scarlet Snow Alliance escape really is incomprehensible,” the red figure coldly smiled.

Chinande did not say anything more but rather looked at Mars. That direction was this mission’s crucial point. At this stage, if the Scarlet Snow Lianne still was in the dark then they were idiots. The enemy was already at their doorstep.

It could be clearly seen that shades of white and red figures burst open from Mars’ atmosphere like denser tiny meteor sparks, firing over at the Scarlet Mourning Hall.

Leading them were the four Perpetual Motioners with Two-Faced Person as their head.

After the war from that year, the remaining Perpetual Motioners Energy Machinist were only them four, all of which entered the Scarlet Snow Alliance and became branch sects, living in seclusion on Mars.

“Prepare to attack,” Chinande shouted. “We have to first eliminate them before Sawtooth King and the rest could react.”

Mars was a stronghold base bestowed by Sawtooth King to the Scarlet Snow sect. If it weren’t for the sudden removal of the Scarlet Mourning Hall’s stronghold above that attracted a large amount of attention, they probably wouldn’t be able to spot something amiss.

At one side was a team of pure crimson while on the other side, a mixture of red and white. The two assembly of people swiftly closed in and stopped at a distance of a few thousand kilometers.

“So it is the Scarlet Mourning Hall! Attack!” Not wasting a breath, the Two-Faced Person flung his arm and signaled the start of the battle. All these years, there was animosity between Scarlet Snow Sect and the Finite people of the Scarlet Mourning Hall in the North Pole. A blood feud, to say the least. Wars of bloodbaths that raged between the two parties had caused the fall of many experts of Inherited Level, Non-Failing Level, Level Eight, even Level Nine as well as Level Ten Perpetual Motioners meeting death together.

Suddenly, a vast fluctuation of force field spread out, sending the people of the Scarlet Snow Sect to be thrown off the leaping ball of inverse space.

With a swoosh, a large black round empty hole appeared between them, engulfing everything around in extreme.

Both parties flew into it in tacit agreement.

Those who could fly in space in true form were either top buffed Energy Machinists or Mech incorporated Mech Pilots who were at least the Non-Failing Level. Up to this point, these average performers were only serving side dish and would not even possess the qualification to even participate the battlefield.

All of them soon made it into the black hole. The opening then shrunk and just as it was going to vanish, a pitch dark spaceship leaped out of nowhere, shot into the hole like a rocket and disappeared into it.

The moment the spaceship disappeared, a ray of light blasted from afar and before the last crack of the hole could seal up, it snuck into it.

The poor hole was prepared to shrink completely yet a boundless force field held it up.

“Inverse space battlefield?” A man’s voice echoed in space. Whizz whizz whizz… rays of blue light fired into the hole. Once again, disappearing out of sight.

This time, the black hole finally shut entirely.

******

Inverse space universe.

Countless planets were injecting large amounts of various attributes and rainbows rays. A large majority of the planets were different in size, a lot of them in a shade of yellow while a small quantity was in blue but mostly emerged in change shades of color such as the rainbow.

Two-Faced Person from the Scarlet Snow Sect and those from the Scarlet Mourning Hall were caught in a fierce battle the moment they entered.

They chose a spacious place where there weren’t any nearby planets. Within the dark space, both parties were familiar with each other’s techniques and strategies. The familiarity was to the point of a friendly match with tacit coordination.

Chinande stood high above, levitating in mid-air. Hiding behind a white robe, he did not make a single move. From an outsider’s point of view, he was a member of the Scarlet Mourning Hall’s red-robed minions but this time, his undercover identity was the deputy hall leader of the Scarlet Mourning Hall.

Seeing the battle between the Scarlet Mourning Hall and Scarlet Snow Sect, he was not in a rush to lend a hand.

“Chinande, what the hell are you doing? You’re not here to be a spectator!” The hall leader of the Scarlet Mourning Hall used a quantum computer to transmit his voice in frustration.

He was ganging up against the Two-Faced Person a few light years away. The frightening black-hole type ripples caused by the two reached up to tens of million kilometers of range but the universe was simply expanse. One light year went up to a hundred billion kilometers of range. If it weren’t for quantum technology, communication between them would be a problem.

So from where Chinande was, he could see nothing but a blur of darkness as the battle rays had yet to reach here but in actual fact, it had already begun.

In order to witness the situation over there, apart from perception and induction, the only way was to wait a few years for the ray to fire over.

This was the universe with unimaginative expanse.

This wasn’t limited to where Two-Faced Person was, it was the same for other confrontation between Non-Failing Levels. Each of them fought in pairs and could not lay eyes on other groups.

Chinande did not respond. He remained silent as he hung in space as if waiting for something.

Time flowed by, seconds and minutes.

Without knowing it, it had been over ten minutes.

Chinande maintained his original posture. A long time ago, his team of Perpetual Motioners were slain in one of the Energy Machinist battles, only he survived while most of the Perpetual Motioners of the Energy Machinists passed and only a handful escaped. Both parties had long laid a deadly grudge.

The team of his best friends were almost completely vaporized because of White King yet he pledged his faith to White King just as a loyal dog.

Some criticized him staying true to the nickname he was coined, Wild Mutt but he did not take this to heart. His real identity was then exposed and as the faithful lackey of White King, he seeked refuge from the camp of Finite people.

In the darkness of the cold and serene space, a black spaceship silently streaked from the depths, flying just beneath Chinande.

“So they’re here?” Chinande’s white eyeballs dryly twirled, “Little rat…”

******

Baylon and Clint stood side by side in the cockpit, staring ahead of the three sloping glasses. The pitch black inverse space universe outside was within their sight.

White Winter and another man with short green hair were navigating the spaceship, agilely dodging pieces of broken meteor fragments.

“We should be united far from the battlefield. We only need to capture one Soul Official Class exports of the Scarlet Mourning Hall before heading back,” White Winter grabbed the goatee on his face. He was no longer the shy little boy that was more beautiful than a woman. With one hand holding a cigarette, his other hand was swiftly operating on the navigation board with dexterity.

“Soul Official Class expert is at least the Non-Failing Level. I will personally handle it,” Baylon spoke coldly with a heavy murderous intent.

“Be careful, I sense something amiss,” Red Moon’s voice was heard amongst the people.

“With me on board, I can take two! Don’t worry about it! I will be going with Lonnie!” Clint’s hands rested on his waist as he spoke with arrogance.

“Is your exterior armor fixed?” Baylon glanced at him and frowned.

“Er…” Clint has yet to reach the Non- Failing Level. He instantly rubbed his nose and lowered his head in awkwardness, “Not yet…”

“Then you stay,” Baylon said without compassion. “Without an exterior armor, you don’t even stand a chance to have Master Red Moon make an appearance. You’ll be a burden even if you go. I alone am enough.”

“How ruthless…!” Clint was crushed.

“Is the leaping settings ready?” Baylon held the handle of her white sword on her waist and looked at White Winter.

White Winter gestured an okay sign.

“Be careful,” the green-haired man reminded. “There’s a Soul Official alone just on the right. He must be planning on backing up the others.”

“Relax.”

Baylon took large strides to the center of the spaceship. The secede pod was there.

Clint and the rest behind her immediately stripped away their joking expression and started to solemnly prepare for any possible unexpected event.

Hiss…

The hatch opened and Baylon entered the isolating cabin. The hatch behind her shut tight and the air current gradually withdrew from both sides.

Swoosh!

The exterior hatch finally opened, revealing the dark and endless universe in the outer world. The inverse space universe.

A silvery-white armor was immediately released on both sides of Baylon’s face, covering the lower half of her face from the nose and providing her oxygen.

Her clothes quickly shrunk and tightened, becoming a tight black suit and outlining her bewitching bodyline. Her body leaped forward a few times with agility, somersaulting into the darkness.

Just out of the hatch, were two red figures that leaped and appeared here.

It was two Soul Official dressed in red.

“Two!?”

Baylon’s eyes turned stern. Her body hasten in its leaping. The force field on her body crystalized a swallow.

With a swish, her body embodying an agile swallow dashed towards the two Soul Officials with lightning speed.

The duo immediately reacted and erected force field. The red force field simulated two crimson glow in blossom similar to two large red eggs within the universe.

A large piece of the force field became red sparks and splattered around after a series of clang noises was heard.

“Unparalleled Sword, Peacock!”

Baylon released a phantom of in form of a peacock. Cold air surging from all directions wrapped the two Soul Officials.

“50% mock!” A hint of cold ruthlessness flashed past her eyes. She drew out her white blade with speed and evoked a wave of white light in the darkness. Becoming one with the beak of the phantom peacock, she struck one of the Soul Official in the chest.

“Fantasy Resonance!!” This Soul Official must have known that he was on the verge of death. His opponent’s lightning speed had caught them off guard and he was almost at the end of the rope with just one blow. Hence, he decided to go all out.

A large amount of red silkworms roved out of the red force field, charging at Baylon in biting motions.

Cling cling!

Two crisp sounds were heard.

Baylon gently landed on a slow-moving aerolite. She stood still.

Fogs of blood exploded out of the two Soul Officials behind her. The force field was frozen solid and their bodies turned into ice blocks. They were knocked unconsciousness.

Hu…

Baylon took a deep breath. The mock earlier exhausted her a fair bit.

Clap… Clap… Clap…

Suddenly, clapping sounds were heard coming from above.

“Not a bad performance,” a cold emotionless voice was heard from the upper space.

Chapter 1144: Plot 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It struck a chord in Baylon as she lifted her head to look up.

A figure floating above came into sight. It was a face she recalled many times in enmity.

“Chinande!!” Baylon’s iris shrunk as unbearable fear stirred within her.

Yet at the same time, the hatred that once lived in her memory sunk in, intertwining with fear.

“Level Ten… Perpetual Motioner Holy Lord,” Baylon tightened her grip on the white blade. The handle of the blade was almost crushed in her hands.

Wham!!

In a blink of an eye, Chinande’s face magnified before her.

With no technique whatsoever and using a level ten gravitation in ten thousand folds, she was gravitationally knocked away with one punch.

Wham!

Vast amounts of gravitation amassed in his pale knuckle punched Baylon’s head without hesitation. Space in the universe seemed to collapse and warp around the knuckle. Even the rays of light assembled into this one punch.

A plain murderous intent was clearly emitting from Chinande.

Baylon watched his knuckle slam against her with eyes wide open without an ounce of strength to retaliate. Time seemed to have slowed down as the nerves in her body reacted with extreme speed but no matter how fast she was, it was powerless against the ten thousand fold gravitation.

Watching the knuckle nearing in, Baylon could somehow hear the nervous shouts of Clint, Red Moon; raging screams of White Winter and the lot as well as the roaring of the spaceship’s laser beams.

But it was all too late…

No one could have predicted the unexpected appearance of Chinande who was a level ten Holy Lord, personally attacking them who were merely supporting characters.

Yet it happened and to this point, any resistance would be futile.

“Am I… going to die?” She watched in a daze as the distorted gravitational knuckle closed in. She was not afraid of death. She was only dissatisfied. Dissatisfied with the fact that she grew too slow. Although she developed faster than most, she was still far from talking about revenge.

Unknowingly, she closed her eyes and waited for the arrival of her death.

Wham!!!

The expected pain did not come. It wasn’t just the same pain, even a tiny shred of collision wasn’t felt.

“Even if you’re going to die, you must make your opponent pay. I have taught you this, have you forgotten?” A deep voice rung in Baylon’s ear.

She popped open her eyes and saw a tough and large build figure in a red robe standing in front of her. He single-handedly held onto Chinande’s wielding right hand.

Shrouds of cold, white air were confronting the extensive gravitation of extreme oblivion emitted by Chinande.

“Bro…ther…” Baylon’s eyes widened. She stared at the figure before her in disbelief.

******

Within the spaceship.

“Lonnie!!”

Veins were showing all over Clint’s body. The charging action of pulling open the hatch was quickly stopped.

Phew…

White Winter grabbed onto his pounding heart. A single fleeting moment between life and death had him over the edge.

“I won’t be able to take a few times of this…” He took a deep puff of his cigarette but his trembling hands revealed his less-than-calm state.

“Thank goodness someone blocked…” The green-haired man went pale white. For a moment, the entire spaceship fell dead silent and everyone had their hearts in their mouth. The swift turn of events had caught even those who were experienced off guard.

“Who is that Holy Lord that rescued her?” Clint ran back and asked loudly.

“Let me see,” the man with green hair adjusted the portrait, magnifying it.

The magnified portrait has everyone on board stunned…

“This is… This…!” White Winter’s cigarette dropped onto the ground.

“It’s that fellow, Nonosiva!!” The first to regain senses was Red Moon, “How could it be! I couldn’t even sense it!?”

“Nonosiva?” The green-haired man was dumbfounded.

Clint shared a complicated expression.

“He’s Lonnie’s brother. Blood-related brother. Perhaps you’ll recognize the other name he goes by.”

“What?”

“Holy Lord of Scarlet Snow…”

“Holy Lord of Scarlet Snow, Garen!?” The man with green hair went sluggish. This name once shook the human race. There wasn’t one Mech Pilot that didn’t know this genius of an Energy Machinist.

“Faded… Creation…” At the same time, a cold and ruthless voice came from the outer world.

Crimson snowflakes appeared in space and slowly descended from above. It was no different within the spaceship.

******

Countless crimson snowflakes gathered in Garen’s palm. The snowflakes twirled around, belching terrifying chills. He flung his arm to hit Chinande’s chest.

A faded force field automatically sprung out and this level ten faded force field was absorbing the energy out of Chinande. This was an absolute force field that engulfed all creations.

Chinande raised his arm in an attempt to block but found no strength. The majority of his power absorbed as he began to channel.

“You!!”

Wham!!!!

Their palms directly met with each other.

The snowflakes plummeted out like scarlet blood, expanding onto Chinande’s body.

Garen’s palm broke Chinande’s arm with ease and then ruthlessly pressed onto his chest.

The freezing force flowed onto Chinande’s body and instantly froze his entire body into a snowy ice block.

A streak of puzzlement fleeted past Garen’s eyes as he pushed the ice block containing the frozen Chinande with one arm to move ahead with distance.

He generated the attacking punch of destruction that he hadn’t used for a while.

“Tenfold.”

The violent force was instantly raised by tenfold and a red ring as wide as a few meters burst open from Garen’s hand.

The muscles on his body expanded ferociously. His muscles could be seen expanding more than double its size through his clothes. They embodied black pythons, crawling on Garen’s body.

Kaboom!!

He wielded his thunderous arm in the dark of the space and flung it against the flying ice block containing Chinande.

Wham!!

The ice block was smashed into countless pieces of red ice crystals.

“It’s over…”

Garen stared at crushed bits and pieces of Chinande, before turning to look at Baylon.

The brother he had not seen in over a hundred years, or should he call her sister, seemed to have aged.

“Brother…” Baylon’s eyes welled with tears. It was unknown whether she was happy or sad.

“It must have been hard for you…” Garen extended his arm to pinch Baylon’s face. He gave her a gentle smile. Nonosiva had never flashed a smile at his sibling but this time, for the first time, he gave a sincere smile to Baylon.

Puff!

All of a sudden, a long white spear penetrated out of Garen’s abdomen from the back, striking through his body entirely.

Blood spewed out and splattered on Baylon’s face, clothes and body. She was momentarily stunned.

“Bro… Brother…!?”

Garen lowered his head to look at the long spear on his abdomen in surprise. The smile on his face that blossomed froze.

Everything fell into silence…

A gust of wind particles swayed from the sun. The broken pieces of red ice crystals were still scatteredly floating about. The engine of the spaceship was activated.

Time stood still at this very moment. This spear not only penetrated Garen’s body, it pierced through Baylon’s newfound glimmer of hope as well as the hope of all in the spaceship.

Baylon stared at Garen’s penetrated body in a daze. Her eyes that were first filled with joy and hope turned into despair.

“No!!!!”

Her sharp voice that was filled with hysteria echoed through space.

Her voice was heard by all witness on site but Baylon’s pain, despair, struggle and anger could never be felt by anyone.

Black tadpoles-like characters swiftly emerged out of Baylon’s eyes and wildly coated all over her body. As her voice of despair rang faster, so did the characters.

Garen stretched out his hand, trying to touch Baylon’s face but alas, he could not even succeed in this final little gesture.

Wham!!!

His body immediately exploded into a rain of blood and torn-apart limbs.

Behind him was a white figure floating in high space. It was Chinande! He did not perish!

Chinande’s high and above figure had transformed into a white-maned, young man dressed in pure white. Even the brows of this young man were white. He lowered his head to coldly stare at the exploded Garen.

“I didn’t plan to kill you this soon…” He muttered in a low voice.

“Yes, neither did I plan to kill you this soon…” A gentle voice was heard coming from behind him.

Swoosh!!

White King was startled. He felt a sharp pain from his abdomens. A bloody hand had pierced through his abdomens, stabbing straight from behind.

“You!!” White King’s body was imprisoned. A force of absolute confinement power took over his strength.

Puff!! His body became an illusion, broken apart into soapy bubbles. All that was left was a man with a tough build.

“Distortive power? This body is a phantom of distortion?!” The man was Garen who was killed earlier. He was dressed in the long robe of Scarlet Mourning Hall. He hung in space with a shocked face.

With a swish, a white spark drilled into him, combusting and scattering into a rain of blood as it exploded.

White King’s figure appeared at the other end of space. His cold gaze fixated on the rain of blood.

“Destiny will guide me to the righteous path!”

“Has destiny ever told you that this is not the right path?”

Another shadow of the Scarlet Morning Hall dashed out, tackling White King in close combat. Their attributes of concept clashed and rampaged in a feud.

Wham!

The shadow beat and ruptured into ructions of bloody rain.

“It is meaningless no matter how many times you come at it!” White King’s voice remained icy cold.

“Is it really meaningless?”

Another red figure flew over.

More and more red figures surfaced below. All of them were the people of Scarlet Mourning Hall dressed in red robes.

In a trance, a large crowd of Scarlet Mourning Hall lifted their heads and revealed their faces. All over hundred of them were carrying Garen’s face with a fake smile.

“!!!”

White King wasn’t the only one bamboozled, even Baylon who was still in pain, Clint and the rest were left bewildered.

Chapter 1145: Real or Fake 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Scarlet Snow Sect that followed behind were shaken on the spot.

“It’s Sect Master!! Sect Master Garen!! Hahahaha!! We’re saved!!’ Ice-Grand roared with laughter.

“I knew that Sect Master would be alright. He would definitely turn up! Definitely!!” Ice-Crack laughed out loud.

Two-Faced Person and rest appeared. A row of level tens stood together to form a large red force field to block off any residue of attacks from the outer world.

The four-armed woman stared intently at the battle between Garen and White King.

“If I’m right, Sect Master must be using some tactic to turn those from the Scarlet Mourning Hall into his embodiment. That isn’t White King’s true form either but rather a projection. His distortive attribute is able to mask everyone’s senses. The body that Garen sneaked attack earlier is most likely an illusion of distortion.”

“I don’t quite understand…” Two-Faced Person shook his head. The woman part of the face spoke. “It is chaotic now. What tactic did the Sect Master use to occupy the body?”

“White King first disguised as Chinande to scheme against the Sect Master. He must have predicted that Sect Master would turn up at that moment and indeed he did but he did not succeed in his goal,” the four-armed woman fell deep into thought and provided an explanation closest to the truth.

“Then where is the real Sect Master? And where is the true form of White King?” Two-Faced Person asked in return.

The four-armed woman shook her head.

Who schemed against who and who really won against who? No matter Garen or White King, they were plotting against one another.

******

White Royal Palace.

In front of the dark golden crystal.

White King stood silently before the crystal rock. The crystal clearly reflected his stone-cold face.

“I see you’re well prepared.”

“I should say the same to you too,” Garen replied in the crystal. “It seems that the strength of your projection is no better than my embodiments,” Garen’s eye revealed a hint of a smile.

“Even possessing a unique attribute, you shouldn’t be able to have that many projecteory embodiments,” White King pondered.

******

Battlefield.

Beams of white rays shone from another part of dark space. The string of beams turned into white rings and emerged in an airspace far from where Garen and White King were battling it out.

Figures of vast spirits appeared in the rings. These figures each carried an identity emblem of the Human Nine Emperors. The four people that lead the pack had a larger build than most, doubling or even tripling the height of an average person.

These were the Human Nine Emperor force tailing behind White King’s activity.

At the other end, another group of the white crowd arrived, standing opposite of the Star Emperors. They were all affinity forces of White King. These people were the strongest forces wielded by White King. All thirty of them were Perpetual Motioner and above experts.

These were hidden chess pieces which both parties placed in ambush but now it seemed that these chess pieces would not yield its worth as only the projection of White King made it here so destroying it would amount to little. Moreover, they were uncertain about the peculiar appearance of Scarlet Snow Holy Lord, Garen. Prior to comprehending Garen’s attitude and capabilities, the Nine Emperor force decided against acting recklessly.

At this exact moment, White King, the Human Star Emperors and the rest were staring at the hundred over Garens floating in space. No one spoke a word. These hundred over people were valiant of the Scarlet Mourning Hall yet all sighted at such a strange scene.

A mountain of red-robed Garen were amassed together in a red cloud, facing off White King.

“Now… What are you planning to do? White King…” All the Garens spoke with voices strung together. Their force fields gathered to form a resonance phenomenal. Sharp yet peculiar.

At the same time, White King’s strongest team — the Perpetual Motioners, each lifted their heads. The royal family of White King and all Perpetual Motioner’s followers were bearing the face of Garen.

“You…!!” White King was stunned. The Perpetual Motioners were at a certain level and was one stage of a difference from him, a Saint. Yet now they were controlled by Garen’s peculiar ability. This drastically changed his original plans.

“My King!!” Suddenly, a weak voice was heard.

It was Linora!!

White King spun around and saw Linora appear in space, held by Garen with one hand on the neck. She gave a struggle.

“Garen…!!!” A never-before fiery of rage blared out White King’s eyes for the first time, “You’re seeking death!!!”

He could ignore his parents but Linora who took care of him since he was young was his weakness.

“My King!”

“Your Majesty!!”

Out of the blue, many of the Garens recovered their original identity and face. They anxiously shouted.

“Don’t bother about us! Kill him! For Finite!!”

“Save me! My King! Save me!!”

“Avenge us, Your Majesty!!”

“Long Live Finite!!!”

A jumble of voices rang into White King’s ear.

These chaotic voices that couldn’t be censored or dare not be censored struck chords in him, making him flighty and impetuous.

“My King!!” The real Chinande appeared by White King, “we have to decide on the spot, either to retreat or kill! Please decide!” His stone cold face bore no expression. Perhaps he played so many personalities for a long length of time that he completely lost the ability to be expressive.

Of all the people there, only he and a few princes of the royal family were not possessed. The remaining experts swiftly gathered by his side. Facing the large quantity of Garens encircling White King, the originally Finite squad had turned into the enemy’s base camp. He was in a dangerous situation.

“Retreat?” A hint of struggle creept into White King’s eyes. No matter how powerful or skillful talent he possessed, he still had important people in his life. He was a regular person that hadn’t live more than a thousand years. Even if he was talented, the most talented, even if he had seen destiny’s general trend, even if he had plans to sacrifice for his ideals, White King was still a human no older than three hundred years old. He was a Finite.

He carried with him the hope of rising and uniting the Finite people. No matter what, he must not lose. Garen’s cloning abilities had been tested and it was at the peak of Perpetual Motioner Holy Lord level but as it hoisted the attribute concept of confinement, it made his movements sluggish.

However, this wasn’t the main point. If he were to make a move prior to getting to the bottom of Garen’s peculiar ability, his attack may cause the death of his own people!!

This was the reason for him holding back.

Moreover, a Regent Level wouldn’t be able to go up against him and it would be the same for two or three Regent Levels as well. He would be hot on their tails but it was unknown how many of the Human Nine Emperors arrived. It was possible that they would regroup and with Scarlet Snow Holy Lord, Garen in the mix, the outcome of this sort of battle simply could not be predicted.

In the face of war, the Human Nine Emperors had proved their worth. If five of them were to team up, they could face White King’s distortive attribute while the remaining three who had equilateral skills with the Twelve Golden Merit Blue Princes. However, there had been a turn of events.

“Retreat!!”

This word made out of White King’s mouth with difficulty.

“Retreat? That easily?” Garen’s low pitch laughter rang without fear in space.

Phew…!

Figures of Garen flew straight to White King and his group. Each figure bore heavy and terrifying energy of confinement attribute.

“Retreat!!””Retreat retreat retreat!!”

Voices echoes within the experts under White King.

In the dark inverse space, the white troops hasten their move backward. A large distortive hole appeared behind them. It was a leaping black hole.

The mountain of Garens charged towards the white troops, launching assaults in kamikaze mode. Streaks of red glow were fired within the low-level Finite troops.

“Distortion! Ancient Void!!” White King suppressed his anger and extended his arm to grab a hold of amassed Garen figures.

A large blob of transparent distortion shot from his hand and split up to little blotches, charging towards the Garens and encircling them. The blotches held the berserk Garens in captive within the distortion, sealing them up.

There were more transparent distortion that scattered down like raindrops firing at the Garens in attempt to resolve all in one.

“Solidify everything in existence!” Garen’s voice was heard, “Faded Creation…”

One of the Garens flew up vertically. Pure huge crystalized wings were formed at his back. He suffused himself between the once white robes and golden helmets.

With crackling sounds, his back emerged countless crystalized vines. These vines took root within the void and grew to all directions to form a large, white windscreen

Red snowflakes descended at this moment in the universe, fluttering about. In a space of a few hundred light years, all was covered with the scarlet snowflakes.

Everything that was touched by the snowflakes, regardless of foe and friend, experienced stiffness in their bodies. They lost all will to retaliate and were immediately imprisoned.

The snowflakes counteracted against the transparent distortion, annihilating each other and resulting in a standstill.

******

The Human Race legion.

“What should we do now?!” Bull King, one of the Nine Emperors looked at the strongest Thousand Pillar King.

“Let’s hold our horses for the moment,” Thousand Pillar King calmly concluded.

“Why!?” Now would be the best time to pursue an attack!” Bull King did not understand. “Do you think that White King could have any tactics to counterattack?”

“No, not that,” Thousand Pillar King frowned. “I am not worried but White King but rather the Scarlet Snow Holy Lord.”

“You’re saying that… the battle where the Energy Machinists were annihilated…” Bull King immediately came to his senses. The two were currently the strongest of the Human Nine Emperors. Their decision would impact the movement of the entire human race.

Chapter 1146: Real or Fake 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It is nearly impossible to kill off someone of the Regent-Level. Even if we continued our pursuit, other than taking care of this projection and its base combat power, what else could we possibly do?” Thousand Pillar King looked on meticulously. “On the other hand, if the Scarlet Snow Holy Lord could use such an abnormally large-scale ability against the Finite People, he can easily do the same to my people… Don’t forget, back when we just became the Nine Emperors, only Sawtooth King didn’t join the encirclement…”

“Furthermore, if my instincts are right…” Thousand Pillar King’s gaze moved towards the direction the White King retreated in. “White King seemed to have incurred some injuries at the end of it all.”

“Injuries?!” Bull King slowly responded, his facial expressions tensed up. “You are talking about… The one that managed to confront him alone the last time, right?”

Looking at Thousand Pillar King silently nodding, the two great Regent-Levels’ huge bodies silently faded into the void, trying to hide their current emotions from each other.

******

“Retreat! Retreat! Retreat!”

The Finite’s elite army was rapidly retreating through the Jumping Black Hole in a frenzy.

The flurry of red snowflakes formed a red snowstorm, whirling through a pitch-dark tunnel of the Jumping Black Hole, closing in on them.

Garen relentlessly pursued them, one of his clones had already captured one of the White King’s most important men – Lanerra.

Her entire body was engulfed in the red snowstorm. She was trying desperately to escape, showing no signs of stopping.

At that point, this type of spine-chilling abnormal ability had stopped appearing.

In actuality, this was not some amazingly powerful ability, he could only fully possess one body at a time and superficially apply an Imprisonment Attribute on it. This was a method that allowed him to enter his opponent’s dreamland and take control over their Willpower. It was a unique ability of the Void Creatures and something Ancient Endor was proficient at dealing with.

The reason why there were so many Garen clones, was that out of all of these clones, only one clone could utilize its true potential at any given point, applying the Imprisonment Attributes to his targets. The remaining were just there purely to hypnotize the other targets and drag them into their respective dreamlands. This was a basic Void Creature ability.

However, by making all his clones appear at once, it managed to leave the White King and the other experts completely shell-shocked. It gave off the impression that all of Garen’s clones were simultaneously utilizing their fullest potential.

Naturally, their fight or flight response kicked in and they all retreated in a state of panic.

“Linora!” The White King’s projection was glaring daggers at Garen’s clone.

Within the Jumping Tunnel, both parties did not dare to make a move. If you made any missteps in your attacks you’d easily be tossed into a space-time distortion with no way of returning.

The White King’s eyes started to glow with a soft white light. Looking at Linora who was in the hands of the Garen clone, he suddenly reacted.

“Impossible! You couldn’t have captured Linora! She should’ve been accompanying Empress Dowager back in the God Palace! To capture someone from under Empress Dowager’s nose, you’re far from powerful enough to achieve that!”

The Linora in Garen’s hands suddenly smiled slyly. With a poof of air, she turned into a ball of scarlet red gas and flew up Garen’s nose.

“As expected, it did not manage to fool you.”

Garen clapped his hands together as if trying to brush away the nonexistent dust on his palms.

“However, it wasn’t ever my intention to try to fool you. To be able to fight to such a degree, you’re not half bad after all.”

Garen once again clapped his hands lightly.

Two crisp sounding claps could be heard.

The White King’s kin who were being pursued by the snowstorm and all the ‘possessed’ Perpetual Motion Level experts suddenly dissolved like soap bubbles, as if everything earlier was all an illusion.

From the beginning up till now there were never any reinforcements that arrived from the White King’s kin or Perpetual Motion Level expert teams. There was nothing left around Garen, even the people in the Scarlet Mourning Hall had vanished.

“As you might’ve already guessed, your kin are probably still desperately moving towards the venue of our battle just now, sending themselves to their deaths. Don’t forget that there are still four out of the Nine Emperors over there… Hehe…” Garen revealed a cruel grin. “You, on the other hand, would not even make it in time if you rush there right now. It’s already too late.”

Hearing this, the White King’s face immediately turned green.

He looked around at his surroundings. The group of White King’s men all had terrible expressions on their face. As it turned out, from the very start, what they thought was mercilessly pursuing them was just an unbelievably lifelike illusion. They were completely fooled by Garen’s self-directed play of illusions to the point where they had all retreated in fear, most likely causing the demise of the Perpetual Motion Level team that headed over as reinforcements, trapping them in a Regent-Level ambush.

If word of this got out, it would be the most disgraceful incident ever in Finite People history.

At this moment, in the Jumping Tunnel, the White King and his group of experts, including a few Prince Levels and another Regent Level had a terrible look on their faces. They all simultaneously looked over at the Chinande who was the first who suggested the idea of retreating to the White King.

‘Chinande’ let out a sly grin. With a poof of smoke, his body turned into gas, dispersing into the void.

Within the Jumping Tunnel, there was a clear separation of white team and red team. The illusions slowly started to get dispelled.

Garen’s side seemed to be shrouded by a mist that resembled red smoke. He was the only one in the entire red team.

On the other hand, the White King’s team consisted of him and a few Prince Levels. As for the people in the Scarlet Mourning Hall, they were all deep in slumber. They all had a beetle-shaped gas body placed on their faces, covering their noses and mouths, causing them to sleep soundly.

In other words, from the very beginning, the White King’s projection and the Prince Levels were all in a state of isolated illusions.

Garen did not even lay a finger on the White King in actuality, it was merely an illusion.

Real or fake, which part was real and which was fake, at this point, the White King could not make out the difference. This was precisely what Garen was aiming for.

“Well then, this time, it’s my victory…” Garen let out a cheeky smile.

“Ghostly Trickery!” The White King’s face was icy cold. He furiously waved his palm towards Garen.

A bundle of twisted power directly shot towards Garen’s body, blowing up Garen’s body into ashes with a loud boom.

As Garen died, this body he possessed slowly revealed its original appearance. It turned out to be one of the average Non-Falling Level experts in the Scarlet Mourning Hall.

The red mist that was shrouding Garen’s body earlier also started to fade away, slowly vanishing into thin air. The beetle-shaped gas bodies on the faces of the people in the Scarlet Mourning Hall also started to dissipate.

“Immediately contact Latva!” The White King rapidly ordered.

“We’ve already contacted him, but…” The Prince Level beside him turned pale. “According to our recon spies, Latva’s team got ambushed by the combined power of the four Star Emperors. They were completely wiped out…”

Boom!!

A huge ball of twisted energy burst from the White King’s fist, nearly causing the entire Jumping Tunnel to collapse. His gaze was cold to the extremes.

“Garen!!”

******

Original Battleground

The four of the Nine Emperors looked at the destroyed remains of the area. The remains of the corpses of the White King’s kin and the Perpetual Motion Levels were scattered all over the place.

With their combined strength, the four struck at the key point of the White King’ kin and Perpetual Motion Levels’ jumps with utter precision. Once again demonstrating the fearsome power of when the four Regent Level work together. In an instant, they had mustered up enough power to destroy even stars. With all this power concentrated at a certain point, the result would be the space surrounding the area to immediately collapse. A part of the Perpetual Motion Level was directly disintegrated on the spot, imploding into a black hole causing an even larger space-time collapse. Hence, before the remaining reinforcement managed to land, they had already been sent off to another galaxy countless light years away.

The overall result was that all of the White King’s strongest kin were completely wiped out.

The Thousand Pillar King stared at the red-shirted Garen in front of him with a complicated expression.

“At the end of the day, how much of it was real and how much of it was fake? Even I couldn’t tell anymore.”

“Such a masterful execution. For the White King to have made such an enemy, it’s just…” Bull King nodded his head in agreement.

At this moment in the Negative Spatial Universe, there were only four groups of people left.

Thousand Pillar King and the forces of the Nine Emperors, the Scarlet Snow Sect’s Double-Faced Man and other experts, and the flying ship that Baylon, Clint, and the others were piloting.

Lastly, there was the lone red-robed Garen who was floating in space.

At this moment, Garen was like the most average energy machinist, facing the Thousand Pillar King in silence.

Since the Thousand Pillar King had taken action earlier, he had revealed his actual physical body. He was the size of an entire planet, solemnly staring down at Garen, who was sesame-sized in comparison.

The two were like David and Goliath, even if it was just based on the aura of their energy forces, there was definitely more than a whole level in difference. However, Thousand Pillar King looked very solemn at the moment. If we ignore the difference in size, he looked no different from a serious and calm middle-aged uncle.

“This current body of yours, it’s not your actual body, right?” He softly asked.

Garen smiled.

“Your Majesty Thousand Pillar King, whether it is real or fake, it doesn’t really matter much, does it? What’s important is that it got the job done, is it not?”

“What a powerful junior I have. Never would I have thought that just after slightly more than a hundred years of my slumber, an expert with such outstanding talents as this would suddenly appear,” the Bull King was repeatedly praising Garen as he looked over at him, “Scarlet Snow Holy Lord, if my gut feeling is correct, the ability you used just now should be something to do with the dream world of Void Creatures and Guise-type abilities.”

“Bull King is indeed very sharp,” Garen nodded while smiling, “In reality, my actual strength pales in comparison to the White King’s. It’s just that I had some unique attributes and it was his first time dealing with this type of ability. He was completely unaware of this ability that he was completely unfamiliar with, giving him a huge disadvantage. However, it seems like I won’t be as lucky the next time around.”

“Well said,” Thousand Pillar King nodded in agreement. Even he could tell that Garen’s actual strength is far lower than the White King’s. He had to rely heavily on this type of abnormal ability that utilizes deception and confusion. However, once the opponent had done adequate preparation work, it would be highly improbable if he wanted to achieve a similar favorable result. The scientist of the Finite People would definitely not ignore such an abnormal ability, with their research, they are bound to come up with strategies and countermeasures against this trick in no time.

“Then, we must show our gratitude to Scarlet Snow Holy Lord for the results of this battle,” Thousand Pillar King said cheerfully.

“The pleasure’s mine,” Garen answered politely.

Looking at the Thousand Pillar King and company leaving the scene, Garen finally turned around, gazing at the passed out Baylon, Clint and his crew in the flying ship and the group of Scarlet Snow members who were looking on anxiously by the sidelines.

Chapter 1147: Opportunity 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Due to some personal reasons, I cannot physically be with you guys at the moment,” his smile on his face slowly faded away. “As a matter of fact, this body is not my actual physical body. I have seen all your hard work and effort over the years.”

“Sect Master, please come back!” Ice-Ocean stood forward, “We need you, the Scarlet Snow Alliance needs your presence.”

More importantly, the potential of all the experts with the Distorted Seed parasite that were present at the location relied on Garen’s existence. Once Garen died, all of the Energy Machinists here may very well return to their former weak selves.

This was what worried the Two-Faced Person and the other Level Ten Perpetual Motioners the most. Since Garen went missing, they all had a serious feeling of unease lingering in their hearts. In an attempt to release themselves from his shackles, they have tried to research the principles and theories behind the Distorted Seed over the years but to no avail.

“That’s right Sect Master, after so many years of improvement, the Scarlet Snow Sect is no longer the small sect from the past. The only thing lacking now is a true blue Regent Level in our ranks. Once you’ve returned, our Scarlet Snow Sect will break through boundaries and become a real Regent Level force! The human’s Tenth Great Royal Star Force!!” The Two-Faced Person shouted out.

Garen smiled bitterly as he shook his head.

“It’s not that I don’t want to return, it’s just that my physical body is now at the White Royal Palace, unable to escape confinement. The White King’s physical body is constantly monitoring me. Unless there comes a day where you guys can manage to defeat the White King and break into the White Royal Palace…”

“White Royal Palace!!”

Who would have thought that Garen’s physical body was at the Finite People’s main camp. This was something that the Two-Faced Person and the other experts could have never expected.

That place was completely surrounded by countless Finite People experts. Even for the Thousand Pillar King, the epitome of the Regent Level, it would be a suicide mission breaking into their defense, much less for the average Regent Levels.

White King was one of the top Regent Levels, an existence that boasted itself as the unmatched peak within this universe. Furthermore, within the Finite Royalty, there was also the White King’s mysterious mother – Goddess Dowager. There were also the Twelve Golden Merit Blue Princes, twelve Regent Level experts!

With this kind of lineup, even if we get another Regent Level with a similarly strong power as the White King, it was still an impossible mission.

“White Royal Palace…” Not just the Scarlet Snow Sect members, but even Clint and company on the Flying Ship fell silent.

“No wonder you went missing for so many years. You got yourself stuck in the White King’s home base,” Red Moon sighed. “It looks like he understood a bit more about essences. For someone who understood the concept of essences, when facing others who have not, they would have an absolute suppressing power against them. This effect can be apparent with even the slightest bit of understanding.”

“You mentioned essence, but what exactly is it?” White Winter paused for a long while before asking, his gaze locked onto Garen’s eyes.

“That’s the foundation and the basis behind all Regent Levels,” Red Moon explained.

While listening to his explanation, Clint and the others started to feel more at ease as they were no longer in imminent danger. They listened on curiously at Red Moon’s explanations.

“In theory, the coverage area of essence could go up to an infinite distance. Currently, the furthest essence coverage is wielded by the one known as the weirdest Regent Level, Golden Thread Flower King. His essence can cover an area with the radius of up to hundreds of light years apart, affecting the people within its coverage. It can completely cover the entire Solar System and even its bordering areas.”

“That’s absurd!!?” Clint’s eyes widened. “Essence coverage of hundreds of light years! Then, what about the weakest? What’s the smallest coverage area?”

Red Moon clicked his tongue.

“What’s so absurd about it? Strength is similar to essence, it has a concentration level. The more concentrated it is, naturally, the coverage area would be smaller. If you want to increase the coverage area, naturally it will cause the concentration level to drop. However, once the concentration level drops below a certain extent, it would become more or less useless. You need to, at the very least ensure that there is the lowest level of effect.”

“That’s true…” Clint rubbed his chin, understanding what Red Moon was saying.

“Garen’s abilities look to be similar to that of a Void Creature’s Dream Abilities. It seems to be very strong, very real, and its coverage is area is also quite large. However, he has a fatal weak point,” Red Moon coldly stated.

“What weak point!?” White Winter’s face tensed up.

“His actual strength is too weak. Thus, he has to rely on illusions to make his opponents think they are under confinement. However, once they learn about his essence, their subconsciousness will no longer think he has the ability to put them under confinement, breaking the illusion and causing an opposite result,” Red Moon calmly explained. “To put it simply, his ability is to deceive his opponent’s nervous system, making them see certain things or think that they are confined and are unable to move. In reality, he was just manipulating their nervous systems, using it to create illusions, not actually doing anything in the real world.”

“It’s like inducing a dream on the opponents!”

“Exactly! That’s how you can look at it!” Red Moon confirmed. “With that in mind, that is why his essence coverage area is very wide. As long as there are sentient organisms in the area, it will be under his coverage. This might even exceed the Golden Thread Flower King, reaching a terrifying level. However, it’s only flaw is that once the opponents do targeted preparation on him, it would be extremely hard for his abilities to achieve the same effects. In other words, what’s fake will always remain fake. No matter how real it looks, once it gets seen through by someone, it would become useless.”

“This type of ability seems to be powerful on paper, but in actuality, it is very weak,” White Winter nodded in agreement.

“That’s right… Real or fake, if only Garen’s potential was just a bit stronger, he might actually be able to use this essence of his and reach a terrifying level,” Red Moon said regretfully. “However, I found out that his essence had already been completely locked in this current degree. I don’t know why that is the case.”

Although Red Moon was a Regent Level of the older generation and his experience could help him see through a lot of things, he was still clueless about the truth behind this issue.

******

“My essence…” When Garen was asked about this, he let out a slight smile.

“It’s confinement, freezing. It’s also illusions and dreamland,” he calmly answered.

“Between the Regent Levels, what is the deciding factor for the difference in potential?” Whilst Garen was around, the Two-Faced Person took the opportunity to ask what he wanted to know. He was now at the very peak of Perpetual Motion, with only one last step to reach Regent Level. He understood that essence was a concept, but he could not fully understand the details regarding it.

“Regent Level…” Garen went deep into thought. “It’s the confrontation between concepts. Regent Levels back in the Perpetual Motion Level era gained unlimited strength. However, Regent Levels nowadays gained unlimited Willpower. When Willpower condenses to its maximum point, it would naturally become essence. Regarding this, it’s best for you to find your own essence that suits yourself the most, then only can you become a true Regent Level.”

“My own essence…” The Two-Faced Person and the other Level Ten Perpetual Motioners started thinking.

Garen was also sincerely hoping that some of them would manage to attain Regent Level. Thus, he decided to pass down his wisdom that he attained to aid them as well.

“In my opinion, the difference between Regent Levels does not lie within strength. Since everyone can freely gain unlimited strength, it was not a point of contention. The key difference should be in the difference of one’s essence, and one’s grasp and understanding of it. The confrontations between essences is dependence on one’s depth in understanding. Whoever can grasp their own essences better shall have a greater impact on the battle. In turn, they will have a greater chance to dispel their opponent’s essences, allowing their own essence to affect the opponent. However, no matter how much you try to suppress or affect your opponent, it wouldn’t be likely that you will be able to one-shot them. In other words, the difference would not be too big.”

Garen continued.

“With that in mind, there wouldn’t be any quick deaths between two Regent Levels. Unless it’s a fight to the death or a battle of endurance, most of the time the Regent Levels would survive these battles. Unless, of course, an unexpected situation occurs.”

“In that case, would all Regent Level battles eventually turn dragged out long battles?” A girl with four arms asked. The Two-Faced Person and her were currently the ones with the strongest potential within the Scarlet Snow Alliance. She was also one of the representatives for the other Level Tens.

“Would Regent Level battles ever not be a dragged out long battle?” Garen returned her question.

With this question, the people at the scene came to a sudden realization. From the start of the battle between humans and the Finite People, there were not any Regent Level casualties. The last Regent Level casualty was from an unimaginably long time ago.

Garen put out his right hand, five balls of pale red light appeared on his fingertips.

“Go.”

He shot the red lights into the air, attaching them onto the five strongest people present.

Almost as if a hallucination, the red light seeped into their skin without them feeling anything.

“This is…” The Two-Faced Person frowned.

“It’s a bit of my essence that can attach itself to your bodies, If you have any updates or urgent situations, you can concentrate your Willpower on it and send a message to me. I should be able to receive it,” Garen explained. “My essence is not one that has high offensive power, so it’s slightly more troublesome.”

“There aren’t many essences with high offensive power, supposedly only the Fresh Blood Holy Lord, who is missing in action, had a purely offensive essence. Unfortunately, after she challenged the White King, she went missing, or she might even have died…” Garen thought back to his last encounter with the crazy lady of the Wraith Royalty. At first, he straight up shot a star, almost completely crushing her.

“Alright, my time is almost up,” Garen looked at his current body. This physical body he possessed belonged to a Non-Falling Level expert at the Scarlet Mourning Hall. However, this possession was not permanent, it was only available for a temporary amount of time.

“Sect Master…” Ice-Ocean and company sincerely hoped for Garen’s safe return. If the Scarlet Snow Alliance was led by Garen, it would no doubt improve a lot. Instead of having to cowardly live under the protection of Sawtooth King.

“Say no more, I will continue to watch over you guys in the White Royal Palace. Perpetual Motioners without an essence will have no way of defending against my possession, White King would not completely disregard my presence. He wouldn’t dare to take any direct action towards you guys. He knows that once I no longer have anything to linger on to, it will result in both of our mutually assured destruction,” Garen seriously stated.

To tell the truth, he did not actually fully attain Regent Level. In reality, he used a trick, utilizing Shadow Dragon’s essence to consider himself half a Regent Level.

Thus, his possession was completely vulnerable to the White King’s projection. From the very beginning, He only used ambushes and illusions, temporarily pulling the dreamland into reality, overlapping it. Only then did he manage to create such a large effect. However, in actuality, the damage he had done was pitifully little, far incomparable to when the Thousand Pillar King completely annihilated the White King’s kin later on.

If the White King decides to disregard him as a threat and take action, he would not be able to do anything against it.

“Now return… I will talk to Sawtooth King a bit later…” Garen finally started to feel that his possessed body was at its limit. Looking back at the flying ship, Clint and company were looking at him through the ship’s glass window.

Baylon was still passed out unconscious.

“The stimulus this time, should be able to replace the stimulus from the Battle of Ice Age?” Garen silently pondered, “Hopefully she can successfully awaken…”

In the grand scheme of things, Baylon was originally affected by the death of her brother, causing her to completely awaken, rapidly becoming a top level Royal Star. On the other hand, Clint was also working hard, rapidly growing up. This is now their true turning points.

Chapter 1148: Opportunity 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen had a feeling that, ever since he started using the void crystal to confine himself, the muscular structures of his body had started becoming, leaving his body in a state of a suspended animation.

Even he himself did not know how his body is continuing to exist, neither did he understand why his body was being confined. He just understood that his willpower could still go through a Dream Weave. His hypothesis for this was that the essence for Dream Weaving is of a higher level the essence for confinement.

The superficial confinement essence that Garen knew could at most dispel some of the other average Regent Levels’ essences or be used when conversing with the White King. Only when he was facing a non-Regent Level existence could it have any obvious effect.

When facing an actual Regent Level, it would be extremely underwhelming.

He had a hunch that ever since he forcefully grasped half of his essence, especially the confinement essence, all the way up until when he grasped the Dream Weaving essence, his entire worldview had been flipped upside down.

The world consisted not only of the material world but also the Dream World where our spirits are intertwined with each other and a lot of other things that cause waves and ripples, creating a non-material world.

The entire universe seemed to become even more vast and mysterious, completely unpredictable.

This essentially showed the truth in the statement that “the more you know, the less you understand.”

******

Finite God Palace

The blue sky was filled with white clouds slowly drifting through the air. Golden sun rays showered down from above, landing on the huge white palace below and reflecting on a pale gold surface.

The White King was moving up along the pure white stairway. His silhouette would glow every few hundred steps, instantaneously leaping a large distance, teleporting him to the next section of the stairway.

The white palace stood in solitude in the middle of a huge white desert, surrounded by an endless sea of white sand. Under the light of the golden sun, the entire desert seemed extremely glaring and beautiful.

Soon, the White King arrived in front of the palace entrance in his white robes.

As he stepped forward, the grand stone gates that were dozens of meters tall automatically opened to two sides, revealing a deep and long hall.

The floor of the hall was tiled with thick, white bricks, with every brick being a few hundred meters in width and length. The entire palace looked big enough to house an entire city. It was purely white, wide, and completely empty.

The White King walked into the hall, gazing at the center of the hall, looking at a white circular platform floating in the air.

“Mother, it has been many years. Once again, I’m here to visit you,” White King’s calm voice echoed through the hall.

The Finite King and Queen had been killed by their own son. After the White King inherited the throne, he felt no remorse over his father’s death. However, he bestowed the title “Goddess Dowager” to the mother that he personally killed and had the girl that he loved the most, Linora, take care of this tomb behind him. This caused a huge commotion throughout the world back when he first decided to do it.

“You had personally killed my physical body, all for the sake of stopping me from interfering in your grand scheme. Now, why do you still have the leisure of time to come here and visit me?” A lady’s cold voice rang from the floating stone platform.

“Killing you was not my intention, it was all part of our destiny,” The White King answered calmly. “The reason behind my visit is partially to see you. I also wish to pay Linora a visit.”

The lady coldly snorted out. She stopped speaking and remained silent.

A moment later, a blue-shirted girl appeared from behind a tall stone pillar from the other side of the hall.

“Your Highness.”

The girl’s face was covered with a white cloth, her body looked thin and frail, almost like a willow in the wind, as if she was gonna collapse as she walked on by.

“Lin,” The White King walked up to greet her. Looking at the girl standing in front of her, he let out a huge sigh of relief. “As long as you’re still fine.”

“What happened, Your Highness?” She asked in confusion. However, before she even finished her question, she was caught in the White King’s embrace. Removing the white cloth covering her face, he passionately kissed her.

Surprisingly, underneath the white cloth, the girl’s face was not beautiful at all, as a matter of fact, it was completely hideous.

Small eyes, a snub nose, big mouth, and a complexion that was barely decent. However, no matter how one looked at it, one could not see her as a beautiful person. She could not even be considered average. The only word that could describe her was “hideous”.

However, the way the White King looked at her was one of unconditional loving. He did not care about Linora’s physical appearance. In his eyes, Linora was like a gemstone that constantly emitted a bright shine. The beauty of her spirit and willpower was incomparable to anyone else in the world.

“Your Highness… You’re uncalm again…” Linora softly touched the White King’s hair. She was much shorter than him, so the White King bent down to compensate for their height difference, resting his head on her chest.

“Yes… Whenever I start to feel anxious, you’re the only one who can calm me down,” While the White King’s head rested on her chest, they looked like a couple of lovers, but something similar to a maternal bond could also be felt.

Linora was the absolute source of the White King’s motivation.

“What’s the matter? Did your father’s consciousness escape again? Or did all the Finite Princes band together to start a revolution?” The Goddess Dowager’s voice coldly rang out behind him.

“It’s only a small problem,” The White King raised his head from Linora’s embrace. “I’ll resolve it soon, you don’t need to worry, Mother. You just focus on taking care of yourself in this place.”

His visit was mainly to check up to confirm that Linora was alright. Garen’s trick managed to give him quite a fright.

Since he had achieved his goal, the White King stood up, once again kissing Linora on her cheeks.

“Your Highness, emergency meeting. Prince Dragonrock requests that you get there immediately, it’s about what happened to your kin this time around…” A man’s voice could be heard from the palace entrance.

“Understood,” White King replied plainly.

“Go…” Linora gently caressed his face. “I will always be here.”

“Mm.”

White King’s gaze revealed a hint of reluctance, as he held on to her hands.

******

After the battle in the Negative Space, Scarlet Snow Holy Lord Garen’s name had spread throughout the two nebulae inhabited by the two races.

The combat evaluation report had also reached the Head of the Regent Level Force’s table.

“Scarlet Snow Holy Lord Garen: Regent Level.

Danger Level – Extreme.

Combat Level – Regent Level, ranking unknown.

Combat Coverage: Over three hundred light years (Previously initiated an illusion affecting all organisms within a three hundred and twenty-one light year radius.)

Concept Type: Confinement, Illusion. Precise details unknown.

Special Ability – Possession, similar to Projection. Limits and requirements unknown. There is an eighty percent chance that utilizing his potential will allow him to possess only one body unit and utilizing the body’s full power.

Positions and Authorities – Alliance Leader of the Scarlet Snow Alliance, Scarlet Snow Sec Sect Master, an existence of the Human’s Tenth Star Emperor (Regent Level).”

After that, the report had investigated most of his growth and experiences in his life since he was young. Many academics had also started to research on the sudden exponential jumps in his growth progress as his potential had an irregular growth progress.

In the last battle in the Negative Space, although he had the Thousand Pillar King and other Regent Levels backing him up, the trick Garen used to deceive the White King into retreating to buy time managed to intrigue a lot of tacticians’ interest. Someone had also leaked out the information that Garen’s actual body was still in the White Royal Palace, being confined by the Dark Gold Void Crystal, the strongest material known to mankind. One of the reasons he was still alive was because he had grasped the foundation of the Confinement Essence.

For a Regent Level under confinement, he still managed to have such a big impact. This instantly made the days of most of the higher-ups.

After the Human’s Nine Emperor forces’ research and discussion, they had also officially bestowed the title “King of Scarlet Snow” to Garen.

However, a lot of people thought that instead of King of Scarlet Snow, Garen was more suited for the titles “Crystal King” and “King of Lies”. While being confined in the crystal, he relied on illusions and lies, causing huge losses for the White King and his men. In retrospect, the King of Lies would be more appropriate, considering his essence.

Thus, the official title only existed in name, Garen’s colloquial title became the two aforementioned. Those who were fond of him would call him the Crystal King; whilst those who were not would call him the King of Lies.

The gossip about him also started to die down as time went on.

The Scarlet Snow Alliance had gained independence, founding a whole new territory in another galaxy, officially becoming the Tenth Great Star Emperor Force. They were recognized by the other forces, officially joining the Human Alliance.

However, the mysterious Garen, due to his special circumstances, could not be present for most of the Regent Level events. Naturally, Scarlet Snow’s ranking had also dropped to the last place.

In a blink of an eye, a hundred years had passed.

The humans and the Finite People had once again been in countless wars, but all of them ended without any definite winner. On the other hand, Garen had occasionally participated in these battles. The frequency of his appearance seemingly getting less and less.

As for Clint and the company who joined the Scarlet Snow Alliance, they had all matured into a new generation of experts. Clint had entered Level Eight while Baylon directly attained Level Nine. She had achieved terrific results in numerous battles, once even surviving a fight with a Level Ten Perpetual Motioner in one piece. They had successfully propelled themselves up to the circles of the top ranks. In one of the reconnaissance missions, Baylon managed to use her ability to mimic one of the Finite experts, successfully deceiving the countless layers of strict security and defense, obtaining important information on the enemy, and allowing the human forces to heavily injure three of the Finite Golden Merit Blue Princes.

With that success, she had been dubbed the “Almighty Woman” and her name spread across the two nebulae.

******

White Royal Palace

Garen was still his same old self. There was literally nothing that had changed about him. The confinement essence not just halted all activity on his body, it also stopped all time from passing on his body.

The “him” now and the “him” from two hundred years ago had literally no differences.

As compared to the Confinement Power in the beginning, the crystal’s current power had been raised to a terrifying level. The Confinement Power seemed to have risen ceaselessly. At the start, Garen could still use voice transmission with the White King through the crystal, utilizing his understanding of a part of the confinement essence to transmit voice exchanges. However, now, not even a whimper could be transmitted.

Garen felt that the Shadow Dragon’s essence seemed to have already been increased to a level that he could no longer comprehend.

Now, he could only rely on his knowledge to forcefully receive the everything from the external world unilaterally. The void crystal is continuously absorbing the external world, taking in everything he comes in contact with and subsequently confining it.

Seemingly due to prolonged confinement of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen, the crystal started assimilating some of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s devourer essence.

The current him could only observe and listen, but his own voice could not be transmitted out. Even the most basic of actions like blinking or smiling could no longer be done by his body. The confinement had already been raised to a level that no one could even comprehend.

Chapter 1149: Resolution 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A cold wind was whirling. On the entire island of the White Royal Palace, save for the forever unchanging meteorite flow surrounding it, it was just a wide and empty wasteland.

The Void Crystal with a dark golden hue had already become a part of the island’s scenery.

“I seemed to have miscalculated the outcome of this battle,” The White King’s voice sounded from outside the crystal.

Garen looked at the figure that suddenly appeared outside blurrily through the crystal. Without a care for his image, the White King sat down on the floor cross-legged.

He had already stopped talking since dozens of years ago, even the time for outside activities was starting to get limited. It seemed like the confinement essence had already started to affect his Dream Weaving ability. Most of the time, he was stuck in the crystal, silently trying to get a deeper grasp of the confinement essence. However, his progression was getting increasingly slower, and bearing fewer and fewer results. Most of the time, the results were so minuscule that he started feeling that he was not improving at all.

In this time, whenever the White King felt bored, he would come over to chat with him. At first, he could still barely force out a few sentences, but now, as the Confinement Power was getting stronger and stronger, he was no longer able to say a word.

However, even if he could not reply, the White King would still come to chat. It seemed as though he was rambling to himself, but all he wanted was an audience to vent to, so he did not mind if there were not any replies.

“The Red King has finally awakened,” The White King calmly said. “I heard that he entered Level Eight. That’s fast. Although he’s an outlier from the general trend, this kind of speed is still considered astonishingly fast…”

“There’s also your younger sister, she’s already Level Nine. She’s now even able to escape from the clutches of a Holy Lord unscathed. It’s truly amazing… Just using that bit of information and conditions, they managed to grow to such an extent within just a couple hundred of years,” The White King’s voice seemed to reveal a hint of emptiness.

“Wasn’t this part of the original script you intended?” Garen wanted to reply with that. Unfortunately, his voice was completely sealed by the crystal.

“I know, you’re trying to ask me that ‘wasn’t this the script that I planned myself?’” The White King gazed at the orbiting meteorites from afar indifferently. “It is… Didn’t I start off by pursuing unification and peace? The Red King can bring this generation an even longer-lasting peace, end all wars, and allow the two races to cohabitate in harmony…”

He paused briefly, taking out some sort of snack from his hands. Putting one of them into his mouth, he started to lightly chew on it.

“To be able to promise this type of complete equality, it’s not something I can offer.”

“So you waited for the Red King to grow up, waiting to pass on the baton to him once he was ready?” Even though Garen knew his voice could not be heard, he still asked.

Surely enough, the White King could not hear anything. He had stopped talking. As he started eating the snacks slowly piece by piece, his gaze felt empty.

In reality, the two knew deep inside, every time Garen weaved out, the Confinement Power would get jolted with some stimuli and strengthen its confinement against Dream Weaving. This inadvertently caused the difficulty of weaving out each time to become progressively harder.

Perhaps, after weaving out a few more times, he would no longer even be able to return anymore…

“Is this considered a ‘you reap what you sow’ moment?” Garen was helpless. The strongest confinement had far exceeded his expectations. Not only did it manage to successfully block out the White King, soon it could be possible that he himself would be blocked in. He might even be sealed in here forever.

He believed that the White King had already predicted this as well, that was why the White King decided to use Garen as an audience for his venting. He started coming over to vent with no restraint or any intention of hiding anything.

“Maybe, I can go out two more times,” Garen carefully calculated and arrived at this conclusion. Two more times, with less than a month of a grace period in between. Otherwise, since the Confinement Power continually increases, he might not be able to return anymore. Then, his consciousness and physical body would be separated, making him no different from a Fallen… Oh, it might be slightly different. Once a person had fallen, their consciousness could only remain at a place or in a location, they could not freely move. He might still be able to move by his will…

Once a Regent Level had fallen, this was the result. Even after their death, they still existed as a highly concentrated bundle of consciousness, allowing them to exist for a very long time. It was similar to the types at Ancient Endor, having their soul seeds remain even after their deaths.

That was the case for Goddess Dowager and Red Moon. Just that one was sealed in a palace, while the other was sealed in his own mech’s core parts.

“For the final time I’m weaving out, I have to find a concrete method of escaping this…” Garen did not want to be forever sealed in this void crystal. Living like this without any notion of time or space would eventually drive him insane.

He had a hunch that the opportunity to leave this world was soon arriving…

“It looks like you reap what you sow,” The White King looked at Garen who was in the well and said. “To block me, you ended up sealing yourself inside the crystal with no way of coming out.”

He brought out a jug of alcohol and started to drink without a care in the world, directly drinking it straight out of the jug.

“Laughable… Who would have known, the human’s Tenth Regent Level, the Crystal King, the King of Liars, is now a crystal statue that had almost fallen?”

Garen could see that he was somewhat irritated. Perhaps, he had started feeling conflicted with the pathway he had planned out in the very beginning. Maybe it was a conflict between his ideals and the reality. From what it looked like, the White King seemed to not want to die.

He started having conflicting feelings towards his plan which he had set out to achieve back then.

“Forget it, you’re already at your death’s door, what am I doing here still talking to you?” The White King stood up and tossed away his alcohol jug as he turned and slowly walked off.

Looking at his silhouette slowly disappearing from his sight, Garen had a complicated, indescribable feeling in his heart.

“For the final time I’m weaving out, I’ll need to start considering my future plans…” He made a decision in his heart.

Celine, and Chinande, these were the two matters that he still had to resolve to get the peace of mind.

Did Celine actually lie to him, or did someone kill her and disguised themselves with her appearance? Or maybe there was not a person called Celine from the very start? What if she was a pawn from one of the White King’s subordinates from the very beginning, hiding amongst the masses solely to learn about the Red Moon Star Emperor’s movements?

Even up till now, Garen still had not found a clear answer to this. The last time Garen went out, he did discover some clues. This time, he had to clear up everything.

“It’s time to resolve everything…” Garen started to concentrate his consciousness within the crystal.

******

Five days later…

Some Star Region of Mankind – Central Black Bottom Star.

In a small town located on the high grounds next to a snowy mountain, a tall man covered in a black cloak was walking on a somewhat narrow street. He was wearing a black mask, only revealing two deep blue eyes. His entire body was completely covered by the cloak.

There were a couple of kids running around the town, occasionally stopping to look at this weird and unknown visitor.

This town was situated somewhere rural, it was also the most barren place in the whole of Black Bottom Star. Usually, there would barely even be one visitor every half a month. Thus, every time an outsider comes to visit, these children would be the first to run out to witness their arrival.

At the houses on his two sides, an auntie carrying a steel basin out to water the plants looked over at the man just as she was heading back to her house.

“Auntie, may I ask you a question?” The man’s voice rang out from within the cloak. “Is there a female mech pilot named Celine living around these parts? She has short green hair, was quite stalky and looked decently pretty. I think she moved here about more than thirty years ago.”

The auntie stopped in her tracks.

“Celine? Thirty plus years ago… You mean Big Sis Celine?”

“Big Sis?”

The cloaked man was slightly shocked.

“Yeah, she’s even older than me. What else would I call her other than ‘Big Sis’?” The auntie answered matter-of-factly. “But, what are you looking for her for?”

“I’m her friend, I haven’t seen her in ages so I decided to visit. Since it was en route, I decided to come over to explore the area a bit,” The man answered. However, judging from his voice, this man’s age was still quite young.

The auntie instantly started to feel suspicious. However, as she thought about it more, a lot of mech pilots also had anti-aging capabilities, so she gave out Celine’s house address after a brief hesitation.

“To get to her house, you’ll just need to follow this road. It’s the third green building up ahead. However…”

“However what?”

The auntie looked around the street and softly whispered.

“However, Big Sis Celine had passed away almost ten years ago… You…”

What she said after that, the man had obviously stopped listening. He was completely in a state of shock. Lightly removing his mask, it revealed a fierce but cold face.

“Died?”

The man’s brow slowly lit up in a white V-shape, displaying his current emotional fluctuations. The white light will brighten or dim accordingly to his feelings.

Whoosh!

Just as the auntie and the children screamed due to the sudden breeze, the man had instantly disappeared into thin air, leaving no traces behind, as if he was never here to begin with.

He leaped a few hundred meters in an instance.

When Garen once again appeared, he was already standing in front of a green building on the other side of town.

The building was slightly dilapidated. One side of the metal gate in front of the door was open. A young girl with green hair and a backpack was closing the gate with her back facing him.

The girl was in a black student’s short skirt, black thigh-high socks, and small leather boots. Her body was thin and shapely, almost a carbon copy of Celine back in the day.

Click! Right after the metal gate got locked, the girl turned around. Looking at the black-cloaked man who appeared silently behind her out of nowhere, she was obviously frightened. She leaped back slightly, her hands putting on a familiar pose.

Garen looked at the young girl in front of him that looked almost identical to Celine from back in the day and the Twelve Flying Dragon Fist stance that she was in. It caused him to reminisce about the days of him teaching her back in the Blackboard Region.

“Who are you?” The girls asked, alerted. “Why did you come to my house?”

Garen started laughing. His face which originally looked fierce, suddenly turned even more frightening as he started laughing while his facial expressions remained emotionless. He was originally already a character that could easily make a young child cry just from his looks. Now, his potential and aura seemed to have increased, giving off an even more terrifying feeling. This sight caused the girl to suddenly tense up.

“Me? I’m here to find Celine. Who are you to her?”

The girl once again stepped back, maintaining the best distance for her to strike.

“I’m her daughter. My mother had already passed away ten years ago.”

Garen did not know what to say. Regarding the problem with Celine, up till now, he still had to legitimate answer. However, it was certain now that she was not a familiar or clone of Chinande, but instead an actual living human. But daughter?

“Who is your father?” Garen stopped laughing.

“Father?” The girl frowned. “Why should I tell you? Who even are you?!”

The atmosphere seemed stiff.

Garen suddenly raised his right hand, his palm was covered in a thin colorless film. He lightly grabbed onto the young girl in front of him.

Chapter 1150: Resolution 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Go to sleep… Go to sleep…”

His voice was almost like a magical chant. It seemed to have an irresistible hypnotizing effect. In an instant, the girl’s eyes closed, as she passed out onto the ground.

At this moment, the surroundings had already been silently covered with a spherical film. The townsfolk outside did not seem to notice a thing as they continued on with their daily lives.

Garen placed his hand on top of the girl’s head without any hesitation.

She was an average person, there was not a trace of willpower on her body at all. There was no way she could fend against his Regent Level willpower memory search. However, it was exactly due to the fact that the difference in power between them was so huge, this kind of search was completely unresisted, and it would not do any harm to the girl as well.

After a brief moment, images of the girl’s memories start flowing out from her brain.

Scenes from her memory start continuously playing one-by-one in Garen’s mind. All of her memories, all the way back to when she first opened her eyes as a newborn were recorded down.

Celine raised her with what seemed like a gentle guy. However, not long after she was born, the guy had died. A bit later, when she was six years old, Celine went out for an errand and never returned.

After a few days, someone found Celine’s unrecognizable corpse in a ravine in the wilderness.

What followed was suffering, despair, and depression. When the girl participated in the funeral, she was alone, without any relatives, living on with only the occasional help offered by some of the kind people in the town. Luckily, Celine had left a fortune enough for her lifetime. Every day, she would go to school in town for her classes, then return home to revise her homework and read. She desperately wanted to leave this place and find out about the truth behind Celine’s death. At the same time, she never forgot to continue on her Celine’s ideals – to keep getting stronger! Until no one can stop her!

This was all of the contents of her memories. For a sixteen-year-old’s memories, it would only take Garen a short couple of minutes to finish viewing the entire thing.

“Was she murdered?” Garen frowned. Using his Energy Machine Imprint, he rapidly input a command to send an order. His message was sent instantly over an immeasurable distance, reaching the Scarlet Snow Alliance headquarters.

A huge Alliance Databank suddenly popped up. It was a collaborative effort between the huge forces network and other information networks.

After having the rough direction and narrowing down the search with more precise details, similar information could then be easily searched up.

Almost instantaneously, everything regarding Celine’s murder case appeared inside Garen’s imprint.

For some unknown reason, Celine had left the Energy Machinist forces’ radar, leaving the populated and bustling regions. Posing as an average mech pilot, she continued to live in seclusion. She later found herself an average man to marry. All these made it almost as though she was hiding something. She was later violently assaulted by an outsider pilot, seemingly due to an internal dispute caused by an uneven loot distribution when they banded together to explore an ancient ruin.

Due to her qualifications, countless coincidences, and other factors, before her death, Celine was still only a mech pilot who barely attained the Inherited Level. Her side as an Energy Machinist seemed to have less desirable results as compared to her mech pilot achievements; it seemed like she had given up on it.

Despite the strength that she accumulated over her entire lifetime, at the very end, she died without a trace in this small town.

To be honest, Garen had also understood, Celine was nothing more than a so-called genius only within the Blackboard Region. In the wider scope of things, she was not anything extraordinary. To be able to reach the Inherited Level was already a feat worth commending, that was the extent of growth a lot of these so-called geniuses and elites could achieve. To continue on, what they needed were not more qualifications, but rather, the appropriate temperaments, coincidences, and countless other factors.

“Find the murderer’s location,” Garen directly ordered.

“Understood,” The Scarlet Snow Alliance’s Quantum Communications replied.

Garen regained his focus as he looked at the young girl in front of him. Reaching his hand out, he lightly pinched her cheeks. It was soft and smooth, but also slightly cold.

“Who would’ve thought that she died…”

Originally, he planned to find out the truth. However, it seemed like he had no choice but to bury the hatchet. What happened to Celine back then was a question forever left unsolved, where only the late Celine had the answer.

In the end, did she betray Garen, was she forced to do it, was it another person disguised as her, or was it something else? Everything remained a mystery…

A reply from the Scarlet Snow Alliance was received a moment later.

Whoosh!

Garen’s silhouette instantaneously disappeared from the girl’s location.

As he reappeared, he was facing a strangely busy pub. It was dark and noisy, with multiple boys and girls twisting their bodies to the music. Their clothing was either very sexy or very enchanting.

Garen looked past the crowd and saw a group of carefree-looking boys and girls. These people had their legs crossed across the table. Some were smoking, while others were drinking. They seemed to be playing some sort of game.

There was also another person on the other side playing with his phone. With the bright screen shining on his face, he looked as pale as a ghost.

Garen carefully identified these group of people. He also looked down at his current clothing and appearance. He was in an extremely sexy outfit, with perky breasts jiggling all about. He was even wearing a white miniskirt with a black pantyhose, his long blonde hair going over his shoulder.

At that point, Garen did not know whether to laugh or to cry. Even for reconnaissance investigators from the Scarlet Snow Alliance, to dress up to this extent is going a bit overboard…

He directly used Dream Weaving, landing in this Scarlet Snow Alliance member’s body that was currently high from an acid trip. (TL Note: The original words were ‘嗑药’ which meant “taking drugs” or “popping pills”, and ‘迷迷糊糊’ which meant “blurry”. They were changed to “tripping acid” and “getting high” as it is more localized and suitable for the context.) However, he did not expect the target to be a girl, much less someone in such an erotic outfit.

Casually using the energy field condensation to form a makeshift black cloak, Garen walked towards the table with the people he identified earlier.

A black shadow from underneath Garen’s feet silently shot towards the group.

Shooop!

The shadow suddenly split into a few strands, fading under the target group’s feet.

After a moment, they all started to wobble about before collapsing onto the table.

Bam!

Suddenly, their skulls all simultaneously burst open like an exploding watermelon.

Aaaah! Aaaah!

Almost immediately, the entire pub burst into screams. The people nearby were startled by what had just happened, causing them to run away in panic. The people who were a distance away were completely oblivious of what had just happened, as they continue to twist the bodies to the music, enjoying themselves to the fullest.

With the sudden frenzied movement of the people, the pub turned into a chaotic mess.

Garen turned around and left the scene, taking off his black cloak in the process.

Whoosh!!

In a flash, his sight returned to outside the pub. He was now in the body of a small boy, quietly taking a nap in his mother’s embrace.

Garen slowly opened his eyes, silently watching the chaos unfold within the pub.

This was his Dream Weaving Possession. As long as it was within his range, anyone asleep or without a clear consciousness could not escape from having their fates controlled by Garen.

As his distance with the pub grew larger, while still possessing the small boy, he once again closed his eyes.

Whoosh…

Countless rainbow-colored strips zoomed past his two sides. It looked like a liquid rainbow, continuously flowing past him, emitting all sorts of colors.

This was a rainbow-like circular tunnel. It was extremely long, almost feeling as if it was endless.

Garen’s body was weaving through the tunnel, flipping about. This tunnel seemed to be indestructible. He had attempted many times in the past, using various different methods, but he still did not manage to break this dream world tunnel.

He could only use it as a medium, entering different individuals’ dreams.

A light suddenly flashed in front of his eyes.

As he opened his eyes, he was in a dense cemetery in the wilderness. No one was taking care of the place, some of the crosses on the tombstones was already started to tilt or break due to nature’s wear and tear.

Garen’s current body was stood in front of a black tombstone, the words engraved on it had already started to fade away.

However, he could still vaguely make out the word “Celine” written on it.

This body that Garen possessed belonged to a Scarlet Snow Alliance member. When Garen left, the body owner would automatically move accordingly the orders given by the Scarlet Snow Alliance.

Squatting down, Garen gently placed the bouquet of white flowers in front of the tombstone.

Time was almost up for his current trip out… He needed to quickly resolve the trouble. Garen originally planned on staying a bit longer over here. However, he could only regretfully look at Celine’s tomb as he let out a sigh.

“Looks like, the truth behind everything will have to be left for Lonnie to eventually unravel…”

Whoosh!

With a flash in his eyes, he once again entered into the dream world.

******

At a huge white waterfall, large amounts of lake water flowed down the waterfall, forming what looked like a stretching of shining white silk. The downflow of water caused a huge white splash, creating an amazingly majestic sight.

The Great Diamond Waterfall, it was one of the Finite Central Star Region’s most famous tourist attraction.

From a bird-eyes’ view, the entire waterfall formed a semi-circular arc shape. The waterfall had two sides; on the left was a green lake that was as flat as a mirror, while on the right was this majestic white waterfall.

The white clouds in the sky drifted with the wind. At the center of this bright blue sky, a golden star gently showered the place in warm sunlight, warming up the coolness from the splashes of water.

Gush…

Amidst the continuous gushing of the waterfall, at the center of the waterfall, a white-shirted man sat on top of a black rock silently fishing.

Both his hands held onto his long white fishing pole, allowing his fishing line to be pulled tight by the rushing current. His face showed no emotion.

Sitting alone at the center of this thousand-meter-long waterfall, this place was charged with various twisted magnetic fields and radiation, not even an average Inherited Level Mech Pilot would dare to fly pass the airspace above. However, the white-shirted man seemed to show no concern at all as he continued to silently sit atop this black rock as if he was waiting to get a bite. However, at the same time, it seemed that he was also awaiting something else.

It was at this moment, on the other side of the waterfall, a silhouette in a black cloak slowly stepped into the waterfall. Carefully treading the boundaries in between the white waterfall and the green lake, the black cloak seemed to be completely unaffected by the water currents. He was just carefreely walking through the water, casually allowing the water to flow past his shins. He slowly made his way towards the white-shirted man.

Not far away, the large water splashes had caused a lot of water vapor to be propelled into the air, forming a rainbow under the sunrays.

The black cloak continuously made his way toward the white-shirted man, completely unaffected by the radiation or the magnetic field, and he finally stopped when he had reached the white-shirted man.

“After searching for you for so many years, I never would have expected that you would be in a place like this,” Removing the cloak, Garen’s face was revealed. “It’s time for payback.”

Behind Garen, a brown, Middle Aged-style sailboat slowly floated up, drifting in the air towards afar. That was the tourist sightseeing boat over here. On the boat, one could vaguely see a group of people looking over at their direction, screaming in confusion. No one had thought there would still be anyone who dared to enter this place.

The white-shirted man slowly stood up from the black rock.

Turning over, the man had a completely cold and emotionless face. His eyes were almost like a pair of white stones, completely matt, devoid of any sense of life.

“Your action holds no meaning,” His voice was dry and coarse, as though he had not said anything for a long time.

“Light of Justice, former Light of Freedom, the so-called strongest Star Emperor Perpetual Motioner, Chinande,” Garen stared straight into his eyes. “Tell me your true identity.”

Chapter 1151: Premonition and Pursuit 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Amidst the splashing of the water, Garen’s voice reached the other person’s ears clearly.

“True… identity…” Chinande repeated once.

He was quiet for a long time, and then he crouched down again, actually deciding to ignore Garen.

“If you want to see it, come see for yourself.” Finally, he pointed at his own forehead, closing his eyes slowly. He continued to hold the fishing rod, and just like that, he sat down once more. As quiet as a statue.

Garen frowned.

This was not how Chinande’s original records were like. In the past, he was never like this, but it seemed that after that war with the Finite people, he had changed into the strange person he was now.

Garen had always wondered how Chinande ended up becoming the White King’s Royal Star. That had all been a myth.

Until now, he only had one motive for coming here, and that was revenge.

Revenge for the Second Elder of the Scarlet Snow Sect back then, and for the time Chinande tried to control him. And now they were at this level, he was a Regent Level facing off against Chinande, a Perpetual Motioner. Therefore, no matter what, there would be no accidents for a short while. Be it the White King, or the actions of the nearest Regent-Level fighters, Garen was completely aware of them all.

“See for myself?” Garen repeated.

Without any hesitation, he strode forth, and lightly pressed his hand against Chinande’s forehead. The memory data connected immediately, and countless memories surged at him madly from the depths of Chinande’s mind.

Bam!!

In an instant, a world of light, white light, exploded from the point of contact.

Garen was immediately drowned in the sea of light.

The ocean’s worth of memories kept flashing past at incredible speeds, and finally stopped on a scene in space.

It was inside a floating metallic palace, and the White King’s hand was pulling away from Chinande’s forehead.

There was a corpse in white robes lying beside them.

Garen looked at it closely, and discovered, to his shock, that it was another Chinande.

“Starting from today, you are the new Light of Justice.” The White King’s voice reached his ears. The child-like White King still looked like a young boy, his smile gentle and clean.

Garen looked at Chinande’s body within his memories.

It was just a mass of bloody red flesh, that did not even resemble a human!

Boom!!

Amidst the loud explosions, the memories began to recede rapidly, and everything around him became a mess of colors again.

Garen pulled his hand away slowly, looking at Chinande in front of him. It had never occurred to him that this so-called Royal Star would be an artificial creature that the White King created with his own hands.

“In that case, the White King knew that I would come looking for you?” asked Garen in a low voice.

“How many more times can you come out?” Chinande asked quietly.

Garen paused.

True, the person who knew his condition best, except for himself, was none other than the White King.

He instantly understood the White King’s intention.

Chinande was no more than one of his creations, it did not matter much to give him to Garen. This way, he could prevent Garen from finally going berserk as a result of never being able to find Chinande.

This was no more than a deal.

Garen’s eyes turned, and he stared straight at Chinande in front of him.

“Are you fine with this?” he asked, a question that seemed meaningless at first glance.

Whether he was fine with it or not, Chinande could not disobey the White King’s orders.

Chinande widened his eyes.

“I am merely an artificial creation, His Majesty’s lapdog.” His eyes were dry and completely devoid of light.

Artificial creation?

Garen suddenly found that slightly funny, the enemy that destroyed so many Energy Machinist Sects and troubled him for so long, turned out to be no more than one of the White King’s artificial creations. And what was worse, it seemed to have given up on living a long time ago.

Then what about his many years of intense training to strengthen himself, what about his long search for Chinande’s whereabouts? What was the point of all that? It was completely meaningless!

Inexplicable rage surged up within him, and Garen pressed his palm down hard.

Bam!!

Blood splattered everywhere.

Chinande’s head exploded immediately, and there was nothing left above his neck. The flood of blood and brain matter was instantly condensed together, mixed with his bone and flesh, suspended above Garen’s palm.

Chinande’s corpse slowly slanted to a side, but his breathing continued. His powerful life force showed that this body was in fact the body of a Holy Lord, Chinande’s actual body.

Just like that, everything was over.

Garen had a feeling as though none of this was real. Holding in his hand a bead of flesh and blood that had been condensed into the size of a fingernail, he did not even give Chinande’s corpse a second glance. Turning around, he leaped lightly, and his whole body shot into the air, the ice-crystal wings, as pure white as jade, unfolding behind him. They layered onto each other, growing larger and larger, wider and wider.

Within a few seconds, they had almost covered the entire sky above the waterfall.

Countless scarlet snowflakes scattered down. Within a few short seconds, the whole planet had instantly changed from summer to winter.

The enormous waterfall gradually slowed down, gradually freezing over, until eventually it became completely motionless. It had turned into a beautiful ice sculpture.

Chinande’s body was in there as well, frozen into the ice. The barrage of red snowflakes covered it, and soon dyed the white waterfall a pale red as well.

With a rumble, before anyone on the entire planet could even react, the ice-crystal wings had vanished in an instant. Other than the cold red snow, there was no other trace of it.

In the waterfall, beside Chinande’s body.

The White King’s silhouette appeared slowly. He crouched down, putting his hand on the spot where Chinande’s body had been covered.

“I’m sorry…” he spoke softly, in a voice only he could hear.

******************

Garen unfurled his wings, flying in the Negative Space. He could occasionally see the cracks in the Void Battlefield around him, and starting a few years back, these cracks seemed to have increased in number.

He was like a large white bird, flapping wings the size of half a planet as he flew at rapid speeds, the frustration in his chest pent up with nowhere to go.

It was true, he had no reason to fight anymore.

Chinande had waited for him on his accord, and leaped to his death without any resistance. Garen had no more reasons to harm other, innocent parties.

The strongest Royal Star, Chinande, was just another Perpetual Motioner in the eyes of the White King, just one who was slightly stronger than usual. If his death could calm a Regent-Level extremist’s quest for revenge, how hard would it be to let Chinande kill himself?

Hiss…

From a black crack in space, a giant black snake poked its head out, its sun-red eyes staring at Garen.

This was one of those Void Boas that had been showing up more frequently recently. Void Boas like these were mostly made of space dust and other regular materials, but they survived by constantly eating high-energy objects, so each one had at least Non-Falling-Level power.

Recently, wild creatures such as these had been increasing in number.

The Void Boa was just about to approach Garen, but it seemed to smell an unprecedently dangerous scent. Quickly, it pulled its head back, and soon vanished without a trace.

With a few flashes, Garen stopped on a small planet at the edge of the Negative Space.

Like a pair of hands, the wings on his back tore apart the void in front of him, revealing a large crack big enough for him to pass through.

The huge wings quickly shrank, returning to Garen’s back. The white robes and golden helmet appeared on his body once more.

Garen flew into the crack lightly.

*********************

Scarlet Snow Alliance, Scorching Sun Galaxy

This day, an all-enveloping red snow fell all over the entire galaxy at the same time.

An enormous presence with clear white ice-crystal wings had descended upon them. Every regular person in the galaxy could see the transparent white wings flapping constantly in the air above the planet, that was an extension of the Alliance Leader, the Crystal King’s true body.

Because the Crystal King was there, the entire Scarlet Snow Alliance could remain safe and stable.

Suspended in the middle of the galaxy, on the edge of the star, Garen did his best to showcase his strongest, most dazzling power. He was not showing off just for the heck of it, but now, just before he left, he was also telling those small-fry hiding in the woodwork that he was still here. He, the Crystal King, Garen, still lived.

“This might be able to protect the Scarlet Snow Alliance for another few centuries. But that’s the extent of it… A few centuries later, Clint and the others would have grown up.” Garen looked down, at the four planets surrounding the star. He had done all that he needed to, Chinande was dead, his Will, flesh, and blood condensed into a bead that Garen now squeezed in his hand. The Scarlet Snow Alliance would become Clint’s strongest ally, until he grew up.

Now that he was protected by the humans, it was too late even if the White King wanted to go back on his decision. The general trend was set.

Slowly folding his wings back up, Garen shot down, and flew straight toward one of the main planets.

Everything around him was rapidly magnified, flitting past, and the surface of the blue planet quickly expanded into a lake.

The green lake was surrounded by a forest, and there was a tall white tower with a sharp tip beside the lake. Clint, Baylon, and the others stood on the top of the tower, along with the Two-Faced higher-ups.

All of them looked up, at the direction Garen was approaching from.

“Alliance Leader!””Sect Master!”

“Big Brother!”

Several different voices called out at the same time.

Garen slowly reduced his speed, and landed on top of the tower. He steadied his footing, and finally looked at Baylon as she was now. It had been many years since they last met, and there were even more white hairs on Baylon’s head now. She was looking at him with concern.

“Bro…” Baylon took one step forward. “I received your message, and we got here as soon as we could. Did something happen?”

In front of outsiders, she was the cruelest, most cold-hearted murderess, but faced with the people she cared for, she was only cold on the surface, in her expression. Even that was merely a result of the muscles on her face stiffening, such that she had forgotten how to soften her features.

“Exactly! I was eating dinner together with my daughter! You know what they say, the daughter is the father’s lover from the past life, as I thought…” Beside her, Clint was saying with a creepy expression of bliss.

“Ew!” Not far away, White Winter looked at Clint with an expression full of contempt. “You won’t even spare your own daughter! You monster!”

“Hey hey, I’m just close to my daughter, it’s not what you think!” Clint’s expression instantly blackened. “It’s been a while since I saw you, White Winter, are you itching for a fight because you haven’t been getting laid?!” He started rolling up his sleeves.

“What, just you!” White Winter flipped him the bird. His once-gentle personality had made a complete one-eighty. “Lonnie, give him a one-arm handicap!”

“Don’t pull me into your squabbles!” Baylon glared at them irritably, and the few of them instantly went silent. Clearly, her influence in this group was still increasing by the day.

Chapter 1152: Premonition and Pursuit 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beside them, the Two-Faced person and the Four-Armed woman were not as casual and nonchalant. Right now, they were reporting the latest changes in the situation to Garen.

After giving them simple instructions for what to do from now on, Garen told them directly that he might have to go into isolation for a long time, and might not be able to come out for a while, so he needed them to handle a lot of things on their own. Then, he taught them a few contingency plans for emergencies.

“Alright, you guys can retreat now, I want to have a few words with Lonnie and the others in private,” Garen said.

“Yes, Alliance Leader.”

The Four-Armed woman lowered her head in a show of respect and led the other higher-ups down the tower together with the Two-Faced person. Soon, they vanished into the Teleportation Point.

Only then did Garen look at Baylon and the others, who were still bickering.

“Alright, stop your fighting. I have a few things I need to tell you guys.”

He spoke, so naturally Clint and the others gradually quietened down. Although they still glared at each other, they had already settled down, waiting for Garen to speak.

Garen waved his hand, and instantly, a protective force field fell around them.

“This tower has already been covered with countless security and protection measures. If anyone wants to enter, even the legal processes would be picked up by internal servers, so even Perpetual Motioners would not be able to enter unnoticed. Big Bro, just say whatever you want to say,” said Clint nonchalantly. “There is no issue with defense at all!”

Garen was just being extra careful, so he nodded.

“Where’s Red Moon?”

“I’m awake.” Red Moon’s voice spoke, reaching their ears. “Looking for me for something?”

“You need to hear what I’m going to say as well,” Garen said solemnly.

Seeing how stern he was, the rest also stopped goofing around, their relaxed expressions slowly turning serious as they waited for him to continue.

Garen waved one hand, and a bright black Space Ring shot out, falling into Baylon’s hand.

“This is?” Baylon pinched the ring, slightly confused, but as soon as she reached her Willpower inside, her expression changed abruptly. “S-So many things!!?”

She was shocked, there was a veritable ocean of rare metals in there, as well as many other precious materials. She could even see some parked giant Battleships and Mechs, all of them the best of the best in terms of quality.

“I’m leaving this all to you guys,” replied Garen calmly.

“Leaving?” Baylon’s expression immediately changed. “Big Bro, are you going somewhere?!” She was unnaturally aware of such vocabulary, so she instantly noticed something was amiss.

Garen nodded.

“This might be my last time coming out.”

He told them all about his relationship with the White King, and also came clean with them about his own condition.

“A Confinement Essence that even the White King can’t do anything about?!” Red Moon was at a loss for words as well.

Upon hearing such shocking news, the rest had completely lost their good mood from before. Instead, their hearts felt heavier and heavier.

“Something like this… Is there really no other way?” A hint of sorrow rose in Baylon’s eyes. After losing her relatives one after the other, it had not been easy for her to regain a hint of her original personality. But now, she seemed to be relapsing into her most extreme state.

Garen shook his head.

“Sorry.”

The snow slowly penetrated through the force field, falling onto everyone’s heads.

The whole tower fell quiet.

“Next time, I might not be able to come out again at all… From now on, everything will be on your shoulders.” Before Garen finished speaking, Baylon had turned around and strode into the Teleportation Point, vanishing without a trace.

She had tossed away the ring, and it spun a few times in the air before Clint caught it, holding it in his hands.

Garen’s gaze also fell on Clint.

“I understand.” Clint did not look as carefree and half-hearted as he usually did, nodding solemnly. “I will take care of Lonnie.”

“Sorry…” Garen said again. “I have failed in my responsibilities as an older brother.” Although he did not particularly feel for Baylon, he still felt guilty for failing to uphold his promise to Nono.

“You have taken up enough responsibilities as it is,” said Clint seriously.

Garen took a deep breath. He no longer required oxygen to live, but it was still a habit of his.

His gaze swept past each of them.

Clint’s determination, White Winter’s steadfastness, the green-haired man’s seriousness. These were all companions who had gone through life and death together, they were all people who could entrust their lives to each other.

Trust could be very simple sometimes, but it could also be extremely difficult.

In truth, Garen envied them, he envied the way they could trust each other wholeheartedly. But no matter what, he could not do that himself.

“From now on, it will be your era…”

Garen reached out his hand, and all of Chinande’s blood, flesh, and Will stayed suspended above it.

“Clint Beza, let me help you one last time.”

Before he finished speaking, he abruptly shot out his palm, and it landed squarely in the center of Clint’s brow.

Boom!!!

A pillar of red light shot into the air, breaking past the clouds, the atmosphere, and shooting into space.

Using Chinande’s remains and Will as fuel, Garen used the concept of the Confinement Essence in his own body to form a model in Clint’s mind, as best as he could.

This was a model memory recording that could loop infinitely, so that everything about the Conceptual Essence would constantly replay in Clint’s head, until he completely understood some of the Essence encompassed within, or until he understood his own Conceptual Essence. Only then would he finally be able to completely turn off this recording.

As the red light shot into the sky, Garen’s body also began to fade and vanish.

Trying to pass down his Conceptual Essence as a recording went against all the laws of the world, so naturally he would have to pay a heavy price for that. This body of Garen’s was supposed to last for another few days, but now, he had instantly used up all of his power and Essence.

The others were all forced to take a few steps back by the blinding red light. They had to shield their eyes from the dazzling red light with their hands.

In the distance, under the tower, Baylon watched the red light over there. She seemed to have sensed something, and crouched down slowly, burying her head in her knees.

The Two-Faced Person and the other higher-ups were in a golden, rounded hall in the distance, and they all bowed at the pillar of light through the wall.

********************

The next time Garen opened his eyes, he saw the White King outside of the crystal, looking at him with a calm expression. Garen did not know when it started, but he had begun smoking, sucking slowly on a cigarette in his mouth.

“The crystal has gotten even harder,” said the White King softly. “This should be your last time coming out, huh?”

There was no voice replying from within the crystal, and the White King had long since gotten used to that.

He walked to the side, and picked up the jar of wine that had been placed there a long time ago, pouring himself a cup of wine. The aroma of wine permeated everywhere, and the pale green wine squirmed and squiggled like a live creature in the cup.

The White King shook the cup slightly, and then reached out his finger to tap the side of the cup.

Ding…

There was a light sound.

The wine in the cup actually changed colors, instantly turning from pale green to pure red. It was bright red, blood red.

“Did you hear that?”

Garen’s gaze fell on the cup. To his shock, he realized that it was not wine, but blood.

Swirling the cup lightly, the White King spoke with a calm but slightly melancholic tone.

“It really did turn red… Looks like you really can’t come out anymore…”

Only then did Garen understand, the White King had evidently discovered a way to test whether or not he could still reemerge. He was still able to come out one last time, but once he used up that last chance, he could never return. He was unlike the other Regent Levels, the Essence he understood was not the one that suited him best, it came from the Dark Shadow Dragon, and that was actually an Essence that did not suit him at all.

In other words, if it were not for the Dark Shadow Dragon’s Void Crystal, he would never have reached Regent Level, at the most, he would have stayed at Perpetual Motion. The Void Crystal made him, but in the end, it also destroyed him.

In truth, Garen had not completely comprehended the whole Essence concept, he had just used a trick, using the Essence of the Dark Shadow Dragon to confine himself, forcing his body to reach a material level where he existed purely as his Essence. He had completely merged with the Void Crystal into one entity.

But as the Confinement Essence evolved, he had also ended up a prisoner behind its bars.

“In a sense, I have achieved my goal,” said the White King softly. “Even if you sped up the Red King’s growth, everything will still return to the general trend in the end.”

“What’s the point of saying that now?” Suddenly, Garen wanted to laugh, for no reason at all. Ever since he came to this world, he had completed the Hellfrost Peacock Queen Body, reached Army Level, and may even be a match for the Ancient Endor Demon Lords now. He had also condensed his Soul Seed Ring, that was his biggest gain in this world.

The Soul Seed Ring could forcefully raise his main technique up a level, unconditionally, a derivation of strength in principle.

“Do you have any other wishes?” The White King took a sip of his blood wine. “Perhaps I could help you fulfill it.”

“This guy… is going crazy.” Garen looked at the White King through the crystal with some pity in his eyes, but his image could not go through the crystal. The Void Crystal absorbed everything, and converted it all into confining power. Even light could not travel through it.

The White King’s sanity seemed to have already started distorting. There was no one to share his secrets, no one to stay by his side, no one to comfort him. He was alone in everything, horribly alone.

Outsiders would only obey him, fear and respect him. Then they would distance themselves from him. So he could only look for a crystal like Garen’s, that could not talk or reply, and treat it as his own sounding board.

The White King was still there, chattering away. He no longer cared if Garen would reply, he was just looking for an outlet.

Garen could not be bothered with him, and just looked at his own attribute pane.

The attribute pane in front of him was like the most technologically-advanced quantum computer screen, it could scroll through countless skills from the top to the bottom. There were several hundred different techniques of different sizes scattered within, and an ordinary person may take days to find a skill they were looking for.

Garen quickly found the information about his Soul Seed that he was looking for.

‘Soul Seed — Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique (Blue), Holy Phoenix Demonic Book (Black-Gold). Hellfrost Peacock Queen Soul Seed (White)’

He needed to consider his way out, or if this continued on, he could very well end up trapped in this crystal forever. He would be the first Ancient Endor Demon Lord to trap himself to death…

Chapter 1153: Drifting 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The main trait of the Demon Lords was that they had many Soul Seed Rings. Soul Seed Rings structured this way, known as Soul Rings for short, could allow Demon Lords to reach their strongest state quickly and inconspicuously within a short period of time whenever they invaded a world.

But now Garen only had one Soul Ring, and according to his estimates, it was highly likely that powerful Demon Lords would have multiple Soul Rings. That way, once they entered a new universe with new rules, they would be able to integrate into the new power system there quickly, using the power of the Soul Rings to level up rapidly and eventually controlling the strongest power there.

That was the true terror of the Demon Lords. They were the real pillar in the fight against the Void Creatures.

“I don’t have a Will, so I can only rely on my soul’s special transmigration quality and the condensation power of my Soul Seed to sustain my existence. If I want to continue living for a long time, I’ll need to find a new body as soon as possible, and…”

With a loud crash, Garen felt as though the whole palace gave a huge tremor.

A tremor?!!

He was instantly shocked. Putting aside the question about whether or not anyone in the White Royal Palace had the power to shake the whole palace, there was also the Dark Shadow Dragon’s Void Crystal that he was trapped in to consider. It had the Conceptual Essence to swallow and confine all forms of power, so a low-level power like a tremor should not be able to reach him inside.

He looked at the White King outside the crystal, but the latter seemed completely oblivious.

Roar!!!

There was a monster’s howl, faraway and deep, reaching Garen’s ears from a distance. And the White King still showed no signs of hearing it, which clearly meant he did not hear these sounds at all.

“This is…” Garen’s eyes grew dead serious, “… the tremors from the Soul Seed!!!”

According to his Energy Machine Imprint’s quick calculations and derivations, as well as the innate understanding of the Void Creatures’ language that he had acquired by becoming a Hellfrost Peacock Queen, he soon understood what that roar meant.

That roar represented danger! Greed!

Garen quickly looked at one of the icons on his Status Pane.

On the pane that said ‘Potential Quality — Void Pursuer’, there was a bright and blinking red light, and some Ancient Endor symbols appeared behind it.

The translated meaning of the symbols was:

‘Warning! A giant threat in the form of a Void Creature is approaching, Level: Army. Race: Void Thane. Twelve in number. Please evade them immediately, the best method would be to enter the Mother Stream in order to escape.

‘Please beware, your position as a Soul-Ring-Level Void Pursuer will greatly increase your chances of being pursued by Demon-Lord-Level beings from the Void, please be constantly vigilant.’

Garen immediately remembered the enormous Ancient Endor Creatures with countless Soul Seeds that he had encountered when he first came to this world. They swam at the edge of the Mother Stream, like fishermen out fishing, always prepared to hunt and kill any inheritors of the Ancient Endor civilization who happened to float past.

“I lured that Army-Level Ancient Creature here?” Garen’s heart began to pound. He knew very well that only the weakest of the Void Creatures waiting beside the Mother Stream were Army Level, the normal ones were all Demon Lord Level without exception. And because they had several dozen Soul Seeds, even if these were not condensed into Soul Rings, they would still be able to squash him effortlessly.

Even as a Void Pursuer, the one he had lured here was the weakest.

“Looks like I really can’t stay in one place for too long…” Garen knew that he had no other choice.

Giving the White King outside one last look, Garen sighed inwardly.

He had come to this world, but he never thought that he would eventually leave like this. He had not found any more information about Ancient Endor, but instead he had collected enough technological knowledge, all sorts of the highest-end technological skills, and the Hellfrost Peacock Queen Soul Seed that he had formed at the very end.

“It’s time to leave…”

Garen had no more regrets, his body immediately leaving his body. Like shapeless mist, it flew out of the top of the crystal, and flew silently back down the direction he had once arrived from.

This was not weaving through dreams like before, this time he was truly dying. Garen’s soul left Nonosiva’s body of its own accord, and floated toward the direction of the Mother Planet, where he had come from.

Soon, a Void Black Hole appeared abruptly, sucking Garen’s soul inside, and jumping toward the direction of the Mother Planet.

The White King did not stop him, as the Crystal King, Garen had the ability to weave through dreams, so even if the White King stopped him, he could instantly weave into the body of a Scarlet Snow Alliance member before breaking away. It would be meaningless to try.

He just raised his head to look at the Jumping Black Hole, motionlessly, and Garen could not tell what he was thinking.

The Crystal King, the King of Lies, from the beginning to the end, he only lived for a mere few centuries, as dazzling and short-lived as a firework.

Standing in front of the crystal, the White King stayed silent for the longest time, until he sensed that the Spatial Black Hole that Garen had jumped into was completely gone. Only then did he slowly turn around and leave.

And the Void Crystal grew stronger and stronger, constantly increasing its Confinement and Devouring Essence. This Void Crystal would one day become an unprecedentedly terrifying black hole.

A black hole was more than just a natural phenomenon, any natural phenomena that had a powerful gravitational force, such that it could even devour light, could be called a black hole. Because there was no reflection of light, it looked completely black. But no one knew what was inside, it might be caused by the collapse of a star, or the self-detonation of a Perpetual Motioner, or it could be many other things.

Humans just called anything that looked black and had terrifying gravitational attraction power ‘black holes’.

But be it the White King or Garen, neither of them had any interest in these things. The general trend was set, and they had each accomplished their own goals and missions. Everything else was of no more importance.

*******************

Edge of the Mother Planet

The star infinitely emanated golden light, and in a patch of black space by the border, as a few meteors were pulled by the gravitational force toward the sun and swept past this area, a hint of distortion appeared in this part of space.

Hiss!

Suddenly, a black crack opened up in this area of the Void, and wisps of an eerie shapeless aura flew out from inside. It was a form of soul, unseen to the physical eye.

Garen flew out of the crack, carefully calculating the spatial point of the Mother Stream that he had broken out of when he arrived here earlier.

The Mother Stream flowed through the entirety of space, connecting countless universes, parallel ones and perpendicular ones, ones of every shape and size, they were all connected like countless branches to the entire Mother Stream. And what Garen needed to do now was find the tiny hole in space that he had created when he came here, so he could use this hole to rush back again, leaving this world.

The Energy Machine Imprint spun at high speeds. As the person at the pinnacle of the Energy Machinists, Garen’s Energy Machine Imprint had already reached an unprecedented level, and his computing power was equal to the Human Alliance’s strongest quantum calculator. Of course, once he activated it, it consumed a shocking amount of energy and Willpower, so only a peak-level existence would be able to withstand such a heavy cost.

Garen was beginning to understand some Essences, and he could even use his Confinement Essence to devour the dark energy directly. While the Void Crystal merged with his Devouring talent, he had also been integrated with some of the Void Crystal’s special ability to absorb dark energy with the Void attribute. He no longer needed to rely on the power of the Dark Shadow Dragon Whelp to first convert the dark energy into a material object before he could absorb it.

‘Target found.’ Soon, the Energy Machine Imprint came up with a result, the spatial point was in the Void nearby.

There was no research regarding the soul in this world, the closest thing to the soul was the Will, but that was only the external aspect of the soul, and the surface level of that as well. Perhaps many, many years later, the studies would finally involve the true, essential soul, and maybe they would be able to find this spatial point then, maybe they would discover the existence of the Mother Stream. But that would be a very long time from now.

The V-shape on Garen’s brow blinked with a faint white light, his gaze locking onto that hole in the distant Void.

He did not act, because he did not know how to activate this hole. If he applied his power wrongly, it was very likely that he could destroy the hole, and then he would be in real trouble.

So the best way would be to open it from the inside, facing outward.

That was why Garen was waiting.

Waiting for the instant where the hole was opened from the inside. He could sense that the Void Creatures in his Soul Ring probably also existed on the soul plane, so normal people could not see or touch them. Only other souls would be able to sense them.

Garen had already sensed that there was a Void Creature with an Army-Level soul here, and there would certainly be a similar one on the bank of the Mother Stream. So what he had to do now was release his scent, waiting for these Void Creatures in soul form to appear and open the hole for him.

Time ticked by.

Garen stayed completely motionless, in the middle of the same action and the same stance.

One day passed, two days passed… A month passed…

In space, nothing much would have changed at all within a month. The only thing was that some of the nearest planets changed their position somewhat, but everything else was just as before, with nothing at all out of place.

Roar!!!

All of a sudden, the roar of a beast reached him faintly from a distance.

Garen finally perked up, concentrating.

With a tear and a yank, transparent ripples rose around that Void point, spreading in all directions. A giant black panther with ox horns slowly poked its head out of the ripples.

Roar!!!

He roared at Garen, and the purely soul-form soundwaves traveled past the long distances in an instant, reaching Garen’s ears.

“It’s finally here…” Garen advanced instead of retreating, his soul turning into a white thread that shot at the black ox-horned panther.

An enormous image of a peacock appeared behind him, whoomph!

The peacock’s sharp beak pecked forward, as fast as lightning. The beak, that was only several thousand meters long at first, instantly grew until it was several tens of thousands of meters long. It bit down hard, grabbing the blank panther and tossing it out.

Rawwr…

The panther wailed, but it was only Army Level, so it could not resist Garen’s power. As a Demon Lord Level, Garen was no longer someone an Army Level could hope to face. He applied force with his Soul Seed Ring directly, emanating pure Soul Energy.

The Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s top half pulled back, and it actually pulled the panther out of the ripples as though it was pulling out a carrot. Then, it threw its head back and swallowed it.

The bottom half of the Peacock Queen was connected to Garen’s tiny body, so the image looked completely off-kilter, as though it was Aladdin’s genie lamp, but infinitely magnified. The panther that had been devoured also disappeared without a trace, as though it had gone into an abyss.

In the Void, after the panther was dragged out, the ripples instantly got even faster, smaller, more hurried, as though they were about to close in on themselves.

Garen jumped in, head-first and without hesitation.

The peacock behind his whole body faded and vanished, and his soul body vanished into the ripples as though it had dived into the water but created no splash at all.

Blurb-blurb…

Bubbles floated out from the corners of Garen’s mouth.

He was surrounded by a familiar green liquid, that was the water of the Mother Stream, filled to the brim with life force. This was the River of Life, the beginning and the end of all things.

Chapter 1154: Drifting 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Returning to the Mother Stream again after several hundred years, Garen felt that familiar corrosive power, that assimilative power. This power was unbelievably immense, and even as he was now, it was the most he could do to protect himself, as he flowed with the current.

He turned back to look at the hole leading to the Mech Universe, the gap had shrunk until it was only as large as a fist now, and it was still shrinking.

Around him was a limitless expanse of green. He could see nothing, and hear nothing,

Only the endless rush of the stream water continued to reverberate beside his soul’s ears.

Garen looked up and saw that the surface of the stream was nearby. Through the surface of the Mother Stream, he could see the colorful Spatial Barrier outside.

Roar…!

There was another fearsome roar.

To his shock, Garen saw many cracks instantly appear in the Spatial Barrier, and then an outside power seemed to punch a hole through it by force. A long, seemingly endless arm stretched out from it.

That was a golden-bronze arm, shining with a metallic glow as it extended toward him infinitely.

Bam!!

The water splashed and rose into high waves as the arm crashed into it. That arm actually reached straight for Garen. As though it could stretch forever, it descended over him with a terrifying power.

“It’s a Void Creature!!” Garen knew he was in trouble, and hurriedly activated his Soul Ring, unleashing his pure Soul Energy to surround his soul, and diving rapidly into the Mother Stream.

With a whoosh, he just managed to avoid being captured by the enormous hand. It just brushed past him at the side.

But even this tiny contact caused the Soul Energy on his arm to instantly disintegrate, turning into several dozen transparent maggots that stuck onto the outer wall of Garen’s Soul Energy, devouring it in large gulps.

A sense of dizziness overwhelmed Garen, and he instinctively knew that this was because he had used up too much Soul Energy. Something that could destroy the Barriers of the Mother Stream was not something he could afford to fight now.

“I need to leave right now!” He made the decision, and cut off the part of his soul that was being eaten, tossing it into the distance.

And then he swam down the Mother Stream like a fish.

Thankfully, his Soul Ring could now generate infinite Soul Energy, unlike before when he could only use the limited power stored inside his Soul Seed. If the Mother Stream finished devouring that power, he could only surrender to imminent death. Now, things were different, Garen was perfectly capable of producing new Soul Energy infinitely, so that he could last even longer and swim even further in this Mother Stream.

Boom!!

The stream water shook wildly, as the Mother Stream’s powerful life force surged madly into the arm that had intruded into it.

Garen turned around, and saw that the golden-bronze arm was being rapidly corroded by that countless green current, revealing the black material underneath as large dollops of bright red blood also dripped out, merging into the Mother Stream. A large part of the green river water around it turned dark red.

Roar…!!

That unidentified creature roared out in pain, and had no choice but to pull its arm back, the palm quickly leaving the Mother Stream while all covered in blood as it retreated back into the hole in the Spatial Barrier.

The hole was also rapidly regenerating, and soon it was just as new. The waves slowly calmed down.

Inside the water, Garen heaved a huge sigh of relief. He had not felt this sensation for several hundred years, of instantly falling from the pinnacle of a world to the very bottom, turning from the hunter to the hunted. Just a moment ago, he was one of the 26 people at the very peak of the Mech World, and now he was running for his life, humiliated and ashamed.

“It’s true, space is large enough to hold all sorts of wonders…” Garen sighed inwardly, and calculated his losses. The Energy Machine Imprint quickly showed its usefulness, because the Imprint was constructed around Willpower, and Willpower was a small branch of Soul Energy, he managed to retain it, and activate it using his soul. But right now, as he left the Mech World, the Energy Machine Imprint also began to operate slower.

After all, the computing laws behind its operation were mostly designed according to the laws of the Mech Universe. Once these laws changed, its auto-recovery powers should already be praised for keeping it running until now, when in fact it should have been immediately immobilized.

To put this into perspective, it was as though the speed of light was three hundred thousand meters per second in the laws of this universe, but they were nine hundred thousand meters per second in that universe. Or if one plus one equals two in this universe, but equals three in that one.

Of course, the latter was not that big a change, but it was enough to show you where the problem lay.

The reason Garen’s soul could be used throughout the many universes was because its roots lay in the most basic laws, tossing aside all the other non-uniform aspects. All that remained was the general law that could be used in any universe.

This was the true power of the Warlocks. What they controlled was the general law of power that could be used across many universes.

In the Mother Stream, time was meaningless, and everything was mobile. Garen followed the bend of the stream slowly, going against the current as he swam back up the direction he came. Back then, he had been swept to the poorest branch of the Mother Stream, the Mech Universe, so now that he wanted to leave, he needed to go against the current.

After transmigrating into so many worlds, he had gone from his initial curious excitement to his current state of numb acceptance.

As for his goal, Garen had long forgotten what his original goal had been back then. Why did he choose to dive into the Mother Stream? Why did he continue to transmigrate like this? He could no longer remember the meaning and motive behind all this.

The deluge of new memories had washed away almost every trace of his initial determination from way back when.

As Garen swam upstream, he considered it slowly.

Was it for the war between Ancient Endor and the Void Creatures? Or was it simply so he could experience new lives in different worlds? Or was it so he could find the original motive for transmigrating?

Perhaps he was even looking for a way back.

As he swam, Garen’s thoughts flew at high speeds. The turning of the Energy Machine Imprint gradually slowed, most of the functions lagging and stopping due to the lack of laws, until only a few of the most basic computing functions remained. The computing power was less than a ten-thousandth of what it used to be, but even then, it was stronger than the strongest super-calculator back on Earth.

Occasionally, Garen would encounter Void Creatures like the one that had tried to fish him out in the Mother Stream, but he managed to evade each of them safely.

But as Garen continued to ponder, he grew more and more lost, more and more confused. The more he searched, the harder it was for him to justify his continued existence, everything was just a repetitive cycle that would not end.

Other than to pursue even greater strength, he could not find any better reason for living.

“What is it that I want?” he asked himself.

By the time he asked this question, according to estimates, three years had already passed since he entered the Mother Stream.

He did not know where he had drifted to. There was never anything other than the endless green water around him, there were no living creatures, and only the occasional piece of flotsam floated past him. Even these items would not last much longer, dissolving rapidly in the stream water.

Throughout his entire journey, the only living things he could encounter were the occasional Void Anglers. Every one of these creatures was enormous, and each one had at least several dozen Soul Seeds. These were not the lowest grade Soul Seeds, either. Soul Seeds could be divided into the stages, namely Multicolor (TN: lit. messy colors), Colorless, and Unicolor (TN: lit. uniform color). Garen himself was at the lowest level, Multicolor, and his Soul Seed had formed only the most simple Soul Ring, so he was at the lowest end of the Demon Lord Level spectrum. If he wanted to advance further, he would need at least five Soul Seeds, forming a large Soul Ring. Then he needed to remove all the other colors, before he could advance to the Colorless Level.

And the Void Anglers that appeared outside the Mother Stream were all at least at the Colorless Level, they would not even show their faces if they did not have at least ten Soul Seeds. And the weaker ones, according to Garen’s guesses, probably had fewer Soul Seeds than that, so they were smart enough to stay hidden and not look for trouble. The Barriers of the Mother Stream were also stronger in some places and weaker in some, so the weaker creatures would not gain any benefits from coming here, other than getting hurt for no reason.

These creatures were not enveloped in the power of the Mother Stream, so their movements were slower. As a result, he played them like a top, and every one of them ended up becoming Garen’s only source of replenishment.

But in the end, his Soul Energy was still not infinite.

Five more years passed, and Garen felt his Soul Energy begin to weaken. The production rate of the Soul Ring was losing out to the rate of consumption, and he immediately knew that he could not continue drifting aimlessly like this.

He had a Soul Ring, and a position as a Void Pursuer. If he stayed in one place for too long, he would be the prime example of bait, luring Soul-Ring-Level Void Creatures to his doorstep.

In order to solve this threat, Garen designed a virtual model, and counted the longest duration he could stay in one world. He could not linger for longer than two hundred years, or else he would attract the Soul-Ring-Level Void Creatures nearby.

“The Void Creatures and the Ancient Endor civilization, they must have a place where the battle is mostly centered at! I can’t be the only inheritor around. If I can find another inheritor, then I can truly join a group, and then we can resist the Void Creatures together.”

With such an idea in mind, Garen started paying attention to the countless universes flowing outside the Mother Stream’s Barriers, trying to find a universe with the same scent of a Soul Seed.

Such universes were very easy to find, because not every universe could have Soul Energy Aura. Garen was a Void Pursuer, and he remembered how useful his super-sensitive sense of smell could be now. Put together with the Energy Machine Imprint, he could differentiate the wisps of Soul Energy Aura out of the tiniest hints of each universe’s aura.

Even though he knew the chances of such a search being successful were slim, Garen had finally found a new aim, so he was no longer as lost and listless as he had been.

Time passed slowly… The Soul Energy produced by Garen’s Soul Ring diminished further, and the parts of his own body that he could protect reduced further and further, as the power grew thinner.

After goodness knew how long, the chance he was waiting for finally manifested itself.

*****************

Poof!

A giant black octopus tentacle stabbed hard into the Mother Stream’s currents, pouncing at Garen. The tentacle was covered with countless little suction cups, and brought with it a powerful suction force that surged toward Garen.

“You’re asking for it!” Garen laughed coldly, watching the tentacle unleash its suction force in the Mother Stream. “Unleashing a suction force in this thick Mother Stream water? You have a death wish.”

He taunted unabashedly. After staying alone for so long, he had developed a habit of talking to himself, otherwise, he might even forget how to talk.

As though proving Garen’s jeers right, that black tentacle did not manage to catch him, but instead it instantly absorbed a huge amount of Mother Stream water, until the entire tentacle expanded, growing larger and thicker as it went.

Chapter 1155: Reincarnation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bzz… Bzz-bzz…

Countless tiny white cracks appeared on the surface of the tentacle.

“Don’t let me see you again!!!” roared the owner of the tentacle angrily. His berserking Will was intense enough to create countless waves in the water of the Mother Stream.

Bam!!

The huge expanse of green water exploded from within the tentacle, turning into a rain of blood that fell onto the surface of the Mother Stream, creating even more tiny ripples. What remained of the tentacle hurriedly retreated. It instantly vanished through the hole that was created in the Barrier.

The hole rapidly shrunk, but he could still see the colorful flowing light outside, though he did not know what that could be.

Just as Garen thought that everything would return to being peaceful as usual, and that he would continue drifting, suddenly he sensed a faint but clear wisp of Soul Energy Aura, appearing rapidly outside the hole.

“That’s…!” Garen was instantly stunned. His reflexes, far faster than light, recovered immediately.

Without a hint of hesitation, he gathered up all the Soul Energy he had and turned it into a propelling force behind him, so that he leaped out of the water like a fish.

Splash.

His whole body turned into a white line that shot toward the hole in the Barrier above him.

All skills and abilities were useless in the Mother Stream, because the laws of other universes were ineffective here, and only the General Universal Laws applied here. Garen’s Confinement Essence and the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s natural abilities were not affected, but he needed a physical body to use those, so he could not do anything in pure soul form. Therefore, the only thing he could use in the Mother Stream was the Soul Energy generated from his Soul Ring.

This remained true even if the strongest Void Creature came here, and that was also the crucial reason why the Mother Stream could protect the true souls of the Ancient Endor beings.

Garen was worried that his power was insufficient, so he used all of his Soul Energy up all at once, his body almost turning into lightning as he shot through the hole in the blink of an eye.

Poof!!

There was dull sound in his brain, and all Garen could see was rainbow-colored flowing light. He was blind to everything else.

The universe outside the hole was no longer the one where that giant octopus had been. Within a few short seconds, a ton of rainbow-colored light had flowed past outside, and the universe where Garen had sensed that Soul Energy Aura was a completely unfamiliar place, several universes away.

The rainbow-colored streaming light continued to flow past him, and Garen reached out his hand, trying to grab this streaming light, yet he could not touch anything at all.

The streaming light continued for more than ten minutes, and dark light spots began to appear slowly in front of him. Some of these light spots were grey, and others were black, all of them brushing past Garen.

As time passed, there were more and more light spots, with less space between them.

Psst!

Suddenly his vision blurred, and Garen abruptly found that the everything before him had opened up. The streaming light had instantly vanished, and directly in front of him was a wide, dark, vast and limitless area of space.

In the very center of this space, there was a giant planet with purple-red edges.

Garen could not help but turn around to look, the space behind him was just a sea of black, and he could still vaguely see the tiny ripples in space gradually vanishing.

“As expected… The place where the Mother Stream’s currents connect must be where the habitable planets exist.” Garen understood. “Things can only enter the Mother Planet when their lives end, and there they enter a new cycle. And the Mother Stream also transmits life in its endless flowing tides.”

He flew toward that single purple-red planet. The sun, a star suspended in space near it, drew his attention.

The light emanated by this star was golden in color, and it had many black spots on its surface, so it looked like a moldy kumquat.

“This…” Garen suddenly frowned. “There are such powerful laws here…”

The V-shaped white mark surfaced on his brow, but it faded instantly as soon as it appeared.

Garen closed his eyes, and carefully felt the differences in the laws of this universe as compared to the previous one. After a mere dozen or so minutes, he opened his eyes once more.

“Impressive…! It is 53% similar to the laws of the Mech Universe, and most of the Energy Machine Imprint’s functions don’t work here. Other than the basic computing abilities, there were strict laws regulating any unnatural powers, as well as anything that existed purely as energy.”

He looked at the kumquat-like sun, that piercing light forcing him to narrow his eyes slightly.

“This sort of universe… is even stricter than the Vampire World, the intermaterial bonds are shockingly strong, so it’s probably not possible to use other methods in order to leverage on the pure energy here…”

He allowed his body to fly toward that purple-red planet using its momentum alone. Looking at the purple-red planet from a distance, he would not have noticed that he was moving at all if it were not for the galactic debris brushing past him on both sides.

“Without a Jumping Ball, I can’t use any powers other than my Soul Energy… No, even my Soul Energy is being suppressed, no form of pure energy here can exist without material form… What an extreme world.” Garen frowned slightly, carefully analyzing the laws of this universe.

“But I can still use some of the knowledge I had gained over the past few worlds, so I should be able to protect myself without any problems. I just have to pinpoint the individual power system of this universe, and then I will be able to increase my powers quickly. It might be slightly difficult to reach the same heights as before… But in a world like this, I won’t be able to use unnatural powers, so naturally others can’t either, not even Void Creatures. My safety will be guaranteed!”

In that case, however, it would probably be very hard for him to leave this world on his own. That was why Garen was starting to wonder if it was a mistake to come here.

The vast Soul Energy around him was rapidly diminishing, it was being worn out at an even faster rate than when he was in the Mother Stream. Because this place did not allow anything that existed as pure energy to last for so long, so Garen knew that a soul such as his would not be able to last very long in here.

“I need to find a new body as soon as possible…”

He created an explosion behind him with his Soul Energy.

Psst!

The faint transparent light exploded, and Garen’s body immediately shot out, his speed reaching a terrifying level. Because he existed as merely a soul now, his own mass was close to zero, meaning he was practically insubstantial. The explosion of Soul Energy created a massive force that was enough to send him propelling forward at extreme speeds.

As he continuously approached the purple-red planet, mysterious images and fragments appeared before Garen’s eyes once more.

“These are the memories of the planets again… I can only receive them while I’m in soul form…” Garen clenched his teeth as the information overload surged into his brain, and was completely unsurprised by this sudden barrage of memories.

The same thing had happened in the past few worlds that he had transmigrated to.

But this time, it seemed to be slightly different.

The memories of this planet were scarily long, it seemed to have existed since the moment this entire universe exploded into being.

As the information surged in, other than the general trend of this planet, there was also a lot of f information about this universe as a whole. Although these were just fragmented clips, within a mere dozen minutes or so, Garen felt as though he had experienced the entire history of the entire planet and the universe, from the moment of their conception until this current instant.

“This universe… only has one habitable planet!” Garen resisted the headache, and looked at the enormous purple-red planet in front of him in shocked admiration. “According to the survival records included in the information given, this planet is the center of this universe, and it’s the only habitable planet in this entire universe.”

All the contents about the general trend instantly flowed through Garen’s brain.

This was a normal yet abnormal world.

Compared to the previous few worlds, this world was a lot more realistic, and a lot simpler.

The general trend of the entire world originated with the Four Great Cornerstones. In other words, it hinged on four people. Four users of unnatural powers who were constantly reborn and resurrected on this planet.

They had the Sacred Sigils of the Ancient Universe, and possessed unimaginable power. The four of them represented the entire planet, and the four basic powers of this universe. Other than them, no one else could use unnatural powers, they were the origins of all the legends. At the same time, they were also the source of the Soul Energy Aura that Garen was sensing.

“The Soul Energy Aura I sensed before this… is over there!!” Garen instantly determined his target location.

“The Four Great Cornerstones? What a strange law…” With a final sigh of admiration, his soul sped up further, turning into a shapeless light that fell straight toward the planet.

***********************

Lily of the Valley, in the country of Slann

In a small and slightly old yard by the suburbs, a yellow-skinned man with a tan was holding up a bespectacled boy of fifteen or sixteen with both hands, his expression solemn as he yelled urgently in a rather tongue-twisting language.

The hot sunlight shone down on both of them, and a faint stench of sweat began to rise from them.

The man was frowning so hard that his brows were knotted together, and he hurriedly picked up the boy, running toward a cooler, shaded part of the yard. He placed the boy gently on the slightly scalding floor, and then ran into the inner house hastily. Soon. he came out again with a basin of cold water, and there was even a white towel in the basin. The towel had been washed until it was yellowing slightly, and it looked like it had quite a few years behind it.

Splash.

He wrung the towel dry, and gently wiped the sweat off the boy’s face.

The boy had slightly pretty features, but he was mostly just plain. His skin was slightly pale, as though he did not get much sun, and his lips were extremely cracked, his eyes tightly shut. It was quite clear that he had a case of heatstroke.

Whoosh…

Suddenly, there was a cool breeze.

Faster than anyone could see, an invisible light fell directly down from the sky, stabbing directly into the area between the boy’s brows, It sank inside, vanishing without a trace.

The man did not notice a thing, and continued to wipe the sweat off the boy’s body carefully.

Soon, possibly because the cool wet towel had an effect, the boy’s body finally trembled a few times,

“Water… Water…”

Suddenly, he awakened blearily, calling out in a hoarse voice.

“Water? Here! Come on, drink slowly… take it slow.” The middle-aged man hastily took the cup of water he had prepared beforehand and brought it to the boy’s lips.

“I told you a thousand times not to fall asleep in the yard under the sun, but you never listen!” nagged the man in a low, whining voice that was completely different from his stern appearance.

The boy did not say anything more, and fell into a deep sleep after drinking a few sips of water.

The middle-aged man shook his head helplessly, picking up the boy in his arms and walking into the house, placing the boy on a bed mat in the room.

He reached out his hand again to touch the boy’s forehead, testing its temperature. When he felt that it had cooled down somewhat, he finally left, relieved. The stress of the past few moments had caused him to break out in a sweat as well, so he desperately needed a cold bath right now.

The man’s footsteps faded into the distance, and he entered another room, closing the door with a bang.

Only then did the boy lying on the mat slowly open his eyes.

Chapter 1156: Reincarnation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It’s a new beginning once again…” The boy spoke with a tone of wisdom, nostalgia, and a hint of weariness.

“After such a long selection, this should be the perfect body according to the general trend,” A white, indistinct V-shaped mark flashed between the boy’s eyes without leaving a trace.

Everything related to the boy’s memories instantly swept through Garen’s mind.

‘Kong Xiaofei: Seventeen years old, introvert and keeps to himself, a Year 2 Senior High School Student of Linglan City No.3 High School. Average results, bad in sports, enjoys reading comic books, drawing, sleeping…’

Garen swiftly scanned through all the different flashbacks that were swarming his mind, mainly focusing on Kong Xiaofei’s family.

Kong Xiaofei’s father, Kong Yuan, brought him and his elder sister up single-handedly. He works at an oil company with a decent pay and he was an ordinary, honest good man.

His mother died while giving birth to him.

The main focus was Kong Xinxue, Kong Xiaofei’s elder sister. When Garen was observing the planet’s memories, his fuzzily detected her as a major character.

Due to the fact that the memories were too overwhelming, plus the rules of the universe being too strict, he could only vaguely see pieces of it. He was not able to see the main content clearly. However, he was sure of one thing, one of the Four Great Cornerstones would come into contact with Kong Xinxue sometime in the future. And when these four fight hand to hand, Kong Xinxue would then play a more important role.

“It probably will not take a few years. By then, we will see whether the Four Great Cornerstones are of the same kind as me…” Garen was actually looking forward to it, as he started to feel this body’s state attentively.

Garen’s face fell as he started inspecting. “No wonder this body didn’t even bother to fight me back. It’s deteriorated to this point…”

He took a look at the Talent and Power data that was on display.

‘Kong Xiaofei — Strength 0.2, Agility 0.3, Physique 0.1, Intellect 1.1, Potential 0%. Soul Limit 50.’

Garen took a deep breath. “Besides the Intellect stats reaching the standards of an adult, the others were so horrible that he could hardly bear to see it, it was no different from advanced cancer…”

He held back the urge to cuss, instead, he focused on regulating all his remaining soul power to nourish this body.

Ever since the Soul Ring was formed, his soul power could finally be able to shift around at ease to nourish the flesh. The flesh’s essence was able to produce a God in the form of a soul, and the God would naturally be able to replenish the body’s essence. However, the only shortcoming was that this process has a high rate of consumption.

Especially in this sort of crazy strict world…

“It’s a good thing the pure energy state within the body isn’t really restricted, which is equivalent to energy attached to the substances.”

Garen checked his soul power storage; there were about fifty-three units which were vacant. In the Mech World, every unit would be sufficient to fully nourish one adult’s body and completely heal every indiscernible damage.

“However, there would be an eighty percent loss if one was to use his soul power to replenish his flesh. Moreover, this universe’s rules are ridiculous… A 5% effect at most on the body is already not bad… To hell with it!” He could not resist ranting.

Five percent. This meant that after all his remaining soul power was exhausted, there would not be any more extra components to nourish and strengthen this body. The rules here were ridiculously strict. In the entire universe, there were only four people who had extraordinary powers, the superpowers that were supported by the entire universe. Even putting this way could not describe how exaggeratedly crazy this was.

Frankly, Garen knew it deep in his heart. It was what he had expected.

Furthermore, he wanted to restore and accumulate a brand new soul power. The rate of the Soul Ring recovery was indeed terrifying. In addition to its ghastly output, he would have to wait for a long period of time if he planned to use it to nourish his body.

“Seems like I’d have to make use of whatever pharmacology and biochemistry I’ve learned from the other worlds… After all, I’ve lived for so many years, I am considered as an elite biochemist,” In the end, Garen still found a way out. He was going to utilize this universe’s substances to strengthen his body, and not just insist on using pure energy to nourish his body.

At the thought of it, he immediately spread all the stored soul power in his body to every part of his body altogether.

There were no sounds or any light effects, just the plain sight of Kong Xiaofei, the body Garen was attached to. Colors were gradually returning to his cheeks, and even his dried lips were starting to have a tinge of moisture.

The effect was immediate.

Garen could see with his naked eye that his body’s state was rising rapidly. As time passed, his soul power reduced and became weaker, but his body’s attributes, on the other hand, increased.

At the end, when the last traces of his soul power was almost exhausted.

‘Kong Xiaofei — Strength 0.5, Agility 0.6, Physique 0.4, Intellect 1.4, Potential 0%. Soul Limit 50.’

The attributes were just slightly improved.

“Why are there no changes!?” Garen was shocked. He put in so much effort assembling this Soul Ring from a couple of worlds, and all the soul power produced by the Soul Ring was now wasted just like this. This was a complete tragedy.

However, he could vaguely feel the small changes that were happening within his body, and he suddenly understood.

In this world, the rules were as such. There would no longer be drastic changes like before, no more radical occurrences that involved processes that would nearly be neglected. Every single change here would only happen bit by bit.

Even if he completely saved up all his soul power, it would be impossible for him to change a seriously-ill patient into an ordinary person brimming with energy. He had to recover according to his body’s restore rate in order to recover to his original state of physique.

“In other words, if you can master the ropes of the other worlds, you can advance through several processes instantly, inciting other strengths and then on, create a miracle.”

Garen lied on the mat. Since he was not able to recover his body in an instant, he might as well lie on the ground and have a good rest.

The good thing was that while his body was being nourished, his body would still be able to withstand for a few more days without eating or drinking. At the same time, his qualities would still continue to rise all the way until he finished up his powers.

“Energy Machinist Imprint can still be used for basic computing powers… But I’d need my soul powers to support it. I guess I won’t be able to take both into account in the future,” Garen said helplessly.

Lying on the mat feeling tired with a tinge of weakness surging within the body, he lost all desire to move his body.

As time slowly went by, he soon heard the sound of a key unlocking the door outside.

“Thank you for sending me back. Please, you can go now,” It was a melodious voice of a girl. She seemed young, maybe about eighteen or nineteen years old.

“Remember the concert this Saturday! You’re one of our main characters, so you have to come,” An old man said.

“I’ll try. I’m really sorry, teacher.”

“Alright, enough with the chit chat, I’ve got to go to send off the others.”

“Yeah. Take care.”

Footsteps could be heard before the sound of engines whirred up, indicating that the car was leaving.

Bang.

The yard’s door closed.

“Xiaoxue, you’re back?” Kong Yuan’s voice could be heard from the living room.

“Yeah, how’s Xiaofei doing?” The girl’s voice sounded extremely cold.

“Doing much better, I tucked him into bed already.”

“… I’ll go see him for a bit,” Kong Xinxue’s voice was getting nearer and nearer.

Garen recalled every single detail about Kong Xinxue and the relationship between her and Kong Xiaofei.

‘Kong Xinxue: Seventeen years old, a violin prodigy, Year 3 Senior High School Student of Linglan City No.1 High School. Participated in the region’s student classical music competition thrice and was crowned champion back-to-back for three years. Talent has already been gradually shown, and in the next two years, she’ll become a famous international classical violinist prodigy. Then, she will finally emerge as an incredible, world-renowned violinist when she reaches twenty-four years old.

Has a cool personality, maintains an ordinary relationship with her brother, Kong Xiaofei, which may be slightly distant.’

“What a stunning sister. No wonder the brother is such an introvert, always quiet and keeping to himself,” A thought flashed through Garen’s mind.

Soon enough, a young girl dressed in a white dress appeared by the bedroom door and peaked in.

The girl had long red hair flowing down her shoulders and bangs across her forehead, a hint of wariness in her eyes. The white dress on her accentuated her young body perfectly, showing off every single curve just nicely. It was a plain white dress with no patterns or any lacework, just a simple black belt wrapped around her waist.

“Are you feeling better?” Kong Xinxue asked softly. Once she saw Garen awake, the worry in her eyes was wiped away.

“Much better,” Garen responded.

Kong Xinxue nodded, then turned and left.

The conversation between these two siblings had always been like that, it was as if both sides were used to it already. Since they were young, since they knew how to speak, Kong Xiaofei and his sister always kept conversations short and brief.

“So this body has red hair…” Then only did Garen realize that his own hair was actually a shade of fiery red.

*********************

Since the day of the heat stroke, Garen took a leave so that he could stay at home to rest.

Kong Yuan goes to work every day from nine to five while Kong Xinxue was always busy preparing for her school examinations. Both of them had their hands full, unlike Kong Xiaofei who was always idling away his time at home.

His sole purpose of coming to this world was to search for an inheritor of the same kind. Even if the inheritor was not the same kind, he should at the very least have the presence of soul power. He had everything planned. If the other person was not an inheritor of the same kind, he would take the opportunity and absorb the person’s soul power. With that, he would increase the soul power in his Soul Ring, maybe even increase his Soul Seeds.

The reason why he attached himself to Kong Xiaofei’s body was that this person was destined to die already. In the near future when Kong Xinxue came into contact with the Four Great Cornerstones, Kong Xiaofei would die from an accidental involvement on the first night they meet.

The one who would kill him was actually one of the Four Great Cornerstones.

To attach himself to an identity like this, there was no longer the need to search around all corners of the world. In the entire star, the only Four Great Cornerstones would automatically come on their own, which actually saved up tons of Garen’s effort.

The second purpose was to hide away from the Soul Ring-Leveled Void Creatures and at the same time, properly consider the path on which he was about to embark.

However, the one thing that disappointed Garen was that the rules in this particular universe were too strict to a certain standard. The powers his body brought was far from what he initially expected. Thus, it was most definitely going to be a problem if he aimed to reach the extent good enough to face off the Four Great Cornerstones. After all, Garen was still unsure of what those four were really capable of.

Ever since he came to this body, Garen restricted the interactions between him and Kong Xinxue along with Kong Yuan. He would only see the both of them every day in the morning and nighttime. Meanwhile, life over here was somewhat similar to back when he was in Earth, a slight combination of life in China and Japan. Rice was deemed as the main course, and everything was available, including sashimi, stir-fry vegetables, dumplings and so much more.

One week had passed by in a blink of an eye, and there was not much communication in general. Garen’s body was starting to recover.

Chapter 1157

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“One, two, one two, one…” Garen was in the midst of doing push-ups, counting non-stop in the yard.

It was the weekend, which marked the end of this week’s holiday. The extra corresponding courses in school meant nothing to Garen, except that he would have lesser time to train and to recover.

After finishing ten push-ups, he got up and wiped away the beads of sweat off his forehead. Although his physique was slightly better, he still had to give Kong Yuan and Kong Xinxue some mental preparation as well. He could not just suddenly recover, that would be suspicious.

“Up so early huh… Xiaofei,” Kong Yuan yawned as he walked out of the house in his black pajamas.

The sky was not even bright yet.

“What do you want to eat? I can go buy it for you.”

“Bread and eggs,” Garen answered simply.

Kong Yuan nodded, “Go see if your sister’s awake, and see whether she wants anything.”

“Alright, I’ll go see.”

Garen pressed on his T-shirt to ensure the black material stuck on his skin would absorb his sweat; he then marched toward Kong Xinxue’s room.

Thump thump.

Nobody responded to the knocks on the door.

The door opened by itself, so perhaps it was not closed properly.

“Makes sense. The weather’s too hot, no way she would just stuff herself in her room,” Garen knocked harder.

Thump thump thump!

“Who is it?”

A barely-awake voice came from the room.

“It’s me,” Garen answered.

Not long after, Kong Xinxue opened her bedroom door. Her hair was a mess, as she stood there in her white nightdress.

“What is it?”

“Dad’s asking you what do you want for breakfast.”

“Same as you,” With a slam, Kong Xinxue closed the door once again. She seemed mad.

Baffled, Garen staggered back to the living room and relayed the message to Kong Yuan. He had no idea why Kong XinXue was angry, perhaps she just got up on the wrong side of the bed.

After breakfast, Kong Yuan went out to buy some vegetables.

Garen and Kong Xinxue were left in the yard under the cool morning sun, both of them sipping fresh tea.

The pale green tea was rickety in the cup as Garen kept swirling his cup around. It seemed thrilling as the tea almost spilled out of the brim every single time.

“Just drink your water, stop playing,” Kong Xinxue sat upright at her place with a stern look on her face, both hands circled around her cup.

With no other alternatives, Garen placed his teacup back down. He could not possibly tell her that he was actually training the accuracy of his body control.

Sitting in the yard, both of them were at their wits’ ends. Garen was still wearing spectacles, and his messy long hair covered up part of his face. Moreover, his spectacles were slightly oversized. With that combination, his face was basically covered up already. His clothes were untidy as well, the sweat on his T-shirt had already dried up, emitting a rank odor.

On the other hand, Kong Xinxue was dressed entirely in white, her hair tied into a simple ponytail behind her using a simple black silk. In addition to her delicate facial features and her proper posture, she gave off an elegant vibe.

“Recently… Do you have enough pocket money?”

They really did not have any topics to talk about, therefore, as the elder sister, Kong Xinxue took the lead and spoke first.

“If you don’t have enough money, I have some here.”

“It’s enough,” Garen replied curtly.

Then, it was silence.

The sun gradually turned half of the yard into a bright shade of gold as cicada sounds could be heard from the only brown tree in the yard.

“I’m going to take a shower,” Kong Xinxue stood up and walked toward the house.

“Okay.”

Garen responded shortly as he watched her enter the house, and only returned his gaze once he heard the sound of the bathroom door clicked shut.

Lifting the teacup gently, Garen took a sip again as he slowly regulated his breathing and heartbeat.

After a week of recovery, plus the nourishment of his powers, he was almost fully recovered, already reaching the normal standards of this body. Due to the fact that the body showed a heavy deficit along with plenty of damage in the congenital structures, he could only improve them in the future. At the very least, his powers were not fully exhausted yet.

“But I can’t just fully rely on my powers. I’ve got to choose a secret technique as my foundation,” Garen had been forcing himself to wait until this moment to begin thinking about this problem. He could only wait until his body was completely recovered before he could consider the training issue, otherwise not only would he be not training his physique, he would be hurting it instead.

All the secret techniques and killing moves he once masted slowly came to mind.

“This universe’s rules are indeed harsh, it would take an extremely long period of time if I want my own flesh to achieve the level of being able to resist heat weapons. I need about two years time and a killing move that can quickly come to form. It has to be highly destructive and capable of driving my body to train…”

After searching through all the sects, a swordplay similar to the Japanese Kendo came to Garen’s mind.

“To use the weapon’s sharpness to make up for my shortage of destructive power is indeed the shortcut for combat power. I’ll go with agility, it should not be that bad”

At a realm like Garen’s, although he did not comprehend Boards, his martial grades were thoroughly revised, already reaching another state of a realm. Most of the principles behind swordplay and fistfighting were somewhat similar.

Garen just simply focused all the essences from the other secret techniques on this certain swordplay, and soon, an extremely complex yet precise killing move was slowly taking shape.

Picking up a broken branch from the ground, Garen started drawing strokes in the air.

Up and down, then four corners. Every direction consisted up to thousands of different coping techniques to face all sorts of situations.

This was an extraordinarily-precise swordplay, no mistakes could be made on every track. Once an error is made, a brand new swordplay would be required to rectify. The entire swordplay was basically unlocking a series of locks. After the entire chain locks were unlocked, the effect produced would be groundbreaking.

To activate an extraordinary power as an ordinary mortal.

Of course, this was the original effect of this swordplay, who knew to what extent it would have in this world.

“Just try it then, let’s see to what extent can this pure technique be activated.”

Garen picked up a branch and slowly started drawing strokes in the air.

The branch became blurry between his fingers as it slowly started getting faster. As it accelerated, the blurry appearance intensified.

Wind!

All of a sudden, the branch stopped.

Crack!

With a soft crack, the branch broke in half, and the expected extraordinary power effect did not take place at all.

Garen sighed in disappointment.

“Although I did expect this, I really did not expect it’d be this hard to activate the extraordinary power’s boundary… This universe is indeed…”

He threw the branch away.

“Looks like I can only seek pure material attacks then.”

Ah.

Suddenly, Kong Xinxue’s scream could be heard from the house.

Garen’s expression changed instantly as he darted toward the house.

The first thing that came to mind was the Four Great Cornerstones. Did they decide to come earlier!?

“There’s no water…” Kong Xinxue’s urgent voice sounded.

But there was not enough time.

Garen had already reached the door of the bathroom and reached for the door handle.

Click.

The bathroom door opened with just a slit, and there was Kong Xinxue, stunned, staring back at Kong Xiaofei who was at the door. Her entire upper body was covered beneath a wet white towel, but the lower part of her body was not covered and strands of black hairs were visible.

“There’s no water?” Garen was shocked as well. Looking at Kong Xinxue like this, he was startled as well. Being too fast can be a pretty troublesome issue sometimes…

“Get out!” A red flush crept onto Kong Xinxue’s face as she yelled. “Get the hell out of here!”

********************

Garen had never expected such a thing that would only happen in television dramas would actually happen to him.

After about ten minutes or so, Kong Xinxue sat in the living room, still angry, right across where Garen was at.

“I can understand that as a boy sprouting from the youth of his teenage years, there would be intense urges coming deep from within you, feelings you may or may not have before. But please, don’t go wild expressing your unsatisfied and lewd desires towards your own sister for no reason at all! Do you even know what your own sister means to you? Or maybe you’re suggesting that you, as a seventeen-year-old young boy, have absolutely no knowledge on moral education?”

Bang!

She brutely slammed the table yet again.

“I, Kong Xinxue! The eldest daughter of the Kong family. I’ve always tried to put up an image of a proper, serious eldest daughter in front of you, Kong Xiaofei. I’ve always tried to live my life representing the positive life values! But I can’t imagine that the corrupt society we live in would put up with those toxic on the internet. Yes, toxic! Toxic that were able to poison and make my very own brother, my closest relative, to change.”

“Can you even understand how I’m feeling right now? Hmm? Kong Xiaofei! I’m talking to you!?” Kong Xinxue noticed that even now, Kong Xiaofei was distracted! Distracted!?

She was lecturing her one and only brother and he was distracted!?

Unforgivable!

Bang!

A loud noise sounded as she slammed her hands vigorously against the table, causing it to shake.

“Every single day I return home, I’m doing all I can to restrain myself from any sort of vulgar behavior and using words of profanities, all this to provide the only boy in our Kong household a positive environment to grow, in the perspectives of human life, the world, and moral values. Yet, look at yourself now. In time you will learn how to keep yourself in check. Now, have you stooped so low to the point where you peep at me while I was in the showers!?”

Her voice instantly raised by an octave.

“Well, I say… Can you lower down your voice…” Garen forced a wry smile. “I wasn’t trying to peep at you in the shower…”

“You were ogling!” The urge to lecture that was buried deep within Kong Xinxue finally burst out now.

“Although they both have the same words and there’s only one character difference, there is a vast difference between these both serious natures! (TL Note: In Chinese, the term for peep and ogling shares the same Chinese character.) Hu…” She exhaled heavily. “I’m still contemplating whether to tell Father straight away.”

“I think you had better not…” Garen was completely speechless, “I told you, I really wasn’t peeping. I just heard your scream and that’s why…”

“And you’re still making up excuses for yourself.” Kong Xinxue took a sip of water. “I can understand your feelings right now, always hiding in the corners sneaking your so-called reading materials that cannot bear the light of day. Even though I did give it a try, all just an attempt to understand my only brother, to understand what kind of thoughts he would have. Thinking back now, these things are really just disgusting…” She said as an appalled look was written all over her face.

Chapter 1158: Kong Xinxue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“However,” Her entire upper body suddenly leaned forward to Garen, both of them had their noses against each other, their faces almost stuck together.

“I am pleased.”

“What?” Garen was shocked at her sudden movement. He had never seen such a temperamental person in his life. Even after transmigrating between so many worlds, this was the very first time he encountered someone who displayed such a split personality. The very second before, she was still cool and collected, but at this very moment, it was as if she changed into an entirely different person.

“I am relieved, as you have finally grown up, you’ve become a man,” Kong Xinxue grabbed on to Garen’s collar and almost lifted him up.

Bang.

She released her grip and Garen fell butt first back on to the chair.

“As a man, there will always be the dark desires buried deep within your heart that will tempt you into taking actions, and you’ve finally taken the first important yet poor-natured move. I don’t know if I should be happy or upset, but there’s one thing I know for sure.”

Kong Xinxue stood up and walked toward her own room.

“And that is, courage is the key element that makes a man.”

“Courage?”

“Do you know the Infinite Self-defence Rights?” She threw at him a black fountain pen. The pen rotated speedily and marked a straight trajectory before landing beside Garen on the sofa. “As a man, you have to be alert at all times and be ready to step up for a lady. Furthermore, how are you going to battle if you don’t have any weapons?”

“Weapons?”

Garen held the fountain pen up. There was nothing different about this item, it was just an ordinary black fountain pen.

Kong Xinxue turned back.

“Humans only know that it is not illegal to use one’s scissors for self-defense, but they don’t know that a fountain pen actually provides a better concealment. Practice using it… It’ll come in handy one day.”

She waved elegantly, then entered her room. After her door was slammed shut, no movements could be detected anymore.

Garen stared speechlessly at Kong Xinxue as she walked into her own room, then glanced at the fountain pen held in his hand.

“Weapon? This?”

An undeniably appropriate image kept bouncing into his head.

Nighttime in the streets.

“No… Please, don’t… I’m begging you…” Eyes filled with tears, Kong Xinxue begged as she shrunk into the corner in the alley.

Several thugs surrounded her, lustful smiles written all over their faces as they grinned at their trapped little sheep.

“Hey, little girl…It’s dangerous to be out about the streets alone in the middle of the night.”

“Looks like we’ve got to educate you on what safety is about, hehehe…”

“Shout all you want, nobody would come to your rescue no matter how much you scream or shout…”

Chirk.

A flick knife sprung out in the hands of one of the thugs.

According to the Infinite Self-defence Rights, the perfect time to counterattack is when the opponent shows his weapon!

There would only be one chance! Speed! Ruthless! Accurate! One fatal blow!

The silver ballpoint pen swiftly fell into her hand as a cold look flashed through Kong Xinxue’s eyes.

Ah! Ah ah!

After a few screams, everything was silent in the alley.

“What a terrifying lady…” Garen shook his head in an attempt to shake away the crazy thoughts in his mind. However, for unknown reasons, he was slightly amused.

“She has a personality, and her actions are different from how she portrays herself to be, it’s like she has a dual personality. And she’s pretty. Such a special girl, no wonder one of the Four Great Cornerstones developed a crush on her,” Garen touched his chin, finally acknowledging the fact that this world was actually quite interesting after all.

********************

Monday, it was time for school.

Hiss…

Garen had his head on the table as he napped.

The teacher’s lecture sounds in the classroom automatically played as his lullaby. The scratching sounds of students making notes around could be vaguely heard as the scratch marks echoed in the classroom, giving off a certain hollowness.

This world was almost the same as Earth, the similar lifestyle that was a combination of Western and Eastern cultures. There were also heat weapons, missiles, tanks, and even nuclear weapons. If it were not for the different name and the geographic location, Garen would have thought that he had arrived at another parallel world to Earth.

The basic knowledge learned in class were practically as easy as ABC to Garen. The only thing he needed to pay attention to was that he should not use other world’s more advanced formulas to calculate when he solved questions in order to avoid triggering a worldwide buzz.

“Hey, Fei, I heard you suffered a heat stroke and almost died. Is it real?”

His deskmate, also one of Kong Xiaofei’s few only friends, Koslan, was currently pretending to copy down notes as he squeezed Garen’s elbows.

“It’s fake,” Garen simply responded, “Would a person who almost died return beside you this fast?”

“True, makes sense,” Koslan nodded in agreement.

“Alright, I’m going to take a nap. Don’t disturb me,” With that said, Garen slipped into a deep sleep once again. In this world, nobody knew his real identity and his specialties, so naturally, there would be no threats of danger.

The only trouble he had was that particular day two years from now where one of the Four Great Cornerstones would kill Kong Xiaofei in an accident.

He did not need to go searching around, he just needed to wait. Until then, he would figure out whether the Four Great Stones were the same kind of inheritors, or were they perhaps just some Void Creatures.

After a nap, classes had already finished. For someone like Kong Xiaofei who had disappointing academic results, the teachers had long given up their hopes on him already.

The No. 3 High School was not a good school in the first place, most of the teachers just muddled along however they could.

“Hey, Fei, Koslan,” A masculine-looking girl dressed in a black-pleated dress walked toward the both of them.

“It’s Patch. Why are you looking so feminine today? Are you experiencing your second spring (TL Note: Directly translated from Chinese, ‘second spring’ is used to describe a person who experiences falling in love a second time later on in life when she’s older.)? Koslan greeted her with a bright smile.

“Don’t call me Patch… Also, what’s with this second spring? I haven’t even had my first spring!” The girl was Zong Buqin, also a close friend of Kong Xiaofei in class. Due to her over-masculine looks and how she always liked aiming for the last hit in games, she was nicknamed Patch.

“So? Are you feeling better?” Zong Buqin looked at Kong Xiaofei with a face full of concern.

“Much better,” Garen nodded.

“Are you up for some ice skating then? The Dream Ice Arena will be done renovating today, let’s go have a look at how is it now.”

“I’ll pass, I have something on already, you guys go ahead though.” Garen declined immediately. He only had another two years, and even though he was confident that he would not lose the battle, he should definitely not look down on his opponent. He had to perform the best he could.

“Aren’t you scared of flashing someone? Wearing a skirt to ice skate,” Koslan grinned devilishly.

“So what if I do? Are you going to look?” Zong Buqin had her arms on her waist as she retorted.

“Yeah.”

“If you really dare, I’ll even lift my skirt up!”

“Are you going to be responsible for it?”

“You’d want to run once you see it!” Zong Buqin snorted.

“Forget about it then.”

“Alright, you both continue your banter, I’ll take my leave first,” Garen left the classroom, blatantly ignoring the duo who was quarreling. In Kong Xiaofei’s memories, those two had the pranking scale that not many people could actually relate to.

He walked all the way until he reached the balcony.

Garen pushed open the metal door and walked toward the railing, then he looked down.

“Other than the Four Great Cornerstones, this world has no other systems of power, all they have is technology. Should I consider joining the government’s troops to sell some skills?” He thought about it as though he had returned to his peaceful and relaxing life back on Earth.

There was no danger, even the so-called Four Great Cornerstones were not much of a threat in his eyes. Life continued to move on undisturbed, according to its timeline. There were no sudden twists or turns.

He pulled out his handphone and used the front camera to check himself out.

Red short hair, thick spectacles frames, and a pale, ghastly skin. His blue-white uniform shirt’s collar was folded high, covering his neck. His height was just average, and his body was neither too fat nor too thin. He was wearing a pair of unadjusted ordinary leather shoes that were coated with a layer of dust filled with wrinkles, shreds of evidence that indicated that he had been wearing them for a long period of time.

“At first glance, you’d know he’s not any more special than any other ordinary kids.”

With a heave of sigh, Garen placed his spectacles down. To his surprise, his face was actually pretty good looking. His thin brows nicely complemented his big eyes and sharp nose, his moisturized lips and his glowy skin that had the slightest tinge of hair growing were signs that his body was actually recovering recently.

“Forget about it, that’s all. I’ll resume training the swordplay I learned earlier.

Garen began regulating and controlling his breathing and his internal secretion softly.

The Energy Machinist Imprint’s computing power could provide him a detailed observational data toward his body, and at the same time, provide the most suitable adjustment plan in order to help his body achieve the desired goal in the shortest time possible.

Every inch of his muscles started trembling as the different muscles were fighting against each other, forming a different direction of force in the body. This was an extremely high-end form of training that only powerhouses who were precise about themselves could use.

With the aid of Garen’s Martial Art Realm and Energy Machine Imprint, he easily fulfilled the requirements.

His finger started drawing strokes, one after another, in a coherent but cool, decisive manner.

********************

A week passed by in a blink of an eye. Every day was passed with the accompaniment of Koslan and Zong Buqin’s bickering.

Garen would go up to the balcony to train his swordplay with every free time he had. At his level, it was natural for him to master the essential points in a short period of time, and the entire swordplay only consisted of three stages.

Firstly: Slight knowledge. Reaching mastery of ten thousand and above of different sword skills with high accuracy.

Secondly: Proficient. The ability to use different sword skills to carry out combinations at random to deal with external changes.

Thirdly: Thorough. Completely mastering all sword skills and turning everything into one’s own instinct, reflecting sword skill in lightning-like condition.

Garen’s own Martial Arts Realm had long surpassed the third grade of this swordplay, so the only thing he had to do was master all the sword skills and incorporate everything into this body’s instincts.

This required a vast amount of repetitive practices. After all, this was a new set of body, not his body from before.

Besides that, he really had to strengthen his body. Also, he had to find a sword, a sword that was suitable for him.

“The power would slowly nourish my body, so I can still buy some herbs and make myself some medicine. I don’t know whether the medicine in my memory is suitable or not, but I can always give it a try.”

“Meanwhile, regarding the sword problem, I can enroll in the school’s unlimited Martial Arts department.”

Chapter 1159: Life’s Turning Point 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The world was indeed strange.

The center of the universe was just like a planet. It was as if the entire universe only had that merely one surviving planet left.

Garen did not know how to describe this particular feeling other that it was plain weird.

However, with his capabilities, it was just a holiday for him to just have fun and enjoy as he waited for the general trend to begin.

This was the attitude that he had in life.

Time flew by fast.

In a blink of an eye, three weeks had already passed by, marking his one month time in this world.

On the other hand, his swordplay was slowly coming to shape already. Although he faced several limitations in this body, his improvements in all aspects had certainly been extremely alarming. Not only that, he even used his Soul Powers and other methods to raise his physical attributes.

*********************

After sleeping through another boring day of classes, Garen finally crawled up from his desk lazily. He did not know why just a moment of relaxation would result in him losing the urge to move forward. Sometimes, he even thought that living a simple life in this world was not a bad idea as well.

He took a look at his current attributes.

‘Kong Xiaofei — Strength 1, agility 1.2, physique 1.2, intellect 1.5. Potential 0%. Soul Limit 50.’

“So this is the final limit of my powers? It’s basically the standards of an ordinary person,” Garen felt helpless. He originally thought that he could at least still slack off a little. However, from the looks of it now, he had to make a greater effort in order for this to work.

He raised his head and checked his surroundings. There were a few students chatting in the white classroom, their chirpings no different from birds.

Koslan and Zong Buqin were still bickering like lovebirds.

Two students were at the back of the classroom holding their textbooks as a blackboard and using chalks to draw on them as though it was enjoyable.

The boys were dressed in white shirts and black slacks whereas the girls wore white blouses paired with black mini skirts and long, knee-high socks. Their outfits resembled the Japanese traditional uniforms.

“Feels like St. Oriole Academy…” Garen took a breath, once again reviewing the history of this world.

The planet was divided into three continents and four oceans. The Red Nation, Slann, and the Black Federation were known as the three big kingdoms, whereas the other small countries survived along the edge. Peace was able to be maintained because of nuclear weapon chains that were similar to those back on Earth. Everything else was not any different compared to Earth. Other than the customs being slightly similar, he basically found zero connections.

“Name-wise, there is even a sensation of combination, that’s so boring,” Garen did not even want to use his brain. After all, he was on a holiday break, so what was the point of fighting flat out?

Clap.

The girl sitting in front of him dropped her eraser on his feet.

Garen bent over to pick it up, then threw it back to the girl.

“Thanks.”

The girl turned over to give him a smile. Though it was not considered pretty, it was still pure and sincere.

“No problem.”

Garen stood up. It was time for him to go home.

The afternoon sunlight shone in from the window not far away, the warm rays touched the back of his hand.

Bag in hand, he walked out of the classroom alone and started his way back home.

Behind him was the noisy school and the sights of a few random bullies asking money from kids. The students would actually try to avoid this area subconsciously.

Garen walked to the front of a vending machine and threw in a one yuan coin dug out from his pocket.

Suddenly, two huge figures appeared behind him and surrounded him.

“Yo~ Someone’s pretty rich, what do you say about making friends? Shouldn’t be a problem for you to buy each of us a bottle of green yogurt huh?”

One of them who sported long hair and a silver ear piercing grinned, “How is one bottle enough for us? Each of us should get three bottles.”

The fatty person beside beamed devilishly. Both of them were dressed in all loose, black long sleeves and slacks. One had white hair and the other silver, obviously, they were not good seeds.

Garen exhaled heavily.

“I’ve always thought that teaching you gangsters a lesson would be pretty boring, that’s why I’ve never done anything. However, since you guys took this upon yourselves, don’t blame me…”

“What are you babbling about, punk?” When the gangsters saw that they could not get the money out of Garen, they got agitated.

Whoosh!

Garen spun around and his blade drew out a curve which landed on the long-haired teenage boy’s neck. Bang!

The boy only realized it after the blow landed on him and blinked his eyes in surprise. Their eyes rolled and they lost all strength.

Plop. One of them fell to the ground.

The remaining fattie had his mouth wide open, his expression was shocked and speechless.

“You…”

When he finally reacted, he swiftly swung a punch at Garen. Even though the punch was quick, it was nothing.

Garen shifted his head to the side, effortlessly avoiding the punch, before rushing forward and retaliating with his knee.

With a plop, the fattie fell onto the vending machine. He rolled his eyes, he, too, had passed out.

Garen bent over and searched the gangsters, picking up about ten dollars of change. As he stood up, he realized students walking by around him were sizing him up with a terrified look.

“How boring.”

He found life like this was too boring already. It was obvious that fighting back against gangsters was a never-before-seen incident in the school, as everyone stared as if they were looking at aliens.

He turned around and bought a can of Coke, and walked back to his home as he started drinking,

“Well, teaching gangsters a lesson really is old stuff, but I did bump into them, no way was I going to just let it go,” he thought.

This body’s physical fitness was the same as an ordinary person’s. In addition to the terrifying effects from his practice swordplay, fighting a dozen of them would just be plain warm up, not to mention just two of them.

As he walked toward home, Garen did not notice a short-haired girl dressed in white athletic attire standing not far away, silently watching him. Or, perhaps he did notice her, it was just that he did not bother.

After all, high school life was indeed two different things for him.

********************

“I’m back.”

Garen opened the yard’s door and closed it back.

In the small pond located in the yard, a red Koi fish wriggled as if it was welcoming him home.

The yard seemed to be empty.

As Garen walked into the house, there was a strip of paper left on the table. He took it up and read it.

‘Will be organizing some activities at my company this afternoon, you guys go ahead and order takeout or make something to eat for yourselves. — Dad’

The house was empty and completely silent, save for the occasional car honks from outside.

The afternoon sunlight shone over the ground, mapping the entire living room a shade of bright red.

Click.

Suddenly, the yard door opened slowly once again.

Kong Xinxue walked through the door with her violin case in hand. She was wearing a white dress, her fiery red long hair gently flowing in the wind. The natural makeup on her face was unusually refined, and she looked as if she was the most beautiful picture standing before the setting sun.

“Wow, you’re actually home earlier than me, that’s unbelievable,” Kong Xinxue turned her gaze toward Garen who was standing in the house.

“Why so?” Garen casually replied. After living together for this period of time, he sort of understood this sister’s nature. Although she seemed cool and elegant on the outside, she was definitely a sucker for ripping others’ scars on the inside. People were usually convinced by her cold exterior, and that usually ended up them being lied to without even knowing.

“Just unbelievable,” Kong Xinxue turned around and walked straight to Garen. “Something a person cannot do or take, at least according to the dictionary.”

She actually explained the meaning of this term in detail.

“So why is it unbelievable for me to be back first?” Garen added.

“Well, I thought you would be back early and try to force your way into my room, rummage through my things to find the tools I used to vent my wild desires last night, then have unforgiving, disgusting illusions about your lovely, pure and precious sister who cherishes you so, so much. Don’t you feel shameless,” Kong Xinxue no longer needed to put up a facade in front of Garen anymore, she just unleashed her bad nature without any hesitation.

“Have I done that before?” Garen blinked his eyes innocently.

“Haven’t you?” Kong Xinxue was standing right before Garen. She was almost at his height, her towering chest almost touching Garen’s chest. Her red eyes that resembled rubies stared into Garen’s eyes.

“Look me in my eyes and tell me you’re not lying.”

Garen had his eyes fixed at her eyes.

Both of them glared at each other until their eyes started hurting, but neither wanted to give in and blink.

The house was entirely silent, no sound could be heard besides the sound of each other’s breathing.

The clock on the wall slowly ticked away, and five minutes passed…

Kong Xinxue raised her arm to pulled strands of her hair back before throwing a punch.

Bang!

The blow directly landed on Garen’s abdomen.

Her actions were swift and skilled, it was as if she was secretly trained in martial art techniques that were not completely rigid. However, this was not the reason Garen did not dodge. The real reason was that Kong Xiaofei would not be able to dodge with that kind of speed. As for Garen, he just did not bother.

The small fist landed on Garen’s abdomen, then retracted.

Kong Xinxue cast a glance at Garen, then turned back to her own room as if nothing just happened.

“Nice abs.”

With that, she opened the door and entered her room. After that, the house returned to its original silence.

“Why is she acting crazy again…” Garen rubbed his abdomen. The body’s physique had definitely improved a ton, but even though this punch would not actually inflict an actual damage, it still hurt a bit. On the other hand, it was obvious that Kong Xinxue did not use all her strength, it was just a sign of punishment.

This punch represented her place as the eldest daughter in the Kong family and the powers she held. Those who dared go against her would never end up in a good place.

“Though she seems mature and crazy on the surface, in reality, she just can’t shake off the nature of a childish normal student,” Garen thought as he walked over to the dining table and poured himself a cup of tea.

Just another boring day.

In the evening, the rare sight of Kong Xinxue with her apron on was preparing dinner while Garen was helping out at the side. Small exquisite of dishes were then served on the dining table.

Tomato scrambled eggs, vegetable soup, and green pepper stir-fry meat. Although they were all just ordinary home-cooked food, they definitely looked delicious and it seemed that both color and fragrance were in place.

“Thank you,” Garen spoke.

“Go wash your hands,” Kong Xinxue gave him a commanding look.

Chapter 1160: Life’s Turning Point 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was Garen’s first time staying with a neurotic patient who was suffering from personality splits. Hence, he was always constantly worried about what kind of unexpected things the patient would actually do.

“Got it,” He then stood up and went to the basin to wash his hands. Behind him, he could hear the sounds of Kong Xinxue placing down the bowls and chopsticks.

Two of them then started eating silently.

As time passed by, the dishes on the table slowly reduced, and soon enough, the plates were empty. Even the soup was half gone.

“Is it delicious?” Kong Xinxue did not eat much as most of the time she was just staring at Garen eat. She seemed to find Garen’s eating gestures something new and interesting.

“They’re okay,” Garen answered honestly. Even though the dishes did look tasty, the taste was surprisingly displeasing. It was fairly confusing as to where the delicious scent was coming from. For Garen to say that it was decent was already too good of a compliment.

“Your eating posture,” Kong Xinxue leaned closer as she had her stare locked on Garen’s lips.

“What is it?” Garen was slightly startled by her sudden closeness and backed off a little bit.

“It’s nice,” Kong Xinxue continued. “It’s like a rigid etiquette. Really, it’s unbelievable. The piece of meat under your lip actually isn’t stained by any grease. Such a precise yet elegant eating etiquette… This is probably the first time I’ve seen something like this.”

“Oh, really?” Garen put on a bored face as though he did not want to respond. An ordinary person might not be able to understand his true meaning, but Kong Xinxue could see through it. Not only did she make it hard for people to predict her next moves due to her split personalities, she also had an extremely subtle observation, which Garen already figured out long ago.

“Don’t you want to talk about it?” Kong Xinxue retracted her head. “Seems like people this age have a really wild imagination… I heard students this age can easily suffer from a special illness.”

“A special illness?”

“Basically thinking that you’re different from the others and that the world revolves around you. You think protecting and maintaining peace in the universe is all on you, just something like that,” Kong Xinxue said calmly as she poured herself a cup of tea and slowly sipped on it.

Garen noticed that the cup of tea she was drinking was not the one on the table, it was another cup of something that she prepared herself.

“Do you want to drink?” She lifted her cup and asked.

“What’s that? I smell something weird,” Garen answered with his brows furrowed.

“It’s soy sauce.”

“…”

A weirdo indeed.

Garen continued staring at Kong Xinxue who was seated right across him. With just a glance, she really was a cool and elegant beautiful lady, who knew she would be drinking soy sauce as if she was sipping coffee?

“I’m going to shower now.”

Kong Xinxue stood up.

“Do you want to join?”

“…” Garen looked at her as she stared back with her head crooked. He was utterly speechless.

“What a boring man,” She pulled her long hair as she slowly walked to the bathroom. “Sexually incompetent.”

“…”

“As expected… As one of the primary characters, despite being an ordinary person, it was still not that simple at all.” Garen said helplessly as he started cleaning up the cutleries.

No matter what his response was, he would still be the final targeted victim. He was already immune to this move that Kong Xinxue always used.

“Hey, sexual incompetence.”

“… Don’t you think it’s slightly inappropriate for you to call your only younger brother that?”

Garen got up helplessly.

“Help me get my underwear. They’re in the second drawer below my wardrobe in my room. I shall allow you to have a whiff at it, but you better not let me catch you,” Kong Xinxue was standing naked behind the bathroom’s glass door.

“I’m not even a pervert,” Garen was completely dumbfounded and quickly went to her room to retrieve a set of underwear. He soon noticed that all of Kong Xinxue’s underwear were white, every single one of it.

However, as he opened the drawer, a stack of letters fell out. They were all pink color with a small heart print on its top corner, with the words printed behind: To Kong Xinxue.

“Love letters?” Garen simply pulled out one of the letters. The seal was opened and he pulled out a piece of paper which was empty. There was nothing on the paper.

“Nothing?” Garen then swiftly flipped through all the other love letters. They were all the same, empty.

With a precise agility, he stuffed the love letters back before carrying the conservative underwear to the front of the bathroom.

“Just place it on top of the washing machine outside.”

“Alright.”

Garen placed the underwear down and turned around to leave.

“Oh yeah, sister,” He suddenly stopped.

“Speak.”

“I’ve known you for so long, but how come I’ve never seen anyone try to pursue you? Is it because everyone found out your weird personality and decided to keep their distance?” Garen asked straightforwardly.

“…” There were no responses from the bathroom.

After a long pause, he could hear the sound of water from the showerhead.

Garen knew that since she did not want to talk about this topic, there was no point asking anymore as he would not get any answers from her. He just had to be patient with her. She was one of those people who would definitely keep their mouth shut for a period of time once they had decided on not opening up about a certain something as she believed that talking about something before the period of time would not reveal her true thoughts about it.

She was just such a weird person, so perhaps it was not something out of the ordinary that nobody liked her.

With that thought, Garen left and entered his own room.

********************

In a blink of an eye, another month had passed.

Everything moved on as usual. School, practicing swordplay, eating, and squabbling with Kong Xinxue. Life was so plain to the point that Garen had forgotten what was he waiting for already.

Until one day.

“Father.”

Kong Xinxue sat across Kong Yuan, her blouse was as white as snow. She looked like the most elegant white plum blossoms, her face calm and indifferent.

“This is the cash reward I won in my competition.”

With both hands, she pushed a bank card on the table toward her father.

Kong Yuan awkwardly stared at his own daughter.

“Save it for yourself. You’re all grown up already, you should save up some money for yourself,” As a man, he still had his own dignity. He could not possibly take the money that his own daughter worked hard to earn.

Garen was drinking tea by the side as he leisurely stared at the both of them.

“Sister asked you to take it, so just take it. We’re family, after all, it doesn’t matter whose money belongs to who does it?” He persuaded.

“Yeah, this is just a little something I worked hard for as a token of appreciation for this family,” Kong Xinxue replied sensibly, “I’m genuinely happy that I’m able to contribute to this family.”

She could always use a strict tone to say something that was able to arouse one’s enthusiasm.

Kong Yuan still did not accept it.

“You know it too. Our financial situation at home is not that bad, we’re not short of your contribution.”

“This is not a contribution, I just want to be a part of the process of building this family. Also, don’t you think our house is a little too small? Although I understand that as a man, you should maintain your self-esteem and restraints. But, whenever I ‘accidentally’ pass by your room and see you with your right hand and that certain rigid movement pleasuring yourself, I, as your daughter, really feel sad from the depths of my heart.”

“…” Kong Yuan was absolutely stunned.

Garen froze as well…

Being pointed out by one’s own daughter that he self-pleasured, also being caught more than once, was the most terrifying thing in the world for a middle-aged father who was almost forty years of age!

The atmosphere in the living room froze.

Garen could see beads of sweat slowly trickling down Kong Yuan’s forehead and temples.

This father did somewhat understand this quality of his daughter, but he did not expect her to use such a sorrowful method of persuading him to accept this money. Even worse, it happened in front of his son.

Gulp…

A soft sound came from Kong Yuan’s throat.

Even Garen felt sad for this father. It was perhaps the most distressing thing of all the fathers in the world to have such a neuropathic daughter.

“So… ” Kong Xinxue pushed the bank card once again, “Please, just take it.”

Her casual expression proved that she was not even bothered.

The atmosphere was then slightly alleviated.

Kong Yuan had his head hung low and started drinking tea like Garen. He had to relax his triggered heart someway.

“Although this one thousand two hundred million…” Pu!

Kong Yuan spat out a mouthful of tea. Even Garen who was sitting by his side choked on his tea and started coughing.

Kong Xinxue did not finish her sentence as she used a magazine on the table to block herself with an incredible speed. The tea splashed onto the pages of the magazine, then she placed it back down as if nothing happened.

“One thousand… Two hundred… Million?!”

Kong Yuan’s expression and tone were implausible as he stared at his familiar yet unrecognizable daughter.

“Yes, my dear father. Your hearing did not go wrong, you don’t have to suspect anything,” Facing the alien stares coming from these two men, she still did not show any trace of abnormality.

“I participated in eleven regional level competitions and I emerged as champion in eight of those, the four competitions that I won silver in did actually affect my reputation. After that, I just received twenty-one concerto lists from all over the country. The pay is pretty decent too. Oh yeah, I won about one thousand one hundred million from the lottery last month and I just claimed back the cash reward a few days ago.”

“The last point is the actual point…” Garen could not resist complaining.

In other words, Garen did not care about the money much, but it was still a bit hard for Kong Yuan to accept such a huge sum of money which was almost equivalent to his income his entire life. His daughter even presented it right before his eyes and used such force in hopes that he would accept the money.

“We’ll go check out new houses tomorrow then.”

Kong Xinxue concluded.

This was the turning point of life that marked the start of a dramatic change.

Garen remembered the fragments which showed that the Kong family house had impressive conditions, but little did he know this was how it all happened…

And that was the end of this time’s family meeting.

It was until then, Garen finally picked up a little interest on this world, all because of this cheap sister, Kong Xinxue.

This sister who was constantly suffering from typical split personalities was always in and out of different mental states, she could always end up doing things he would never expect.

This peculiar unknown feeling made him feel that maybe this world was not that boring after all.

Therefore, he decided to follow up on Kong Xinxue. He had a new interest for such a neurotic sister and her daily life.

Chapter 1161: Joy 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen woke up bright and early the next day. Since it happened to be the weekend, he decided to follow Kong Xinxue out and see if he could discover anything interesting.

After eating breakfast and washing the dishes, Kong Xinxue changed into a black dress, took an umbrella, and left the house.

Meanwhile, Kong Yuan had left for work. Garen was bored because he had already grasped Saber Art instinctually and all that was left was to strengthen his body. The constant nourishment from his Soul Energy and the Internal Organ Training Method of his specialized Saber Art Secret Method fused into his Energy Machine Imprint. This allowed it to control his body with ultimate precision while achieving the most superior effects of his Internal Organ Training Method at all times.

The presence of the Energy Machine Imprint was equivalent to Garen constantly training himself at every moment because his physical strength seemed to change daily. Nonetheless, this was merely child’s play for someone like him who already had tremendous accumulations.

The No. 1 High School was the best senior high school in Lily of the Valley. The students there either had the best grades or were the children of the government merchants with the most powerful family backgrounds. This school greatly surpassed the others within the city in every aspect.

Garen left the house following Kong Xinxue. When he saw her getting into a taxi after walking down a street, he followed her frantically.

“Excuse me, please follow that car in front,” Garen instructed hastily.

“No problem.” The driver sneered dubiously. There was clearly a slight misunderstanding.

Numerous cars came and left on the roadway in the downtown area. The traffic seemed somewhat heavy during the weekends but once they had passed a few consecutive red lights, they arrived at the front of a gymnasium quickly.

Kong Xinxue got down and was immediately greeted by several people that consisted of both men and women. They seemed very eager as they pulled her into the gymnasium hurriedly.

Garen got down from the car behind her and raised his head up to look at the building.

‘Performance of the Famous Symphony Orchestra’s Intelligent Paradise’

An enormous red banner hung above fluttering in the wind, giving off distinct characteristics of socialism.

Several security guards kept watch at gymnasium’s doorway. They were dressed in blue uniforms and were smoking and chatting happily with each other. The door closed quickly after Kong Xinxue and the group entered.

Garen glanced at the writing that was stuck above the door which read: Passageway for internal personnel.

“Is it a concerto performance?”

He severely lacked in general knowledge regarding both classical music and earning money. Therefore, he was unclear about the total remunerations that could be earned through concerto performances.

“However, attending a concerto after buying a winning lottery ticket clearly shows that an individual is planning to train their own Ability Qi Fields.”

He turned the corner around this door and walked to the gymnasium’s front, to where the tickets were currently being sold at its biggest door. More than ten people were scattered in a queue to buy tickets.

Garen rummaged the insides of his pockets for loose change. He had about more than a hundred left before he walked forward to line up and buy a ticket.

It was time for him to enter soon. He followed the stream of people and entered the gymnasium where it was completely pitch-dark inside. The faraway performance space in the center was the only section illuminated with lights while numerous music stands were already arranged on top. Several staff members were busy tuning the audio.

The attentive Garen quickly soon realized that some people were already walking out from the side of the area. The group was preparing to get on stage and Kong Xinxue was one of them. However, a man with a gentle face and holding a bunch of roses in his hands was following her from behind while mumbling incoherently.

Kong Xinxue seemed as though she was too busy to deal with him. She merely answered him occasionally instead.

“Oh… The pursuer has been discovered.” Garen was tinged with excitement suddenly.

The performance began quickly. As for classical music, Garen had previously learned how to play the violin in any case. Although his standard could only be considered as that of an above average amateur, he could still distinguish the good parts from the bad ones by hearing it.

Kong Xinxue’s violin sound took up a significant proportion of the performance and could be clearly heard. No wonder the others looked up to her immensely.

He listened until he was about to be lulled to sleep when the performance finally ended.

Garen stood up and walked to the front approaching Kong Xinxue hurriedly.

He was holding a single white rose that he bought from the flower girl beside him.

“This is for you, beautiful Miss Violinist.” Garen pushed through the crowd and reached the front before passing the white rose to her directly.

“Thank you…” Kong Xinxue’s gaze stirred when she recognized Garen. However, she plastered a dignified and graceful smile on her face before accepting the rose.

Both of them moved up near to each other quickly.

“Dad didn’t give you an allowance for you to just waste it on simply buying flowers!” said Kong Xinxue quietly so that only the both of them could hear her.

“What’s wrong with buying flowers for my own sister?” replied Garen innocently.

“If you want to listen, I’ll let you listen to this every day when I’m at home so don’t come here and cause trouble,” said Kong Xinxue while lowering her voice and furrowing her eyebrows.

“I only came here to observe what my beloved older sister does exactly every weekend when she goes out.” Garen continued to reply blamelessly.

“If you don’t want your cell phone number to appear on the flyers that advertise erectile dysfunction treatments on the telephone poles, you better not let me see you a second time.” A hint of maliciousness flashed across Kong Xinxue’s gaze. “Alright, your impotent self can get lost now. Don’t let me see you again.”

Garen was speechless.

However, he did not leave but continued following Kong Xinxue instead. The mischievous intentions in his heart intensified as he looked at the jet-black long silk dress that she wore.

He simply tore off the corner of a flyer from the side of the wall and crunched it into a ball before throwing it in front.

Plop.

The paper ball hit Kong Xinxue’s bottom precisely.

Kong Xinxue felt it and turned around to glare at Garen at the first instance. The warning overtones in her gaze were extremely intense.

It seemed as though she was being spoken to by a girl beside her. This forced Kong Xinxue who was about to react to continue maintaining the dignified smile on her face instead when she turned around to chat with the other party.

Plop.

Another paper ball hit her bottom accurately but discreetly once again.

The corners of Kong Xinxue’s eyes twitched before she turned around discreetly to give Garen a brief warning.

Garen smiled at her provocatively.

The third paper ball shot out furiously but was single-handedly blocked by Kong Xinxue. She pinched the paper ball and glared at Garen with a look that indicated that he was dead.

“Come and spank me, then.” Garen smiled beamingly.

“Hey.”

The figure of an imposing man clapped Garen’s shoulder from the back suddenly.

“Is something the matter?”

Garen turned around. Someone actually dared to disturb his entertaining, stress-relieving activity. This made his mood extremely unhappy.

The person standing behind him was a tall man in a black t-shirt who was more than one hundred and ninety meters tall. He was a skinhead and one look was enough to tell that he was not an ordinary character. Furthermore, it was unusual that the contours of the muscles in his entire body could be seen clearly.

The person glared at Garen while towering above.

“You actually came here just to harass Miss Xue. It seems to me that a little guy like you is probably tired of living, huh?”

Garen glanced at Kong Xinxue’s male pursuer who was standing behind the other man. It looked like this person had clearly only started pursuing her recently. Otherwise, it would be completely impossible for him to not know that he was Kong Xinxue’s younger brother.

“Let’s go for a walk.” The bald man grabbed Garen’s arm and walked out of the little door at the side. The male pursuer from before was following behind them.

The three of them walked out one after another before entering a little alley beside the gymnasium. There were tall walls on both sides of the alley. The area was extremely quiet as chatters and noises from the departing audience were slightly further away.

Garen allowed the other party to drag him while they were walking out and did not resist at all. He had coincidentally planned to teach these guys a proper lesson for disrupting his fun activity.

“Start doing the main thing.” The male pursuer behind him lit a cigarette and said softly.

“Alright.” The bald man was about to put his hand to the task. Garen raised his hand as well and prepared to teach his ‘little friends’.

“Wait!!” Kong Xinxue’s voice echoed behind the trio suddenly.

Her heaving chest was panting. She was still dressed in the long black silk dress from the performance and did not even have time to change out of her stilettos before she ran over hurriedly. It was obvious that she had seen them dragging Garen out.

“Lincoln! Who allowed you to come here and do this?!” There was an extremely stern expression on Kong Xinxue’s face when she admonished him coldly. “When did the time come for you to interfere with my business?”

“Xiaoxue…” The man who was smoking discarded his cigarette butt hurriedly and extinguished it by stomping on it once before smiling bashfully. “But I’m just doing this to protect your safety, right? Since this little guy was already harassing you in public, he wouldn’t know that some things are off limits unless I taught him a lesson.”

“Don’t call me Xiaoxue. After giving me such a horrible-sounding nickname presumptuously, do you really think that I’m unaware of the dirty thoughts that are actually swimming in your mind?” Kong Xinxue glared at the man coldly.

“Uhh… My pursuit of you is extremely pure, really!” Lincoln laughed hollowly a few times.

Shh!

Kong Xinxue held a pen and stabbed it into the wall beside Lincoln’s face violently.

“Look me in the eyes. Are you brave enough to repeat those words?”

“Xiaoxue…”

Bang!!

A knee collided against him fiercely before Lincoln bent his waist in pain. However, a delightful expression could be seen on Garen’s face clearly while he stood on the side.

“Ahh!” A scream of excitement that sounded more like a shriek of pain could be heard suddenly.

“…” Garen looked on as Kong Xinxue continuously beat Lincoln up furiously. The bald bodyguard stood at the side indifferently but had on a pained look indicating that he could not bear to look at the other man being beaten up. It was obvious that this was not his first time witnessing this scene.

“Sure enough… The friends of an abnormal person would surely be crazy as well…” Garen exhaled. One of these two people was a sadist while the other was a masochist. Hence, they were simply the most perfect match in history.

“Therefore… You should stop minding my business.” Kong Xinxue single-handedly grabbed Lincoln who was badly battered. “Also, you should remember that the weak, impotent, repulsive little brat there is my younger brother Kong Xiaofei. Don’t you dare trouble him again.”

Clap.

The pen in the wall broke.

“Younger brother?!”

Lincoln shivered before looking at Garen with a pained look on his whole face. His entire body had been assaulted until he looked like a fool. He finally understood why he was beaten up.

He had almost attacked his future brother-in-law. How dangerous!!

After trying his best to apologize, Lincoln and his bodyguard left the scene hurriedly. Now that it was clearly stated that Kong Xinxue was preparing to teach her younger brother a lesson, it was really unsuitable for them to be here. If his brother-in-law harbored resentment towards him in his heart after looking at his pitiful state here…

After waiting for both of them to leave, Kong Xinxue shifted her gaze towards Garen who was on the side. She became more furious immediately after seeing the beaming smile that was still apparent on Garen’s facial expression.

“You’re done for!” She said simply.

Garen blinked.

“?” What did that mean?

Whoosh.

A square photo appeared in Kong Xinxue’s hand before she threw it at Garen gently.

Garen caught the picture precisely. He glanced at it briefly before his face darkened immediately.

It was actually a nude photo of him, with his important parts pixelated!!!

In other words, it was secretly taken before Kong Xiaofei was about to shower and was unaware of the situation.

“Don’t worry, there are more here.” Kong Xinxue threw another photo out.

Garen caught it again.

It was even worse this time…

It was a high-definition, uncensored picture of Kong Xiaofei who was masturbating with an intoxicated expression on his face…

“…”

Garen lifted his neck somewhat stiffly.

“Stupid monkey.” Kong Xinxue covered her mouth while a loathsome look on her face. “I anticipated your every move each day. I know every inch of your whole body, including your private parts like your d*ck and b*lls, like the back of my hand. I really couldn’t care less if a disgusting bedbug like yourself died a thousand times. However, who asked you to become my younger brother?”

Chapter 1162: Joy 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was the first time, the very first time, that Garen regretted possessing the body of Kong Xiaofei who was such an important figure in the general trend timeline…

It was very obvious that these pictures were not taken recently but were secretly snapped when he was caught off guard previously.

However, in comparison to that, carrying her younger brother’s nude pictures with her was something that only an extremely perverted older sister would do, right?!

Large-scale composing techniques had yet to appear in this world. Furthermore, when you looked at the details, it was clear that all of these photos were authentic.

“How many more pictures like these are there?” Garen took two, full, deep breaths before looking at Kong Xinxue with a constipated look. Although he had already estimated the scariness of ‘lunatics’ with mental illnesses like split personality disorders long ago, he never expected that she would actually do such perverted things.

“There are as many as you think,” said Kong Xinxue confidently. “Perhaps you’re thinking of searching for all of the photos that I have now. You probably think that your male strength can override the initiatives and superiority of others. However, I need to remind you that a price will have to be paid for being impulsive…”

Garen’s emotions got more complicated.

He knew that it was impossible that Kong Xinxue would actually take these pictures out and stick them everywhere. After all, she needed her face and would not ruin her father’s face in the outside world either. However, now that this had happened, he had truly lost all of his own prestige in front of this girl now…

“I’m planning to turn your beautiful, youth-filled memories into a photo album and let our children see them when we’re older. What do you think of this idea?” The corners of Kong Xinxue’s mouth curled up into a devilish smile.

“…” How vile…

Garen was left speechless.

“Alright, today’s matter ends here. I still need to return and remove my makeup.” Kong Xinxue stretched. “Remember what I said.”

She turned around and walked towards the interior of the gymnasium.

A cold breeze suddenly blew behind her.

Pfoo… Bang!!

Unexpectedly, Kong Xiaofei pounced on her swiftly and actually pressed her against the wall tightly in one go.

It seemed like this brat has been training recently. His current outburst was clearly powerful. The actions to gain momentum that were initially properly prepared by Kong Xinxue collapsed instantly. Instead, her entire body was plastered against the wall tightly in a humiliating pose.

“The thing I hate the most is being threatened by others.” Garen sneered coldly twice. “Where are the photos? Take them out.” It was best to properly destroy embarrassing things like these as soon as possible.

Both of them stood against the wall closely, its icy surface causing Kong Xinxue to shiver unconsciously.

“I only have those two on me.” It seemed like she was not frightened at all. “Since you want them, what are you going to give me in exchange?”

“It would be best for you to just give them to me…” sneered Garen. “After all, you’re not the only one who knows how to take nude pictures…”

“Oh?” The corner of Kong Xinxue’s mouth turned upwards. “When did my impotent little brother learn how to take nude pictures of girls? Come on, I’ll leave it to you. As long as you’re brave enough to take them, I have no qualms about the quantity and types of poses!”

“…” Garen was speechless.

He glanced at her long black dress that lacked a single pocket. It was clearly impossible for her to keep any photos there.

“Come on!” Kong Xinxue puffed her bosom forward and nearly hit Garen’s chest with the tops of her breasts. “Come take pictures of me, I’m getting impatient.” A victorious smile gleamed across her face.

Apparently, testing his limits with a maniac was not one of his strong points…

Garen pondered sadly before releasing Kong Xinxue in the end. After pressing this beautiful woman against the wall and standing so close to her, his youthful, male body had stiffened shamefully. He would definitely face another round of perverted teasing if the girl discovered this abnormality.

“You’re just a little monkey that I used as a physiological research project for three days while I even studied your kinks intensively. Are you actually still brave enough to challenge me?” Kong Xinxue’s toxic words made it simply impossible for others to bear with her.

“…your perverted self must be very bored for you to research your own brother’s kinks and even use a surveillance camera to take these pictures secretly?!” He really wanted to shout those words. However, when he remembered that she still had an advantage in her hands, he merely suppressed these words in his stomach.

“Alright, alright, you’ve won.” Garen lamented helplessly.

“Now you’re being a good boy.” Kong Xinxue caressed Garen’s face. “Okay, Big Sis has to go remove her makeup now. You need to be obedient, go home and sleep, understood?”

“…”

“Alright, see you at home.” Kong Xinxue smiled brightly while straightening out her skirt. She entered the gym and disappeared behind the door quickly.

Garen rubbed his chin and felt the desire to tail Kong Xinxue. Although he would only be meddling in her business, the joy of life would follow in the end.

However, the most critical issue now was to find the original copies of these nude photos first…

He strode out of the alley.

In comparison to his previous life of endlessly seeking power, a life like this was occasionally joyful as well. This managed to indescribably improve his mood greatly.

*********************

A week passed.

Garen used various measures to finally successfully solve the nude photos issue. Rather than saying it was solved, all he had to do was to pull open Kong Xinxue’s locked drawer to uncover a drawer full of densely packed, nude photos of him…

Garen’s face literally turned green when he found the drawer.

Fortunately, he managed to find the original copies of these photos. He sighed in relief resolutely after destroying all of these properly.

Nonetheless, he still needed to keep his guard up against his crazy sister. A meticulous person like her would never put all of her eggs in one basket. She would definitely have other records. Thus, it was better for him not to provoke her if possible.

Peace was restored in his life once again. Garen did not provoke his sister while she quietly resumed her role as the beautiful violinist.

Receiving a large sum of money, the Kong household was able to quickly move into a larger house located in a high-end community in the central downtown area. They even bought two high-quality cars that truly resembled streamlined race cars from the outside.

Their quality of life improved greatly as well. Their allowances were increased while their apparel was updated to the latest fashion.

Meanwhile, Garen’s application to join the school’s Unrestricted Combat Department was successful as well. He began his safe blade-wielding plan.

There were special rules in the Unrestricted Combat Department. They were allowed to wear the various accessories that were used for practice at most times. This was part of the special treatment that was given to them along with their credentials. This was also the main reason why No. 3 High School was weakest academically yet also the strongest sports school in Lily of the Valley. Various students with special talents and martial arts practitioners were specially invited to enroll there because what good would it be if these students merely studied? They focused most of their energy in their training while using their remaining bits of vigor to study. Those who could get good grades were geniuses.

******************

Inside the bright and spacious main combat classroom, numerous rows of fluorescent lamp tubes hung tightly to each other from the white ceiling above. The nameplates of each divisional branch’s members in the Unrestricted Combat Department hung above the headquarters’ main door.

Tables were packed tightly inside the classroom. Several members of the divisional branches within the group were busy conducting the formalities with the new students who were either specially recruited or had just applied. Others were explaining certain matters.

Garen sat at the table at the Saber Art Dojo Department. He was bored as one of his hand was supporting his face. His lazy manner made it impossible for people to not want to beat him up in one look. He had completely relaxed after coming to this world. He was enjoying life, taking and experiencing things slowly.

After joining the Unrestricted Combat Department’s Saber Art Dojo, he now possessed his own wooden saber as well. However, he was disappointed because there were only a few martial arts hobbyists in the Saber Art Dojo. The most skillful one was merely a showy individual who had only practiced for a few years. This person would be completely ineffective during actual combat.

He merely had to get rid of the supposed strongest powerhouse within a few rallies before he sat properly at the seat of the top member.

However, no one came over to apply to the Saber Art Dojo because of Garen’s lazy, sleepy state.

Only one person joined after more than half a day. Frankly, the other cold steel branches were suffering similarly. Some of them were even forced to merge together because their membership registration was extremely low.

Two people sat behind Garen. They consisted of a handsome young man and a beautiful girl whom Garen had picked out from the Saber Art Dojo to attract new members to join his department. However, since there were only a total of fifteen people in the Saber Art Dojo, they were merely of that caliber despite being specially selected…

“We want to join the Saber Art Dojo. Please add us to the name list.” Suddenly, a resounding voice roused Garen from his drowsiness.

“Someone wants to join?” The man at the side whom Garen had named as Saber Two smiled radiantly and stood up to greet hurriedly.

The girl who was known as Saber Three stood up to greet another female student as well.

The boy and girl who were standing in front of the Saber Art Dojo’s table looked extremely arrogant. They were dressed trendily and their dressing was not low-grade items. They were obviously from upper-middle-class family backgrounds.

Through the conversation, both of them quickly revealed that someone had specially introduced the Saber Art Dojo to them and asked them to join it. They had clearly rushed here for Garen’s sake.

Through their speech, Garen managed to guess the person who had sent them quickly.

“Lincoln.”

When he saw both of them agreeing implicitly, Garen was too lazy to concern himself with this.

“From today onwards, you will be Saber One and you will be Saber Two. The rest of you can arrange yourselves until the end,” he said while pointing at the young man and woman who had arrived recently.

He decided to refer to them like this simply so that he could manage them easily. Moreover, he was too lazy to remember the names of these rookies.

“…don’t we need to introduce ourselves?” said the new male student called Saber One helplessly. Although he had merely come here for fun with his younger sister, wasn’t it too sloppy to not even do a simple task like asking for their names?

“Names aren’t important. It’s fine as long as they’re easy to remember,” answered Garen simply. “Alright, you guys are the only recruits for this week so pack up.” It would be impossible for him not to tell that the person who arrived had a foundation in combat already. Moreover, he had at least a few years’ worth of actual combat experience. These were things that could be determined through observing his every move including the way he stood or walked.

These two people pushed the original Saber One and Saber Two down right after they arrived. However, the first two people had good temperaments and merely shrugged their shoulders to indicate that it was fine.

The Saber Art Dojo team tidied and cleared the tables quickly before the group of five left the headquarters.

“Now, everyone is free to proceed with their own activities now.” Garen decisively let them go on a break.

“Great Saber, what time should we assemble?” asked ex-Saber One helplessly.

“Everyone can do as they please.” Garen waved his hand. “Don’t come looking for me unless there’s a reason.” He walked away, leaving an unrestrained figure behind before disappearing past the school gates.

“…”

The group could only gaze at him in silence. At this moment, everyone including the new Saber One and Saber Two regarded him as an incomparable pain in the ass.

Chapter 1163: Ambushed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was indifferent towards this person named Lincoln who had forced his way into the lives of the members of the Kong household unexpectedly. However, it was now apparent that there was almost no one who could stand Kong Xinxue. After spending more time with her and discovering the truth gradually, Lincoln’s pursuit of Kong Xinxue turned into fear quickly. In the end, he merely respected her from afar and became good friends with Garen instead.

This fellow resembled a strapping, two-faced person who was also the spoiled son of a wealthy nobleman. In reality, he was merely an average university student who was still studying now. His only distinguishing feature was that his appearance seemed more mature…

“Uncle, your glasses are really cool. Where did you buy them?” A twenty-something-year-old youth moved closer and asked him this question on the public bus.

Lincoln’s face remained expressionless. Standing beside him, Garen covered his mouth and laughed wildly.

“I bought it online…” He glanced at Garen and answered the youth quietly and helplessly in a deep voice.

At this moment, an old woman stuffed herself into the bus. She seemed to have some physical disabilities. An eighty-something-year-old elder man who was standing beside Lincoln glanced at him.

“Bro, you should give your seat to the old lady. We can stand here together.”

Bro!!!!

An old man who was more than eighty years old had just called him ‘bro’!!!

These words were like a sudden bolt of thunder in the sky, striking Lincoln violently burning him into crisps.

He stood up and gave his seat to the old woman with a stupefied expression. As the other party thanked him, he walked over and stood with Garen. The seat that he had previously taken was actually reserved for those with special needs.

“Do you now know why I don’t like taking the public bus?” Lincoln exhaled deeply while speaking softly.

“Got it…” Garen smiled while nodding. “Frankly, when you were pursuing my sister before this, I assumed that you were a successful, wealthy, middle-aged man who was planning to take care of her.”

“Sigh… It hurts when you mention that.” Lincoln let out a long, drawn-out sigh. “You can endure your sister on your own… I don’t think that anyone can stand her other than you.”

Garen shook his head silently and was about to speak.

Screech!!!

The entire bus lurched forward suddenly as it braked violently. The vehicle rushed a few meters further because of the inertia.

“Are you trying to kill himself! Lunatic!! Find other ways to die instead of running to the middle of the road to hitchhike!!” The driver cursed brazenly and was somewhat clearly flustered by the incident. His forehead was drenched in sweat as he was shocked.

The sudden forward lurch and brake movement caused the bus passengers to grumble.

The incident made Garen lost interest in the things that he was about to say. Instead, he lowered his head and looked forward through the gap between the people.

He saw a person standing at the front of the vehicle. It was a man with a crew cut and a long scar on his face. He was also very tall and muscular. When Garen was about to look at him closely, the person left the front of the bus quickly and walked into a side alley before disappearing completely.

Snapping out of it, Garen noticed that Lincoln’s expression seemed slightly abnormal. Lincoln’s head was lowered and he was looking at his right hand. No one knew what he was thinking about.

“Hey.” Garen reached his hand out and waved it in front of Lincoln’s eyes.

Both of them had already decided to play pool together today but for some reason, Lincoln looked like he was breaking out in cold sweat now.

“What’s up?” Lincoln responded finally.

“You seemed distracted earlier,” said Garen suspiciously.

“Did I?” Lincoln laughed. “Nothing’s wrong. I merely thought of something suddenly just now. I need to return slightly earlier so I might not be able to play pool with you.”

“Your main matters are more important. We can play pool any other day,” said Garen casually as he noticed that Lincoln had worries on his mind.

“Alright, I’ll be getting off first to go back and handle some matters. You can play with the boss there instead.” It was obvious that Lincoln was somewhat preoccupied now.

“Okay, go then.”

Lincoln got off at the next stop. Garen watched as he hailed a cab and rushed back.

“Looks like he has some urgent matters,” Garen looked on pensively while sensing Lincoln’s anxiety. Unfortunately, it was impossible for him to see the external appearances of the Four Great Cornerstones because they were similarly protected by Soul Energy as well. Moreover, he could not detect the Soul Energy Auras of the four individuals after possessing this new body.

“Could it be that the general trends have started?” An assumption flashed across Garen’s mind.

He got off the bus quickly as well before calling a cab and rushing back.

*********************

A row of abandoned factory buildings in the outskirts

Outside a grey building, a little black sedan drove over quickly from afar.

Stopping at the factory building’s doorway, the car door opened.

A muscular and imposing man in sunglasses got down from the car before turning around to drag a woman out.

“Get out.” The man’s voice was extremely cold and he was clearly somewhat impatient.

Fortunately, the young woman listened obediently and did not have any intentions of resisting when she got down from the car.

It was Kong Xinxue who was initially supposed to go to the airport to get on a plane to participate in a competition. She was dressed in a long, white dress, black silk stockings, and high-heeled shoes. It seemed like she was dragged off when she was getting ready to perform.

“Who were you calling on the phone earlier?” asked Kong Xinxue calmly. “They didn’t sound like my family members.”

The man ignored her and pulled her towards a narrow staircase instead. The car behind him drove away quickly, leaving a long, tire tread mark in the dirt ground.

After entering the little building, the man spread open a few pieces of newspaper that he had brought before sitting down with his legs crossed.

“Why did you kidnap me? I don’t think you look like a pervert or someone who needs money.” Kong Xinxue looked out the window. There seemed to be no other accomplices and only him instead.

“That car was going really fast. Wouldn’t the driver worried about being fined with a traffic ticket?”

“…”

“How far is this place from the city? How are we going to get lunch?” It did not seem like Kong Xinxue had been kidnapped at all.

“…”

She glanced at the bored man who was closing his eyes and resting.

“Do you know the five ways of writing the box-shaped Chinese character ‘hui’ which means ‘to return’?” ^1

“…” The man widened his eyes and glared at her grudgingly. “Keep yapping and I’ll kill you!” he said furiously.

It seemed as if these words had frightened Kong Xinxue.

She could actually feel this man’s murderous intent. It was bare and completely unconcealed which made her shivered slightly. Despite her crazy tendencies, she was merely a young woman who had yet to even turn twenty-one years old in the end. After being captured by this man and taken here because she was unable to fight back, she then realized that something was amiss. Now that she could clearly sense the other party’s murderous intentions, large patches of goosebumps rose throughout Kong Xinxue’s entire body suddenly.

She bit down on her lips and swallowed her spit before sitting on the newspapers quietly.

The small building became quiet for a while again.

“You’re a good person.” Kong Xinxue opened her mouth yet again.

“?” The man was somewhat confused. He never expected that his victim would actually regard him as a good person.

“After kidnapping such a beautiful girl like myself, most people would definitely force themselves on me even if it wasn’t their first thought. But you’re different.” Kong Xinxue combed through her long red hair vainly.

“…”

“Do you have any brothers or sisters?”

“They’re dead.”

“What about your parents?”

“Dead.”

“Other relatives?”

“All dead…” The man turned silent and lowered his head before taking a multi-purpose army knife out and drawing random lines on the ground with it.

Kong Xinxue sighed dejectedly.

“Actually… I had a younger brother too but he died… My father died as well…”

She met the man’s gaze directly and noticed a sympathetic response in his eyes.

“That was a joke,” she added.

Screech.

The knife that the man was dragging across the ground stopped suddenly when he drew a deep scratch violently.

“…stop babbling!” He glared at Kong Xinxue furiously. He felt like she was constantly testing and challenging his patience.

The sound of an arriving car could be heard outside suddenly.

“Someone’s here,” said Kong Xinxue softly. “Should we hide?” She looked at the man.

“…”

The man vaguely felt as if the roles had been reversed.

He stood up and took out a sharp, black three-edged army knife from his thigh. He strode out and went down the stairs.

A little while later, a few painful screams could be heard from below. There were no more noises after that. The man strode back up the stairs quickly again. He took a cell phone out and made a phone call.

Beep…

The phone call was connected.

“Hey?” It was a man’s voice. Kong Xinxue recognized it as Lincoln’s voice at the very first instance!

“I’ll only wait for half an hour. If you don’t come after that, you will only see your girlfriend’s corpse,” said the man coldly. “Remember, my name is Silver Chain.”

“Where’s Big Sister Xue?! What are you planning to do exactly?!” Before Lincoln could finish his sentence, the other man disconnected the phone call.

“Actually…” said Kong Xinxue softly in a voice that was somewhat timid. “You might have kidnapped the wrong person… Him and I don’t have the relationship that you’re thinking of…”

Bang.

The man named Silver Chain dodged behind her precisely and knocked Kong Xinxue on the neck with a karate chop.

Kong Xinxue’s eyes rolled to the back of her head and passed out. The man held her and placed her down gently on the newspapers beside him. Once Silver Chain had completed everything, he returned to his original spot, using his little knife to scratch lines across the ground quietly.

The entire little building returned to a state of complete calmness.

*******************

In the evening, the setting sun ducked even lower beyond the horizon.

Lincoln’s car finally appeared on the lane in front of the little building. There was a screeching noise as the car braked frantically before he jumped out from the vehicle in his white sportswear.

“F*ck… What happened exactly?!” He could not help but curse.

He was living his normal daily life initially before he heard someone speaking to him suddenly while he was inside the bus. The noise was clearly right beside his ear but no one around him including Xiaofei could hear it.

The occurrence of a single spine-chilling incident like this would have been enough. He had never expected that the voice would also tell him that Kong Xinxue was kidnapped! He could only come to this place to save her on his own. He had to do it alone without informing anyone else.

If they noticed that other people had arrived to help or the police had come, Kong Xinxue’s survival would not be certain.

After verifying that Big Sister Xue had really been kidnapped, he rushed over in burning anxiety.

Bang!

Lincoln’s expression relaxed after he slammed the door close. He observed his surroundings carefully before the various lessons that were taught to him by his father who had disappeared when he was younger now floated back up in his mind.

He strode forward towards the little building in the abandoned factory area.

*******************

“Challenge?”

Garen stood inside the Saber Art Dojo’s interior classroom and looked at the muscular young woman before him who was carrying a wooden stick that was used in martial arts on her shoulder. The flesh on her body weighed at least 100 kilograms ^2 . He could tell with one look that she was the strong type.

“Yes, I felt that there was no need for your Saber Art Dojo to continue anymore. Since there aren’t any activities planned throughout the days, I thought that you should merge with my Staff Art Society instead.” ^3 This girl had introduced herself to him before but Garen had forgotten her name. Instead, he only remembered her by her nickname ‘Wild Boar’.

“You’re… Wild Boar, right?” said Garen helplessly. “You called me out for a combat challenge during one of my rare off-duty weekends? Have you fought against the other members of my Saber Art Dojo?”

Wild Boar nodded before saying, “You’re the only one left.”

Chapter 1164: Ambushed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

From the corner of his eye, Garen glanced at the numerous Saber Art Dojo members who were grimacing in pain. Although he already knew from the start that these people were really weak, he never anticipated that they would be so bad to this extent. This was truly beyond his expectations.

Frankly, he was initially preparing to trail Lincoln and see what was going on exactly. However, the situation over here seemed more urgent hence he decided to come here first.

Even though this organization’s sole purpose was to allow him to practice legitimate saber skills, he would not allow anyone to simply snatch his position as the leader and force him to become their subordinate instead.

“Then you should attack.”

He noticed that a crowd of leaders from various branches was already standing outside the doors and windows, looking as if they were about to watch a show.

The others pulled back quickly and moved aside to leave an empty space for the two people.

“Perhaps we should do it instead.” A voice squeezed past from the other side of the door suddenly.

Two more people walked in. They were the newly appointed Saber One and Saber Two who were also the siblings recommended by Lincoln. Neither of them was around in the department previously but once they had heard of this news, they worried that it would be difficult to explain the incident to Big Brother Lincoln if their other boss here was injured in the fight. Hence, they rushed over quickly and prepared themselves to take over the fight.

“You guys came to do this?” Garen grasped the hilt of the saber at his waist. He had imitated the katana to smith a supposed single-edged saber. The body of a saber like this was advantageous when used for chopping because it was incomparably sharp. However, the drawback was that it was not flexible enough. Nonetheless, it was very suitable for his current Saber Art. Weapons like these that resembled sabers but were actually single-edged swords were unanimously well-received by everyone in the Saber Art Dojo quickly.

“That’s good. Coincidentally, I have some matters to attend to now so you guys can stand in for me. No problem, right?” Garen patted the shoulders of both people.

“This guy…” Saber One and Saber Two were completely speechless. By looking at his manner, they had initially assumed that he would reject them frankly and start the fight immediately. In the end…

“Is he merely getting out of an embarrassing situation because he knows that his opponent has the upper hand and he can’t defeat them?” Saber One pondered silently. However, he was still forced to say the necessary formalities.

“Great Saber, you can leave without worrying because you have us here.”

“I’ll leave this to you then,” Garen nodded earnestly. He took a few long strides and rushed out of the classroom door before suddenly recalling a possibility. What if Lincoln was one of the supposed Four Great Cornerstones? This was not impossible.

Pfoo!

Suddenly, a little object flew towards his face quickly. Some unknown person had shushed at him intentionally. They were obviously extremely disdainful towards his actions that indicated cold feet.

Clang!

His wooden saber moved on its own calmly and hit the front of the little object immediately before cutting it in half like a block of tofu.

There was a brief whooshing noise before a faint ray of light that resembled a red thread appeared when his reddish-brown wooden saber sliced through it. The people around him could only see the red light flashed faintly while Garen’s saber still remained in the sheath on his waist. It seemed as though he had not moved his saber at all. He continued rushing out of the classroom and running into the faraway distance as if nothing had happened.

The object fell to the ground. It was actually a black eraser that was sliced cleanly into two halves by the saber.

Oh!!!!

A crowd of leaders from the Unrestricted Combat Department burst into an uproar suddenly.

“Such fast sword strokes!” praised the Head Minister while standing up. “That was definitely Saber Art that was trained through actual combat. The drawing and sheathing of his saber were almost instinctual. Amazing!!”

Every single leader that possessed proper judgment could naturally see the terrifying nature of his saber, including Saber One and Saber Two. Both of them looked at each other, before turning to gaze at Wild Boar who was on the opposite side.

This person was also dumbfounded before she finally reacted and scratched her head.

“We don’t need to fight anymore. Saber Art and Staff Art have the same roots. I think that it would be better if my Saber Art Society merged with your Saber Art Department,” said Wild Boar readily, throwing her stick away.

“…”

In the end, all of them were merely students who did not value victory or defeat highly.

After all, the Unrestricted Combat Department’s various branches were always either coming into being or merging with one another messily. Incidents like these were common occurrences.

“Is there anyone else who wants to swap pointers?” Saber One stood forward and yelled.

*******************

Other matters were still on Garen’s mind after he exited the classroom. He had no time to pay attention to the surprised gasps behind him. He hurriedly made a phone call to inquire about Lincoln’s whereabouts. Strangely enough, no one knew where he had gone to now.

However, he had yet to walk much further away before he heard the sound of commotion echoing from inside the Saber Art Dojo behind him. Soon after that, Saber One and Saber Two rushed out frantically.

Once they had exited the school gates, they hailed a cab and traveled into the distance.

Garen was standing in a slightly remote area. Moreover, the two other people were in anxious states and did not notice him when they passed by. Nonetheless, this was still very strange.

He remembered suddenly that both of them were introduced to him by Lincoln. Hence, they would probably be aware of some news that was related to him. When he thought of this, Garen called a cab hurriedly and followed them.

The car drove speedily towards another remote place. Garen asked the driver to follow them from behind at a reasonable distance that was neither too far nor too near. Perhaps the impatient feelings that the two people in front were experiencing had caused their anxiety to increase as well. Thus, neither of them had discovered this additional car that was tailing them.

Once they had exited the city area, the cab quickly stopped in front of a small building in an area that was filled with abandoned factory workshops.

Saber One and Saber Two got down from the car swiftly and rushed towards the factory workshop. Before the first cab could even turn the corner, Garen had caught up to them already.

He looked at the small building from afar. Garen had yet to alight from the car before he saw the other two people carrying Lincoln out from the building. His older sister Kong Xinxue was next to them as well. They seemed to be fairly messed up with blood traces on them.

“Oh… Could it be that the general trends have started?” Garen rubbed his chin. It looked like he was one step too late because it seemed like the incident had ended by now. He glanced at the four people as if this was not a big deal.

“Mister, please rush back to the city quickly. These four people don’t seem like decent individuals and I don’t want to provoke them,” said Garen hurriedly.

“You have a point.” The driver turned and sped off towards the city decisively. “Really, the ways of the world have become more chaotic. It’s a good thing that you were here to remind me, bro. Otherwise, we wouldn’t be able to shake off these troubles if we had really encountered them.” The driver started to share stories on a few uncommon murder cases that he had previously witnessed. He sounded perpetually sorrowful.

Garen merely smiled but did not reply because his thoughts were still somewhere else.

*********************

“Four Directional Winds!”

Ring!!

Four rays of white light illuminated every single side around Garen’s body simultaneously. Four wooden pillars were chopped in half at the same time respectively before they slid down slowly.

Wow…!

Suddenly, the members of the Saber Art Dojo clapped vigorously with feverish looks on their faces.

The entire main classroom of the Saber Art Dojo was bustling with excitement.

Garen sheathed his saber slowly.

“These are all of the contents. Your final goal is to learn this basic delicate saber move that I used earlier.”

More than two months had passed since the sudden incident previously. Unconsciously, Garen had now obtained the position of the Head Minister of the Unrestricted Combat Department despite being uninterested. The previous Minister unashamedly forced the position unto him, leaving him no other choice. Fortunately, this position allowed him to skip classes legitimately and this satisfied him greatly.

Since he was now assigned to this position, he was naturally forced to become slightly more responsible. A large group of people would stare at him with hopeful gazes every day while the previous Head Minister had become his eagerly attentive ‘little brother’.

It would be rude if Garen had not displayed some of his skills to allow the others to learn and reach their goals.

Up until now, his physical fitness had improved once again. He had basically achieved more than twofold of an average person’s fitness level now. Since he was always using the Energy Machine Imprint’s help to train the various aspects of his physical qualities, it was unlikely that it would not improve.

Thus, he simply chose a few people from the group as examples for close range teaching. After that, he allowed them to guide the others.

The people that were selected included Saber One, Saber Two, Wild Boar, and the previous Head Minister.

“Alright. Step forward, Saber One. We’ll use the usual simulated attack routine.” Garen looked at Saber One listlessly.

“Head Minister Great Saber, could you call me by my name?” Saber One stood up helplessly.

“You’ve already learned the basic saber skills and grasped them quickly as well. It’s time for you to continue your actual combat training now. Come, attack me.”

Garen held the hilt of the saber in one hand. After possessing this body for such a long time, his current figure was far beyond his initially average and feeble state. Instead, he became sturdier and more muscular now. He rolled up his sleeve single-handedly and exposed the contours of his muscles underneath his white shirt. His current self-was like an abnormally sharp blade.

When he compared himself to Saber One who was standing on the opposite side of him, Garen’s body was clearly two sizes larger. When he looked at him directly, Saber One sensed a bout of pressure that was moving towards his face suddenly.

Hup!

His movements were skilled. He drew the saber and swung it towards the other party. He was using the most basic slaying techniques.

Clang!

The edge of the saber was a real blade. It was instantly blocked by the back of Garen’s saber that remained there steadily without quivering at all.

“Left!!”

Saber One swung his blade towards the left and made another clanging noise. However, he could not see how Garen had managed to block it at all.

“Another few more rounds,” said Garen calmly.

Suddenly, a few more people leaped up on the side, including Saber Two and Wild Boar.

There were five people in total who were simultaneously attacking Garen from all four directions now.

Clang clang clang clang…

All the blades fell two meters away from Garen’s body after they were blocked. Despite how hard the five people tried, none of them could advance to the next step.

This type of Saber Art was simple enough to make people gasp in amazement.

Garen could only see twinkling stars in the space around him that lit up occasionally. He could not see anything else.

“Alright, sheathe your sabers!” Garen commanded.

Everyone kept their sabers quickly and stuck them back in their sheaths at different times. All of them were panting in exhaustion. Garen stood in the center and remained indifferent.

“His physical strength is simply insane!” Saber Two could not help but whisper softly to her older brother on the side.

Saber One smiled bitterly. It was not a big deal for a girl like his little sister to say something like that. However, he was sure that Garen’s ear had definitely twitched earlier. Definitely! It was highly likely that he had heard that…

He looked at Garen’s arms that were almost twice as broad as his own. They were almost the size of an average person’s upper thigh. Garen and the guy from earlier were both similar deviants…

He unconsciously recalled that guy named Silver Chain whom he had encountered previously… Despite activating a certain skill, he had almost died at the hands of that person nonetheless.

“That’s all for today. Everyone is dismissed,” said Garen indifferently. He took his clothes and water bottle before leaving at once. He was completely unconcerned because everything else was the responsibility of the previous Head Minister.

Some people who refused to accept this ended up picking a quarrel with about a dozen other people. However, everything calmed down again after they were beaten up and bruised to the point where they were unrecognizable.

While watching Garen leave swiftly, Saber One told his younger sister to go home with him. The sky outside was getting slightly darker now.

“Let’s go, Xiaojie.”

“Okay.”

The house that they stayed in was not far from here. Their journey home from school only required a ten-minute walk because it was very near.

After exiting the Unrestricted Combat Department, both of them walked side by side past the stream of scattered students. They left the school gates before passing through an intersection.

They continued walking forward past the edges of a shopping street. This was the road that they frequently used to go home.

The road seemed somewhat calmer today as there were only a few pedestrians. However, it seemed to be too quiet.

Chapter 1165: Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It seemed like several electric poles on the street were malfunctioning. Some of them were blinking while the others turned dim occasionally. A few pedestrians walked past, a single car would drive by sometimes.

Both Saber One and Saber Two wore their blue and white school uniforms like regular students and walked home carrying their backpacks.

Saber One’s real name was Yuria. He was a fair-skinned cheerful youth with a beaming smile. Meanwhile, Saber Two’s name was Yurijie. Her hair was tied in two separate ponytails and she had features that were very similar to Saber One’s appearance. The only difference was that her skin was smoother and she was always quiet. She was inseparable from Yuria.

Both of them walked towards a street corner. There was a bar near the corner where the sound of quiet music echoed from inside while red light radiated out from there as well. A row of characters were etched beside the door. However, they were distorted which made it impossible to distinguish the words on it.

“How do you think the Head Minister managed to learn those skills? I found them insanely powerful. I don’t think I could necessarily beat him single-handedly.” Saber One Yuria was holding his cellphone and replying a text message from his friend when he randomly asked his younger sister.

“Who knows,” Saber Two was currently using her phone to take a selfie and preparing to send it to her circle of friends. She pouted while puffing out her cheeks to look cute.

“He was able to achieve strength of such a powerful degree despite being so young. I wonder what he’s like during actual combat?” asked Saber One listlessly.

“Actual combat?” Yurijie put her phone down and glanced at her older brother. “Are you still thinking about the previous incident?”

“Don’t tell me that you’ve forgotten?” Yuria asked a question in reply. “That man captured Big Sister Xue and then led Big Brother Lincoln out even though I was his true goal in the end,” he tugged at his hair. “I was targeted by this deviant for no reason. Sure enough, I can feel a great pressure…”

“Let’s make a police report,” Yurijie suggested.

“Would it even be useful? I’ve reported twice.” Yuria rolled his eyes. “Don’t tell me that I should really tell the cops that we’re actually not normal people and for the sake of world peace, an organization called Vulture has targeted us. Moreover, they want to capture and perform experiments on us? Do you think that the police would really believe nonsense like this?”

“That’s indeed a problem…” Yurijie nodded solemnly. “Then… why not find someone to help you instead?”

“Who could we look for? Please, actual combat and tournaments are two different matters. How many people out there have experienced actual combat in this day and age?” said Yuria helplessly.

“We could pay them and hire some mercenaries or something.”

“…you’ve read too many novels…” Yuria was speechless. “Moreover, how would we get access to channels like that?”

“Then what do you think we should do? We can’t just wait for them to ambush us again in the end, right?” Yurijie shrugged.

“What else can we do?” Yuria rubbed his chin. “Think about it, what would happen if our uncle hadn’t anticipated this day much earlier and allowed us to train with Big Brother Lincoln ever since we were little. The hunting skills that we learned from capturing wild boars and foxes were directly used in this aspect no matter how you look at it…”

“When you put it that way, it actually seems pretty accurate.” Yurijie’s mind had always been duller.

Both of them chatted while turning past a corner and walking into a byway alley. This was a shortcut that led directly to their house. They had walked through it countless times and had become completely familiar with it much earlier on.

However, something happened when they had just turned into the alley.

“Watch out!”

Yuria pulled his younger sister away suddenly to avoid an object that flew at them from the sky.

Shh!

That dark object penetrated the wall beside them quickly and actually sank into the depths of it.

Both of them were frightened to the point where their entire bodies were covered in cold sweat. When they looked at it closely, they noticed that it was a black lethal metal weapon that resembled an animal’s claw.

That lethal weapon had three fingers that penetrated the cement wall directly. It hooked itself deeply inside, digging out pieces of cement and plaster.

“Who was that?!” Yuria’s guard instantly rose to the highest level. He widened his eyes and stared closely at the dark spot in front of the alley.

Within the darkness, a silhouette that was two meters tall walked closer towards them gradually before revealing itself.

The figure actually belonged to a man whose entire body was wrapped in thick layers of clothes. He resembled a heavily wounded person who had just rushed out of the hospital. His entire body appeared swollen but was also enormous and sturdy at the same time. This gave off a cumbersome feeling.

The man’s face was the only part of him that was exposed. However, it caused Yuria’s entire body to stiffen instantly.

“Yuria, I let you escape the last time but that definitely won’t happen again this time…” The man’s voice was deep and rigid. It appeared that he was not human.

He moved one of his hands in a grabbing motion before numerous silver chains came crashing down. They shook and reflected faint silver light.

“Silver Chain…” Yuria’s expression turned grave immediately.

“You need to leave first.” He said to his sister softly.

“I can’t…” Beads of sweat trickled down Yurijie’s sideburns faintly. “There are people guarding the front and back of this place. I can sense the reflected light from the muzzle of a gun!”

“This is troublesome…” Yuria’s heart dropped.

Silver Chain took one step forward.

“This is merely a test…”

Whoosh!

His entire body charged forward. His imposing body was actually as agile as a wild wolf.

************************

Several minutes later, Saber One and Saber Two were both lying beside the wall on separate sides of the alley. Bright red blood snaked down their bodies and flowed down to form two red lines that could be seen clearly.

A metallic bloody scent wafted through the entire alley.

“Is this the strength of a Savior?” Silver Chain appeared colder than the last time. Neither of his two hands resembled human palms anymore. They had fully transformed into mechanical claws that twinkled with cold pallid light in the dark.

“Rumor has it that you can borrow the powers of others?”

Silver Chain walked towards Yuria who was lying on the floor.

“You’re too weak indeed. Legend has it that the strongest Savior can borrow the strength of a hundred men and achieve a terrifying, endless realm.”

Bang.

He walked beside Yuria and kicked him brutally once. The kick made a banging noise and caused Yuria to cough up a mouthful of blood violently.

“You, however, can only borrow the strength of less than three people, right? That’s really pitiful…”

“Don’t touch my brother!!” Yelled Yurijie who was not far away. She had never expected that Silver Chain, whose hands they barely managed to chop off, would actually become so strong within a short period of time that he was simply on another level now.

Never in her wildest dreams would she have imagined that her brother would collapse so easily after merely a few short clashes.

Her brother was famous for his physical strength and could even borrow the strength of others. However, he was defeated so easily now!! This was unbelievable!

“If you want to fight… then fight me!” She supported her body tenaciously despite the fact that her lower abdomen was covered in blood that trickled downwards constantly.

Silver Chain turned his head before looking at Yurijie somewhat impatiently.

“Those who aren’t Saviors are completely worthless to us.”

He left Yuria’s side and walked towards Yurijie instead.

“Do you want me to kill you?”

Yurijie’s pupils constricted instantly. Despite the various types of training that she had undergone and the two deadly battles that she had experienced previously, she could still feel herself shivering when she was truly faced with death. Her heart compressed and tightened as well. She felt as if she was faintly gasping for air too.

“Don’t touch my sister!!” Yuria’s voice echoed behind them.

Silver Chain bared his teeth and smiled suddenly as he was about to speak.

Suddenly, a faint noise could be heard from the electric earpiece that he wore. He stopped in his tracks as if he was listening to something.

“Are you joking? Retreat?! Hahaha…” Silver Chain pinched something in one handful and smashed it abruptly before simply throwing it on the ground. “Both of my arms were broken and I almost died at the hands of these two disgusting little monsters. This is truly the best chance for me to take revenge but you’re actually asking me to retreat instead?!”

Bang!

A bullet hole appeared directly on the ground beside his feet suddenly.

“Huh?” Silver Chain lifted his head and looked in the direction of the marksman who was concealed outside the alley.

“You…are threatening me?”

There was a brief whooshing noise before he fled into the darkness like a large wolf in the dusky night.

Ahh!

A painful cry could be heard far away suddenly. Yuria and his sister took this opportunity to try their best to crawl to each other frantically.

“Go quickly! That guy isn’t human anymore. Half of his body has been fully modified into a machine! I couldn’t even move him at all when we were fighting!” said Yuria urgently. “Go look for Big Brother Lincoln quickly! Don’t make a police report!”

He supported Yurijie determinedly but his sister’s body seemed completely lifeless already. She barely stood up, and the wound on her abdomen burst open and blood began flowing out quickly.

Plop.

Both of them collapsed on the ground again. They could not get up again no matter how much they crawled this time.

“Eh? What are you two doing here? Having a forbidden incestous relationship between siblings?” A bored voice echoed through the entrance of the alley suddenly.

“Leader!””Head Minister!!”

When they saw Kong Xiaofei at the entrance of the alley, both of the people on the ground were instantly moved to the point where their eyes were brimming with tears.

They were finally saved!!

However, Yuria was suddenly filled with panic again when he remembered the current situation.

“Head Minister, help me call my cousin quickly!! This place is very dangerous so you should hurry up and leave!!”

“Saber One and Saber Two?” Garen walked into the alley with his eyebrows furrowed. He sniffed around before detecting the scent of something that was amiss.

“This is… the smell of blood…”

His expression stiffened quickly. He glanced at the brother and sister on the floor with worried looks on their faces. He was about to speak before he turned his head suddenly and looked at the other deep part of the alley.

“There’s a scoundrel who is hiding in the alley sneakily.” Garen’s gaze sharpened before he glared immediately at the two meter tall Cyborg named Silver Chain who was walking out of the depths of the alley slowly.

“Outsider… Leave on your own. Otherwise, die!” Silver Chain raised the sharp black claw in his hand that made a cold, hard noise.

The distance between them was less than three meters away. Garen’s hand grasped the hilt of the saber at his waist gently while Silver Chain’s hand tightened around the sharp black claw as if it could burst forth at any time.

The situation would break out at any moment.

Saber Two who was heavily injured on the ground covered the wound on her abdomen.

“… Head Minister?! How did he appear here suddenly?!” Saber Two Yurijie said softly in a faintly exhausted tone.

“We need to warn him and get him to leave quickly! That guy… is not someone that humans can withstand!” Saber One’s forehead was drenched in sweat. Three of his ribs were probably broken.

He understood now that this was a battle of the Four Great Cornerstones. Their opponent was a member of Vulture, a large organization that was specially created to capture the Four Great Cornerstones. They were an armed force that most people could not counter at all. It would be fine if they were the only ones here because they would not kill two of their own people easily as they were part of the Four Great Cornerstones. However, the circumstances would change when outsiders were involved… People like them did not take human lives seriously!

He could not drag other people into this!

While harboring these thoughts, Saber One grabbed his keys and flung them in Garen’s direction firmly.

“Get out of here quickly!!” He yelled while using his last ounce of strength.

The crashing noises of the keys echoed in the air.

However, something happened momentarily when the keys flew across the sky.

Clang!!

A ray of white light lit up as Garen drew his saber.

Chapter 1166: Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the darkness, the saber was as bright as a silver path, reflecting the dim lights by the street.

Silver Chain’s black claw and Garen’s saber clashed against each other.

Clank clank clank clank clank!!

Big white light sparked around Garen. Those sparks were the result of the clashes between the extremely fast moving saber and sharp claw. Every time they collided, a white light sparked.

“Slash!” Holding his saber with both of his hands, Garen drew a sharp path forward at lightning speed.

Pew!!

Thud thud thud…

Silver Chain retreated a few steps back as a big, deep wound opened up on his chest. Fresh blood started flowing out of the wound, dripping to the ground.

It was only then that the keys Saber One had thrown out started to fall to the ground. It had already been cut into tiny pieces and no longer resembled its original appearance.

He was stunned as he lowered his head and looked at the wound on his chest.

He was injured?!!!

He was a modified Cyborg, a top class warrior from the organization that had experienced hundreds of battles! Surprisingly, he was injured by a man who was less than twenty years old?!!

Silver Chain was in disbelief as he moved his hand and touched the wound on his chest.

“This…”

Shing… Garen slowly sheathed his saber.

“Do you want to scram on your own or do you prefer me sending you off?” He asked in a condescending tone.

“… I’ll let you all off the hook this time!” Silver stared at Garen as he turned around decisively and leaped, disappearing into the darkness in an instant.

Boom!!

Suddenly, plenty of black sharp claws burst out from the darkness and headed towards Garen.

Clang!!

The white sparks appeared once more as the black sharp claws were blocked off with great precision. No one could even see Garen moving his saber at all.

Garen did not pursue after him as he deflected the last black sharp claw. Garen then sheathed his saber once more, making a clunking sound as he did so. It seemed that he had created an Absolute Territory two meters around him with him as the epicenter and nothing would be able to invade this space.

Furthermore, it was as if he was not in the battle at all from the beginning until the end as his white shirt still looked the same as previously when he was walking back home.

The alley was in complete silence. It was as if nothing had happened here excluding the messy remnants from the battle.

“So… So strong!!” Both Saber One and Saber Two witnessed the whole situation with a dull look in their eyes as they looked at Garen deflecting the black sharp claws.

The strong and terrifying cyborg could not even break Garen’s defense at all! This level of Saber Art… was almost at the peak of humanity’s limit!!

“That’s… That’s the Head Minister for you!” Saber One gulped as he now realized that Garen had been holding back more than a trick or two when he sparred with Garen back at the Combat Department. It was no wonder he kept being bullied as the difference between their strength was simply too huge!

It was incredibly ridiculous for a typical human’s strength to reach such a level!

“Are you okay.” Garen walked towards them and helped them up. “Both of you are seriously injured and will need blood transfusion in the hospital immediately.” He frowned and told them as he saw their injuries.

“We’re lucky… that the Head Minister had coincidentally walked passed here…we will be in big trouble if not for you…” Saber Two smiled wryly.

“It’s best for you to not represent the human next time.” Garen smiled gently. “That thing is not something you can win against. You shouldn’t fight it even if you don’t represent the human race.”

Saber One was stunned momentarily, and he smiled.

“Understood.”

He nodded repetitively.

********

Half an hour later. Lincoln’s ambulance arrived to send the two to the hospital.

Garen stood on the street as he looked at the ambulance disappearing in the distance. If it was not for him to pass by coincidentally while Saber One and Saber Two were ambushed, he might not be able to discover one of the Four Great Cornerstones was actually Lincoln’s cousin brother, Yuria.

He was no other than Saber One, whose real name he did not bother to remember.

In the Saber Art Dojo, Garen’s nickname was the Great Saber and beneath him was Saber One, Saber Two and so on until the Saber Tens. This crude management brought about a strong passion for competition and rivalry as the number in the nickname signified their strength.

“I didn’t expect… the Savior, one of the Four Great Cornerstones would be Yuria… I always thought that it would be Lincoln.” He held his saber by his waist tightly as he gazed at the silent street around him. As expected, someone with great influence had set up the surrounding beforehand as they wanted to keep it as an absolute secret.

Garen then walked back slowly from where he came from.

At the top of the building far away, a variety of surveillance equipment was set up. Several people in blue tight shirt were crawled in front of the surveillance system. Their faces twitched as they saw the situation on the other side of the monitor unfold.

“This… This is ridiculous!”

“Seven slashes in one second! What incredible talent in Saber Art!” A middle-aged woman in glasses said as she sweated around her forehead. “This level of Saber Art can be coined as a master in the world of blades and sabers.”

“Are you saying that this kid who’s less than eighteen years old is a Saber Master?!” The person beside her, who was responsible for the operations whispered in disbelief.

“If everyone has this kind of talent in Battle Skills, no one would be using firearms to make up for their lack of skills.” The woman smiled wryly. “It’s as you said. This young man named Kong Xiaofei has indeed reached the pinnacle as a human weapon and it would be an understatement to call him a Saber Master.”

“Legend has it that a Saber Master is able to cut down the airplane in the sky.”

“My Lord, it’s a flying bird…” The woman said helplessly.

“Alright, alright. A flying bird. It’s incredible that he is able to stand toe to toe against our ultimate cyborg warrior without modifying his body at all!” The man in charge praised. “How are we going to deal with this talented man who appeared out of nowhere?”

” I think…” The woman adjusted her glasses. “I think we can try and make contact with him. The purpose of humans living in this world is to obtain reputation and authority to lead a better life. Perhaps we can recruit him into our organization, Vulture.”

“Recruit him?” The person in charge started to ponder about this possibility. “Although he looks very promising, I don’t think we have a suitable position for him even if we manage to recruit him…unless he is willing to be modified.”

“While it’s true that we do not have a place for him to do what he does best, I think he is very suited to become an instructor. You have to know that there are less than five people with talent similar to his in the entire world and all of them are big shots with widespread reputation and influences. He has nothing as compared to them so he should be easily tempted by this invitation.”

The woman explained.

“Let’s send some people to test the water.” The person in charge decided.

“Understood.”

*******

“It seems… that there is a little bit of Soul Energy, but it isn’t as much as I expected,” Garen recalled the amount of aura he sensed from Yuria. He could only sense a vague Soul Energy when their limbs came in contact with each other.

“It seems to be in an inactive state.”

He sat in the courtyard in his new house. The golden sunlight shone through the skylight above him, bathing nothing else but him in the courtyard.

His new house was a villa located in a high-end residential area of the city center. A villa at the heart of the Lily of the Valley, a second-tier city, did not cost much at less than half a million.

The design of the villa is of the traditional, square double story with a courtyard. One may call it a gigantified version of siheyuan ^1 instead of a villa as it had slightly more area than the usual ones. Furthermore, it was much more beautiful as there were exquisite eagle sculptures placed at every edge of the roofs.

There was also a small pond at the entrance with a beautiful copper mermaid sculpture in it.

“I still can’t confirm that he is an Inheritor. I need more time to interact with him,” Garen pondered.

He then recalled that Cyborg earlier and thought that he was rather powerful.

“I believe they will contact me on their own accord to test my attitude soon. The Vulture and The Four Great Cornerstones…” Yuria had told him everything he knew in the hospital and he had also found out that the Cyborg belonged to a large and mysterious organization, Vulture.

“The Savior is able to borrow the strength from the people around him and become strong enough to achieve his goal. Is he able to borrow strength from the others? Interesting…” Although Garen did not know what kind of abilities the remaining Three Great Cornerstones possess, he guessed that it would be something of similar scale.

The ability of the Savior was very subjective as it depended on how the user made use of it. If the people he borrowed the strength from were powerful, then he would be powerful as well. If he were to borrow it from many people, he would then become the Savior who bore the hope of tens of thousands of citizens. This would grant him strength so powerful to the realm where no one had seen before.

Crack… He heard someone returned as the door to the living room far away was opened, breaking off Garen’s chain of thought.

“I’m back.” Kong Xinxue threw her high heels to one side, stepping onto the wooden floor still in her white stockings. She entered the house without even wearing any slippers.

“I heard that you are the one who sent Yuria and the other to the hospital?” Kong Xinxue carried a chair towards Garen, placed it down in front of him and sat on it.

The white one-piece dress was wrinkled horribly as it was used as a cushion when pressed in between the chair and her butt.

“Yeah.” Garen nodded.

“I heard that your Saber Art is incredibly good? Where did you learn that? Why did I not see you practice before in the past?” Kong Xinxue stared at Garen suspiciously.

“It’s because I’m a genius.” Garen had no sense of shame. “I learn those things via observation.” He replied calmly as he sat cross-legged on the floor.

“A genius…” Kong Xinxue was speechless. “Alright genius. Can you tell me why there’s such a drastic change in personality before and after the fever? Don’t tell me a spirit possessed your body or something the Mysterious Old Man novel used to trick the kids.”

“Mysterious Old Man?” Garen was stunned. Transmigration novel had yet to gain its momentum in this world, right? Only people from Planet Earth would be able to mention the Mysterious Old Man novel naturally in their examples.

He then stared at Kong Xinxue suspiciously.

“What are you talking about?”

“What do you mean?” Kong Xinxue seemed to have sensed something as she started to act dumb. “Regardless, I feel that there’s something off about you.”

“In what aspect?” Garen did not understand her.

“Every aspect about you seems off.” Kong Xinxue took a deep breath. “Recently, you’ve scored full marks for every exam paper. The teacher has already taken your paper as a benchmark for being the perfectly answered paper in the entire Five School Alliance. Oh right, I guess you haven’t realized that that was a mock examination for the college entrance examination. Every student in the schools including us would be participating in it. You, on the other hand, have hit a perfect score…”

Garen wanted to say that he had solved them while he’s half-awake but he was not sure if he should…

Regardless, he had decided to come to this world to take a rest so he was too lazy to take note of such trivial stuff.

Chapter 1167: Organization 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Then, someone came running towards me telling that my brother is a martial art genius who only appears once every millennium… You’ve turned from a good-for-nothing into something else entirely, so much so that your personality and attitude has changed as well. It’s as if you’ve turned into someone else.”

Kong Xinxue’s expression turned serious.

“Be honest. Who exactly are you?”

“I am your brother.” Garen thought for a while before replying.

“Stop acting dumb! Be honest. We have a huge circle of friends. We will eventually know who you really are even if you act dumb.” Kong Xinxue smiled coldly. “Furthermore, you don’t seem to be hiding your identity at all from the very beginning. Were you not planning to hide this truth?”

Garen blinked.

“What are you talking about, I don’t understand what you’re saying at all.”

“Stop acting cute!!!” Kong Xinxue glared at him. “This world is a resting point for us. Spill the beans. We’ve encountered many of you outsiders who barged in without going through inspection!”

Although Garen was slightly stunned on the outside, his heart was already sinking from the huge tidal waves.

A Transmigrator!!??

He did not expect that Kong Xinxue was also a Transmigrator! Furthermore, there seemed to be more than one Transmigrator in this world!!!

“What do you mean ‘this world’?” Garen continued acting oblivious.

“Huhu…” Kong Xinxue laughed coldly.

As they stared at each other in the eyes, they both had already known the truth.

“Fine…” Garen nodded. “I have just arrived in this world not long ago and entered Kong Xiaofei’s body. Do you have anything else you wish to ask?”

He decided to be honest with her as he didn’t see any signs of lying from Kong Xinxue as well. Hence, it would be fair to assume that whatever she had said was the truth.

“Well, aren’t you pretty good in acting…” She continued smiling coldly. Now that she had confirmed that the Kong Xiaofei wasn’t the person she knew, her attitude towards him had distanced and was no longer as close as it used to be.

“I have seen many closet perverts like you who would say things implicitly and act cold on the outside and feel sexually passionate from the inside. Each and every one of you is a hypocrite who would act innocent on the surface and has been suppressing your twisted desire inside.”

She pondered for a moment before continuing. “Do you know what I wish to do the most right now?”

“What?”

“I want to punch you.”

“…” Garen blinked. “You can’t win against me.” He said with utmost sincerity.

“…” Kong Xinxue was speechless. “Do you know what the phrase one needs to lose some in order to gain what one desires mean?”

“I do.” Garen didn’t understand the reason she told him that.

“If you wish to f*ck me, you better not hit back!!” Kong Xinxue then stood up swiftly as she threw a punch towards Garen’s face.

Hu…

Her fist stopped right in front of Garen’s face, which was less than half a centimeter away. Her fist was single-handedly caught firmly by Garen.

“I’ll tell.” He looked hopelessly at Kong Xinxue who was well within reach. “Can’t you be a bit normal? Weren’t we having a civilized conversation? How did that unfold into this now?”

“You killed my beloved brother. Do you expect me to be grateful and treat you as my best friend?” Kong Xinxue’s expression turned ice cold.

“You… I shouldn’t have placed any hope on a mentally challenged person.” Garen was speechless as he sighed.

The moment he loosened his hand, Kong Xinxue turned her body around and side kicked Garen’s waist.

Slam.

Her leg was caught firmly by Garen once more.

While her small leg in black stocking was in Garen’s hand, the important detail was not of this. As Kong Xinxue had her leg raised up high, Garen was able to see everything underneath the dress from his point of view…

He could vaguely see a white triangular shape underneath the black stocking.

“See. You’re indeed a pervert!” Kong Xinxue put her leg away as if nothing had happened. “You even dared to peak at your own biological sister!” Perhaps she had realized that she could not win against Garen, so she decided to stop trying.

“You must be an extremely cruel and merciless man in the past.”

“Why do you say so?” Garen sat in his original position firmly, as if he did not make any move at all.

“You didn’t even give me a chance despite how beautiful I am.” Kong Xinxue calmly sat down and she did not seem to be embarrassed about showing what was underneath her dress. Her action assured Garen even more that she was a weird person.

“To yield in and let you punch me?” Garen was speechless.

“Alright, let’s stop talking nonsense. As a Transmigrator, I have the duty to introduce you to people like us nearby so that you can have a better understanding of our internal social network.”

“What social network? Do you have a lot of associates in this world?” Garen was interested in this topic. It was rather stressful to be with this oddball on a daily basis as one small mistake and he would be branded as a pervert.

“A lot? It’s a handful I guess since we have dozens of people. Since this place is where everything started so a lot of people gathered here.” When Kong Xinxue calmed down, she was actually rather lady-like. Her beautiful and elegant face, white dress, black stockings and long hair had made her look extremely seductive.

“It’s been a while since everyone gathered. Perhaps I can suggest everyone to meet up.”

“Do all Transmigrators originate from the same place?” Garen asked another question after thinking for a while.

“No. Not at all.” Kong Xinxue shook her head. “Technically speaking, there is no single location. Although some may come from Earth, they are from a different parallel universe. Naturally, most of them come from Earth and the minorities come from somewhere else. I do not know the reason behind this but this is the current situation.”

“Also,” she gave him a respectful look. “Don’t be conceited that you’re strong. There are many Transmigrators who are very powerful as well.”

“What’s the name?” Garen nodded. “There should be a name for this Transmigrator organization right?”

“Of course there is.” Kong Xinxue stood up. “It’s called Lighthouse.”

******

Garen did not expect that the members of the Lighthouse would give each other a helping hand. According to the intel from Kong Xinxue, not everyone inside had stood at the pinnacle of the world. Most of them were at the middle or above average level and a handful of them had reached the very top. However, the majority of them were at the below average and lower level.

All of them would exchange resources and help each other so that everyone could improve together. That was the motto of the Lighthouse. Afterall, the worlds were incredibly huge and everyone had their own unique system. Hence they should be able to exchange their knowledge no matter what.

Everyone nearby was soon told of the gathering.

Kong Xinxue departed together with Garen ten minutes earlier to a fancy restaurant nearby. Although there was a sign stating that it was closed at the entrance of the restaurant, both of them entered without having any regard for others and locked the door. There were about seven to eight people already sitting in the transparent glass chair by the glass table. All of them seemed to be chatting about happily among each other.

They were in a variety of uniforms such as police, white-collar worker, technician, housewife, and student.

The moment Garen and Kong Xinxue entered, A fat middle-aged man walked up and welcomed them.

“Welcome, welcome! Ah Xue, it’s been a long time since you invited us for a gathering.” The fat man smiled, giving off a friendly and peaceful vibe.

“I’ve brought a new person along so that everyone can get to know him. Everyone feel free as I may have to trouble you all once again .” It was rare to see Kong Xinxue being so polite and formal.

“No problem! I’ll take care of him.” The man patted his chest as he said with alacrity. “You are…”

“Garen,” Garen told him his name on his own accord.

“Nice to meet you.”

“Nice to meet you.”

Both of them shook hand and the first impression was great. As Transmigrators, they could not determine their age based on their physical appearances. Hence everyone did not care that Garen looked like a kid.

“Alright let’s hear it from everybody. As the Plot is just around the corner, what do you guys plan to do?” Kong Xinxue sat down as she gave off a vibe of a leader.

Garen followed along as he sat in a chair beside her. No one felt strange seeing two similar faces sitting side by side.

“Why don’t we transmigrate?” A technician uncle who was drinking alcoholic drink quietly suggested as he frowned. “I’ve been to two worlds, three if you include this one. The problem with facing against the Plot is that it is dangerous. The Plot is not something that could be easily changed. If it were that easy, there wouldn’t be so many predecessors dying in the middle of their journey.”

“Where do you want to transmigrate to? This world is the safest world around. The Power Level here is low and the constraint of the universe is extremely high. Isn’t it more troublesome to go somewhere else?” The policewoman curled her lips. “All I did was hiding here and there as I tried to move forward in the previous world. Ultimately, I died due to unforeseen circumstances. Just thinking of it annoys me.”

“Li Hua is right. We can still gauge which area is still safe or not if we are within the Plot. However, once we are out of the Plot, we will be placed in the dark. I think it’s best for us to play by the ear and avoid the dangerous zones of the Plot. The Slayer is one of the dangerous points among the Four Great Cornerstones and the remaining three should be relatively safe.” The housewife agreed as she added on.

“Are we not going to introduce the new member?” A woman suggested.

Garen stood up and picked up his wine glass as he looked around. “My name is Garen. I’ve recently transmigrated into this world and I wish to be part of the team as soon as possible.” He was quick to earn everyone’s friendliness with his smile and his educated manner.

Soon, everyone present told him that he could inquire them anything if he needed help.

Garen then obtained the means to contact everyone before sitting down and continue listening to their discussion.

“Everyone should be aware of the Slayer of the Four Great Cornerstone’s ability. He possesses every slaying technique in this world. He can learn any assassination technique by just looking at it once and is seriously overpowered. To make things worse, we also have this world’s constraint as well. He, who is one of the Four Great Cornerstone will never die. Who would be able to fight against a killing machine that can’t be killed?” The technician uncle said hopelessly.

“Can we request for support? The people we have here that know how to fight are mainly Li Hua and Yong He and the rest of us are just career professionals. If we are in trouble, isn’t our only option is to be reincarnated? It would be difficult to contact one another if that were to happen.” The woman frowned as she explained.

“What level of assistance can we request based on our current Contribution Points?” Kong Xinxue asked calmly.

“I’ve just obtained a hundred points from the ultimate cake quest.”

“I’ve just finished collecting the consultation. I have about a hundred and fifty points left including the ones that I didn’t use last time.”

“I can only fork out two hundred points. I need to save some to purchase my medicine since this world does not have the medicine that could cure my illness…” The young woman said helplessly.

“I can fork out three hundred points.” Kong Xinxue said firmly. “I’ll note down the number of Contribution Points that everyone had pooled in. Let’s try and collect more Contribution Points in these coming days so that we can afford to hire a high-level helper. Although the Slayer’s ability is very troublesome, he would not be able to learn the techniques of a powerhouse that specializes in sealing and dealing heavy damage instead of killing.”

“That’s a good idea.”

Chapter 1168: Organization 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Alright let’s stop this pessimistic conversation. Let’s talk about our experience in the past world.” Kong Xinxue clapped her hands.

It was obvious that she was the leader of this small group as everything she said was very convincing. Naturally, everyone started to talk about their past experience in the previous worlds. This was to introduce everyone’s history to Garen.

“My previous life can be summed up into a single word, tragic. It was a Machine Girl World and the sky was filled with missiles. I always had the impression that Machine Girls were incredibly cute from the animation back in the days but if you were to encounter them, you will soon realize that they would kill anyone without batting an eyelid. I lived alone in seclusion inside the forest for sixty years before I died at the age of eighty-two due to illness.” The technician uncle said helplessly.

“How can you call that a tragedy, when my previous life can truly be summed up with the word tragic.” Li Hua the policewoman from the other side of the table butted in. “The three major races mainly Orcs, Demons, and Humans were in an all-out war. My family, the half-orc was categorized as slaves and we had been sold here and there as ornamental pets.” She gave off an unbearable expression as she recalled.

“You guys know nothing about it. I was two meters and two centimeters tall and considered to be the tallest among my family members. However, those Demons, Humans, and Orcs were all at least ten meters tall and would often squat down by the cage and play with us as if we are birds… It felt like an earthquake whenever they walked and I thought that I had arrived at the Giant World when I first reincarnated. Ultimately, it’s not us that was short but they were just too tall…”

“That doesn’t sound tragic at all. You get to be a pet where you get to have good food and drinks. You can sleep after you eat and vice versa. My previous life was truly a tragedy. I was reincarnated as a human blood bank for the vampires. I would be awake for no more than three hours on a daily basis and I could not even move since I was placed inside a nursery chamber. Ultimately, I died after living for thirty-two years.”

“All of you have never been to my previous world. That world is defined by the word tragedy!” Another middle-aged man said with a depressed look on his face. “Have you guys heard of the show Dragon Ball? That world is approximately the same as Dragon Ball. They would fire an extremely wide area of effect planet-destroying class missiles at the drop of a hat. It’s best for you to not come out and fight if you’re less than Level Seven or Level Eight. You’d be ashamed to call yourself a powerhouse if you’re not a Level Nine and have become a Guardian of a Planet. They wouldn’t even classify a battle that cost one hundred billion lives as a war! That was classified as fooling around! Unfortunately, I was just a normal Interstellar Technician and was not qualified to learn how to operate a mech.”

“I don’t understand those level things. All I wanted is to live a quiet and peaceful life as a normal human who strives in his career, work hard and enjoy life.” The fat chef said with a smile on his face as he came out from the kitchen, placing two enticing dishes onto the table.

“Everyone has a different goal and will go after the things they deem meaningful,” Garen smiled as he responded.

“However, since we have reincarnated once and lived so many additional years, shouldn’t we lead a better life when compared to the others? Won’t it be humiliating if we keep living the same way?” A woman with short, red hair spoke arrogantly like an elderly.

Kong Xinxue who was just beside Garen started to introduce her to Garen softly.

“Her name is Yuan Xing. She was a boring uncle in her last life. She has now reincarnated as a rich lady from a highly influential family. Furthermore, she has a goddess-like appearance…”

Garen maintained his smile as he nodded at the woman and the opposing party, too, politely greeted him back.

“Isn’t the girl beside her pretty?” Kong Xinxue hinted him to look at the long black-haired woman beside the lady with red hair. The woman was whispering to another person in a ladylike manner on a certain topic. She had fair skin and her facial feature was very exquisite, giving off a natural and elegant vibe.

“Yes.”

“She’s Xi Yuan. She raised and fed pigs for a living in her previous life. Although she has been reincarnated as a beautiful maiden, she still constantly thinks of raising and feeding the pigs. She is now a multi-billionaire who owns a business in raising pigs.”

“…”

The smile on Garen’s face turned stiff.

“Do you see that uncle sitting on the other side?” Kong Xinxue curled her lips. “He was an absolute beauty who mastered the art of seduction via her gaze. He carries that habit along with him even after reincarnation and would automatically move his eyebrows while making eye contact with anybody. It’s best for you to close your eyes to avoid any trouble.”

“Is there anyone normal here…” Garen was speechless.

“There is one. She is sitting right next to you. It is no other than I, Kong Xinxue.” Kong Xinxue patted her chest as she said narcissistically.

“How many worlds have you been to?” Garen asked curiously.

“Three.” Kong Xinxue told him truthfully. “There’s nothing much to say about the first world. I kept striving forward as I thought that I could conquer the world’s economy. Unfortunately, I died in the middle of my journey. There are a few gifted people who you can’t win against even if you were reincarnated. They’re simply that amazing.”

“That’s pretty normal.” Garen nodded. “What about the second world?”

“The second world is the Bacterial World. I transmigrated and became a Bacillus inside the large intestine. I was ultimately killed along with the intestinal worms via insecticide.” Kong Xinxue did not try to hide anything at all. “Frankly speaking, I always felt that I may have transmigrated into a person’s bowel, becoming a bacteria with a conscience. It was really fascinating.”

“… You’re not far off from being an oddball.” Garen was speechless.

“Nothing is impossible.” Kong Xinxue shrugged.

“That’s true.” Garen nodded as he picked his cup up as he gently drank his wine. He stopped speaking as he sat quietly, listening to everyone’s chatter over a variety of topics.

“You seem to be rather lost judging from your look. You should go and search for the Tree of Wisdom. He’s the smartest among us Transmigrators.” Kong Xinxue spoke after a moment of silence.

“Tree of Wisdom?”

“Yep. He’s a wise man.”

“He needs fifteen minutes to do something we can do in one second. You’ll have to wait for at least half an hour for him to finish one sentence.”

“…”

Kong Xinxue then started mimicking how the Tree of Wisdom would speak to them.

“Life… is… extremely… cruel… we… need… to…”

The densely packed crowd sitting in the big square under the tree started yawning here and there.

“Which word has he reached?”

“He’s still at the word ‘to’.”

“Oh. I’ll take a short nap while I wait.”

“I’ll go buy some snacks. Do you need anything?”

“A bucket of small steamed buns will do.”

Garen and Kong Xinxue couldn’t help but burst into laughter as she finished speaking.

“The funniest part is his longest sentence was three hours long! At that time, one of the people thought that he had finished his speech even though he was only eighty percent through. As he stood up and was about to leave the area, he added on and said that what he did was f*cking wrong.”

“When that man found out, he raged to the point he almost vomited blood.” Kong Xinxue laughed as she staggered forward and backward.

“There really are all sorts of people.” Garen sighed emotionally.

“Indeed. We’re all Transmigrators. There’s bound to be good ones and bad ones. We’re considered very fortunate as there are some Transmigrators who encountered all kinds of unfortunate events and tragedies from the very beginning, causing them to have a huge temperament.” Kong Xinxue sighed. “Although I know that it’s bad for me to speak behind someone’s back, I couldn’t help but say it out loud.”

She pondered for a moment. “Alright. That’s all from me. It’s your turn now. How many worlds have you been to?”

Garen drank a mouthful of wine.

“I’ve been to three worlds. Sigh… The first one is a Martial Art World. It was pretty dull and I eventually died from an atomic bomb and a volcano eruption.”

“Died without leaving any corpse behind huh.”

“The second world is a supernatural world. Although I managed to survive well there, I was eliminated by the new era.” Garen was trying to explain that the supernatural power had faded and he was ultimately kicked out by the Planet’s Will.

“That’s pretty tragic but slightly better than the first one. What about the third world?”

The third one…” Gared sighed. “I lost a fight in the third world. I was then captured and died from old age while waiting for someone to rescue me.”

Pfft.

A woman sitting on the other side of Garen could not hold onto her laughter as she started laughing. No one knew when she appeared beside Garen. She had on a cute, white cat ear as a hair clip, two ponytails and was wearing a long sleeve, black T-shirt paired with a black red checkered short skirt which was part of a school’s uniform. She looked very innocent and cute.

“Sorry. I couldn’t hold in my laughter when I heard that you died from old age.” The girl laughed as she covered her mouth.

“… No wonder you always look rather sulky and lazy all the time.” Kong Xinxue ignored the other girl as she sipped the milk from her cup.

“I’ve lived as a failure in all three worlds.” Garen sighed. He didn’t mention the Blood Breed World in the middle of the second and third world. In his perspective, he was just passing by in that world so it was not counted.

“And you are?” Out of politeness, Garen looked at the girl who was laughing earlier.

The girl tilted her head innocently. “My name is Zhao Wenzhen. I am the temporary leader of the Sky Seat’s Shooting Fragrant Sect. I heard that a newly joined member here is a Kendo master. Hence, I’ve personally come here to recruit you into my sect.”

“Kendo?” Garen shook his head. “I do not practice Kendo. What you’re referring to is the Japanese Blade Technique, right?”

“Wrong~” Zhao Wenzhen smiled as she spoke. “Japanese Blade Technique is a Saber Art developed in Japan. What I’m referring to is the Assassination Blade Technique developed during the Spring and Autumn Warring States Period.”

“You pestering fox, can’t you see people are ignoring you? Did you come here to seduce another man again?” Kong Xinxue’s tone was rather hostile as she spoke loudly to Zhao Wenzhen.

“You may call me Ms. Nine-Tailed Fox even though that was from my previous life. In this life, I wish to live a peaceful life as a cute and beautiful woman.” Zhao Wenzhen gestured a V shape with her finger as she smiled with her eyes closed.

“Everyone present here are most likely Transmigrators from Earth. As the other Transmigrators from another civilization were not the same kind as us, we do not communicate much. If we Transmigrators from Earth do not unite together, we can only blame ourselves if we were bullied by others.” Zhao Wenzhen added on as she elaborated.

“I can’t stand people who are extremely flirtatious towards everybody.” Kong Xinxue said in a bad mood.

“Aren’t you used to not seeing an open pervert?” Zhao Wenzhen was all smiles.

“You!!”

“Alright, stop fooling around.” Everyone tried to smoothen things over between the two of them. “Everyone, let’s eat. It’s a classic Chinese meal!”

Garen was speechless as he sat in between these two girls.

“What I know is just Sword Art instead of Kendo… I know nothing of it at all. I feel that Kendo is more towards cleaving in a non-conspicuous manner.”

“What about your technique then?” Zhao Wenzhen squinted her eyes as she spoke gently. “Do you want to spar with me here?”

“Ignore her. She is the boss of the world’s largest mafia. Her definition of competition is to kill as many people as possible.” Kong Xinxue smiled coldly. “Don’t be fooled by her innocent look.”

“What’s wrong with Black Fist? Those people are only good at brawling. If I didn’t welcome them with open arms, give them a second chance and organize the Black Fist Competition in this world when they couldn’t afford to survive, the society would be much more unstable by a few hundred points.” Zhao Wenzhen started to feel discontent.

“Furthermore, how can those idiotic rash fellows be compared with our little brother Garen?” Zhao Wenzhen leaned her body closer to Garen as she, who was wearing a short skirt, placed her snow-white tender leg beside Garen’s leg.

Chapter 1169: Curtains Rising 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Little brother?” Garen laughed out loud. “Do you know how old I am? And yet you dare call me little brother just like that…” He emphasized the word ‘little’.

“Could you possibly be older than five thousand years old?” said Nine-Tailed Fox smilingly. “I’m already 6,600 years old, you know~~”

“You musky fox!” Beside them, Kong Xinxue’s expression was one of disgust as she held her nose and hurriedly distanced herself from them. “If I sit close to you, that foul musk of yours gets me straight in the nose!”

“In that case, you are older than me, but this is my first time seeing a girl insist that she’s older than someone else.” Garen sniffed, and did indeed smell a sweet fragrance. It came from Nine-Tailed Fox and seemed to be a perfume, but it was not particularly thick. It was true, men did enjoy a smell like this.

“That’s why you gotta call me Big Sis… Compared to that worthless Ah Xue over there, there are a lot more benefits to calling me your big sister,” said Nine-Tailed Fox with a laughing, twirling a lock of her long hair around her finger.

On the other side, Kong Xinxue was annoyed again.

“Damn old witch, you’re still acting young at your age? Why couldn’t you have been struck dead by lightning back then!? To think you ended up reincarnating here, meeting you is the biggest stain on my life!” said Kong Xinxue expressionlessly.

“Oh, my… Look, your little brother’s hand is starting to wander, isn’t it?” Nine-Tailed Fox grabbed Garen’s hand, and placed it on her waist gently, slowly moving it downward. Her expression was taunting as she looked at Kong Xinxue. But although it looked extremely promiscuous, in truth she did not allow Garen’s hand to touch her body at all, the back of her own hand staying resolutely between his touch and her skin.

“Pervert!” Kong Xinxue stared at Garen, and spat the words out through clenched teeth.

“It has nothing to do with me,” said Garen innocently. “I’m being forced.”

“…” Kong Xinxue was speechless, Nine-Tailed Fox giggled. Everyone else burst out laughing as well.

They had a lot of fun with that meal, and then some of the others who had business to attend to left first.

Since Garen had laid it out with Kong Xinxue, and no longer assumed the identity of her younger brother, the two of them were not as close as they had been before either. Kong Xinxue could not watch how Garen allowed Nine-Tailed Fox to hug him without resistance, so she angrily downed a few large cups of soy sauce, then she got up and left without a word.

“Let’s go too.” Nine-Tailed Fox had always held Garen’s hand on her bosom, and it looked extremely suggestive on the surface, but in truth he never really touched anything sensitive either.

Now that Kong Xinxue had left, she pulled Garen’s hand away.

“As a Territorial Administrator, that girl isn’t tolerant enough,” she giggled, smoothing out her long hair.

“Are you very close to her?” asked Garen curiously.

“So-so, I guess… We used to be very good friends, but then the guy she finally fell in love with for the first time fell in love with me instead, and I threw him away in the end. Perhaps that was too heavy a blow to her ego, and our relationship started going downhill from there.” Nine-Tailed Fox sat alone with Garen, chatting idly. She drank cup after cup of plain water, but she drank it as others would drink wine. Seemed like she was no regular person either…

“Sounds like a very tragic story.” Garen was bored anyway, so he decided to stay back and listen to some gossip about Kong Xinxue. Unbeknownst to him, as soon as he relaxed completely, it was as though he was a completely different person. Consider how nervous he was before, and that was how relaxed he was now. He did not want to even think about things like Soul Rings or the like anymore. At first he thought he would be able to find a fellow Inheritor, but instead he found something better, fellow Transmigrators. That sense of loneliness buried deep within Garen’s heart was slowly beginning to fade.

The existence of Lighthouse told him that he was not alone, and that there were many other Transmigrators struggling and living their lives in many of the other different worlds. He just never encountered them before. Even if he had, perhaps they simply did not recognize each other.

“I can tell, you’ve been alone for a very long time. I know that feeling,” said Nine-Tailed Fox with a sigh. “There was a period of three thousand years when I was so lonely I nearly went mad. The fact that I was a Transmigrator was a secret that only I could keep, and I was constantly terrified of revealing my true identity in my daily actions and daily life. I only managed to relieve that suffocating sensation, of having something forever stuck in my heart, when I met Ah Xue…”

“When you met Ah Xue? Were you two in the same world before?” said Garen out of curiosity.

“She was the one who saved me…” Nine-Tailed Fox gently picked up a lock of her black hair, twirling it around and around her fingertip. “She found me in a maze underneath some ruins, and brought me into Lighthouse… In the end, she was the one who brought me here, to this world, where I settled down. It’s been 53 years now, come to think of it.”

“No wonder your relationship seems strange.” Garen nodded. “Since you’ve lived for six thousand years, you’re my senior, so I’d like to ask you a question.”

“Go ahead. I can’t promise I’ll be able to answer you, but since I fancy the way you look, I’ll try my best to reply as a reward to you.” Nine-Tailed Fox narrowed her eyes, sprawling onto the table and letting her long hair fan out, some of it falling onto the table like a cloth and some of it hanging down like a waterfall.

“Do you know anything about Soul Seeds?”

“Soul Seeds?” Nine-Tailed Fox was slightly taken aback. “Isn’t that something from the Mother Stream System? I thought only people who used the Mother Stream as their cultivation system would have something like that, but I hear that it’s extremely difficult to condense. Why? Do you want to condense that?”

“Of course I do,” replied Garen frankly. “Since you know about it, that must mean that there are other people using the Mother Stream System in Lighthouse, right?”

“Yes, there are… But the Mother Stream System is quite the unpopular system, it’s very hard to level up, and it is highly restricted by the laws of the world, so it would require a great commitment in terms of both energy and time. Very few people would take this path…” said Nine-Tailed Fox hesitantly. “Using my Faerie System, for example, I can reach a high level of power within a mere thousand years, and even I come to a world with very harsh restrictions like this one, my Vitality will still be extremely considerable. Then there’s the Holy Knight System, people who use it can obtain extremely powerful physical abilities within a very short time. These are all extremely effective shortcuts, but the Mother Stream System is different… Their aim is something far too pure, they always discard more than 90% of their energy because it’s impure, and they only accept the tiny bits of the absolutely pure Soul Seed that’s left.”

“So they’re a bit too slow, is that it?” Garen continued.

“Yeah, extremely slow.” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded.

Panpan was starting to bring up some candelabras, lighting them. There were three three-forked candelabras, placed on the long table to illuminate the faces of those who remained.

By now, the attendees had been divided into three small groups, Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox in one, and the rest divided into two groups. They all kept the conversation to themselves.

“If you have enough Contribution Points, you can apply to go to a world that specializes in cultivating Soul Seeds, I hear that you’d need a large sum of Contribution Points to reincarnate that world. If you use regular methods, it’s really easy for them to discover that you’re a foreign soul, so quite a few travelers have been destroyed by the people there.”

“That’s why I’d need to pay a large sum to conceal myself?” Garen understood now.

“That’s right.” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded. “To us Transmigrators, our souls are the root to everything that’s special about us, so if it’s destroyed, we’ll die for real. Although the Mother Stream System is very mysterious and powerful, less than a handful of people would actually choose it. In my opinion, if you haven’t gotten too deep into it yet, you can choose another type of system.” Garen could tell that this advise came straight from her heart.

“It’s okay, I’m already used to it anyway, and now I’ve even condensed a Soul Seed. I’m already halfway down this path, there’s no reason for me to squander all my past efforts,” said Garen with a shrug. He had based everything he learned on the Ancient Endor Civilization, and he really would not be used to it if he changed paths now.

“You already condensed one? Then that’s not too bad, although I don’t exactly know what Soul Seeds actually do, there should be something special about them. It’s just that the Mother Stream System takes too long, so don’t think of obtaining any decent powers for at least ten thousand years, hang in there.” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded. “Sigh…” She stretched, revealing glimpses of her jade-white abdomen.

“Alright, Little Brother, your Big Sis wants to go back and sleep.” She waved her fingers, and conjured a black card as though by magic. “This is my name card, it’s my private number, y’know… If you ever have the need, just come find Big Sis and I’ll help you get it out of your system!” she said by Garen’s ear softly, bending over.

The card was quietly slipped into Garen’s shirt pocket.

“Sure, don’t mind if I do.” Garen had no intention of declining, this Nine-Tailed Fox in front of him was more than six thousand years old, and would have more knowledge than an encyclopedia.

Accepting the card, he smiled at her.

“If I encounter any problems, could I ask you for help, Big Sis? I might need your help with some things soon. I’ve been swept into this world’s Plot, and things could get very troublesome if I’m not careful.”

“No problem, as long as it’s not the Slayer, I’ll be sure to cover for you! Relax, my little brother!” Nine-Tailed Fox got up, and patted down her short skirt. “Alright, I really gotta go.”

“Thanks, Big Sis,” said Garen with a smile.

“If you’re already calling me your sister, why do you have to be so polite? You look just like me from back then, alone, constantly wary. You poor child…” Nine-Tailed Fox bent over, and touched Garen’s face lightly.

“Be careful, only a very select few unnatural powers work here in this world, so if you ever see a gun, just get away from it as soon as you can.”

She got up and walked out of the restaurant, swaying her hips elegantly. After greeting a few of the remaining people, she left for real.

Garen got up as well, bidding Panpan goodbye.

“Wait a sec, Ah Xue left this for you.” Panpan handed him a small item, it was a round silver button.

“What’s this?” Garen turned it over in his hands, confused.

“It’s a Lighthouse communication device, using the latest projection technology, it can connect directly to Lighthouse’s main server. You can accept Quests to earn Contribution Points there, or you could upload Quests to hire powerhouse, or you could even use it to buy items. You keep it yourself, it can only be used after verifying our unique soul attribute. Others would only think it’s a regular button,” Panpan explained.

“Got it. Thanks.” Garen nodded. He recalled that Kong Xinxue had left in a huff earlier, but to think she had still remembered to arrange all this for him. In his heart, his impression of her improved somewhat.

******************

Leaving the restaurant gathering, Garen soon reached home, and greeted Kong Yuan in a hurry. Kong Xinxue had already fallen asleep.

After Garen quickly cleaned up and brushed his teeth on his own, he entered his own room, and started to investigate that Lighthouse communication device.

Turning on the table lamp with a smack, he adjusted its brightness, and then Garen pressed down lightly on the silver button.

Psst…

A silver light flashed across the surface of the button.

‘Soul Verification complete, system activation conditions met.’ A melodious female voice spoke in Garen’s head. The words were not spoken in any language, but seemed instead to be converted straight into brainwaves.

Chapter 1170: Curtains Rising 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Curtains Rising 2

‘System verified as first-time activation, please input username vocally, and the system will automatically encrypt your soul attribute as the password, no manual settings required.’

“That’s some high-tech stuff!” Garen clicked his tongue appreciatively. Of all the many civilizations that he had experienced, the Mech World was the most technologically advanced. But this thing before him left that world in the dust. Evidently, there would always be something out there that was better.

“For the username, let’s go with Greatsaber,” said Garen offhandedly.

‘Username confirmed, Greatsaber is already taken, please re-enter a username.’

“It’s already taken…” Garen touched his chin. “Then use Scarlet Snow.”

‘Scarlet Snow is already taken, please re-enter.”

“Scarlet Snow Greatsaber!”

‘Sorry, this username is taken…’

“Blood Splatter Greatsaber!”

‘Sorry, this username is taken…’

“Saber King!”

‘Sorry, this username is taken…’

“Saber God!”

‘Sorry, this username is taken…’

“Saber Saint!” Garen was getting exasperated.

‘Sorry, this username is taken…’

“Saber’s all taken, then use Sword!”

“Saber’s All Taken, this username is available.”

“…”

Garen was beginning to doubt this system.

‘Confirm username, ‘Saber’s All Taken’?”

“Confirm.” He could not be bothered to waste more time on this.

Whoosh.

The silver button in front of him immediately projected a pyramidal 3D image.

The white image spun once, slowly, and a black lighthouse logo appeared in the middle of it.

‘Welcome to the Lighthouse System’

A row of words appeared in the very middle of the image, and they were actually written in the local language.

Immediately after that, a white screen that looked like a forum popped up.

It began with Trading Zone on the very top, followed by Quest Zone, Information Zone, and finally News Zone at the bottom. Four in total.

At the bottom right corner, by his personal account, there was an indicator stating his Contribution Points: 0.

Garen immediately pressed Quest Zone, and found two more options inside, Accept Quest or Submit Quest. He pressed Accept Quest, and was instantly hit by a barrage of information.

‘Forming a team to farm Little Hell Demons, price negotiable.’

‘Sunrise Celestial Technique World: Middle-ranking disciple from the Celestial Sect urgently requires Ultimate Yin ingredient in order to create an instrument, those in possession of any please mmm…’

“A regular martial artist from the Martial Arts World is hiring powerhouses to challenge dojos, the fee is one hundred points a day.’

”High altitude exploration quest: ruins discovered in this world, looking for someone to undo magical formation, price negotiable.’

…

Garen was a little overwhelmed by the long list of various quests, it looked like there were all sorts of quests from all sorts of worlds.

At the bottom, there were even quests asking for someone to bake a cake, ferment some wine, or plant something. There really was something for everyone.

He pressed one, and saw that it also contained the world’s weakening degree.

Garen tapped the explanation, and instantly understood.

“Meaning this is how much each world reduces the visiting Transmigrator’s powers? Minus one means you’ll be one level weaker, minus two means two levels.”

He quickly entered the Four Cornerstones World into the search bar, but it came up with no results. He did, however, see the information of this world in the user bar.

‘Weakening degree of current world: -12 (all levels reduced by 12 levels, minimum level Mortal, Level Zero.)’

“…Tsk-tsk, twelve levels, no wonder it’s so crazy here, such an oppression is just downright nuts.” Garen bet that Kong Xinxue and crew’s wish to hire a powerhouse would go up in smoke, what kind of a powerhouse could withstand that twelve-level reduction and still manage to fight that so-called indestructible Slayer?

Even the six-thousand-year-old faerie, Nine-Tailed Fox, had been weakened so far as to become a regular person, what was more anyone else.

Garen did not consider himself in the equation, because people from the Ancient Endor Mother Stream System had to discard their previous powers and leave with only their souls, so they were forced to start over from scratch every time. That was completely normal to him.

But it was different for the other power systems.

Closing the Quest tab, he pressed the News tab next.

‘Demon World Information Exchange’, ‘ Xianxia ^1 World Information Exchange’, ‘Martial Arts World Information Exchange’, ‘Wilderness World Information Exchange’, ‘Latest Updates on World Changes’

‘Encyclopedia of Forbidden and Dangerous Areas’.

There was a ton of information along those lines, all crammed in there.

Garen just browsed through them briefly.

There was also a page for asking questions and requesting help in the News tab.

Garen pressed it, and found a chatroom space. There were people chatting in there, but they seemed to be reaching the end of their conversation.

“Thanks for your help, Silly Bear, I feel a lot better now. No matter how hard the going gets, I’m still a Transmigrator, so I gotta still make something of myself!” — typed the user called Carlos.

“Just try your best! Good luck!” — Silly Bear replied encouragingly.

“Help requested: I’ve been reincarnated as a sprig of grass in the middle of the road, and now I get run over every day, what do I do?” — Lil’ Grass.

“…” — Silly Bear.

“You get used to it once you get run over enough times… My condolences.” — Flying Divine Wings.

“Help requested: My mom was killed! My dad’s still outstation, I have a hoe and two water buckets, and I plan to fight them to the death, anyone got any good suggestions?” — Whole Family Died.

“…Do you know martial arts?” — Silly Bear

“No, I just possessed this idiot kid’s body this morning, and in the afternoon…” — Whole Family Died.

“…It’s a low martial arts world, huh… It’s okay, it’ll just hurt for a while. As long as your soul is unharmed…” — Gothra Number 1.

“…..” — Whole Family Died.

“Excuse me, anyone here knows how to make beans sprout?” — Beanie.

“You wanna grow bean sprouts?” — Silly Bear.

“Nah, I just accepted a quest, it’s a compulsory advancement quest from the academy’s teacher, every one of us has to germinate a hundred buckets of bean sprouts within twenty days… The teacher said that if a Sorcerer can’t even make bean sprouts, they might as well go die!” — Beanie.

“What the heck does bean sprouting have to do with sorcerers!” — Silly Bear.

“Yours sure is weird…” — Apollo.

“No one would come here asking if it was a regular quest that wasn’t weird… C’mon, help me out, I’m dying here!” — Beanie.

Garen laughed as he read, compared to these tragic Transmigrators, he suddenly felt that his own adventures were perfectly great. His mood was a lot lighter, and more importantly, he no longer felt as though he was always the only one fighting, the only one moving forward. This sort of feeling gave him a true sense of belonging, and of acknowledgment.

Soon enough, another question popped up.

“Help requested: I have Human-Level martial power, how do I defeat a Fire Demon unharmed?” — Snow Mountain

“Who do you think you are, Ximen Chuixue ^2 !? If I can do it unharmed, why would I still be here? The heart core of a Fire Demon is worth two hundred Contribution Points per pop, why wouldn’t I be out there earning it for myself?” — Kadaj

“My wife cheated on me, my brothers teamed up to summon a Fire Demon to off me, and they’re supported by the High-Speed Life Halo and Holy Prayer Light up there that my parents just cast. C’mon, guys, help me.” — Snow Mountain

“…Just how bad do you have it, your wife brothers and parents are all working together to get you!” — Kadaj

“I can’t help it, issa long story.” — Snow Mountain

“Hire someone.” — Silly Bear

“Excuse me, do I add soy sauce when frying tomatoes?” — Cooking God.

“…” — Kadaj

“…” — Snow Mountain

Garen laughed as he continued reading, constantly refreshing the chat history and the help requests since he had nothing better to do.

********************

Since he found out about Lighthouse, Garen’s mood has been getting even lighter. Whenever he had free time, he would constantly go through the news, information, and quests on the forums. Most of the quests required leaving this world and heading to another, and the transmigration process costs a fee in Contribution Points. The points needed to enter different worlds varied as well.

So now he still did not have points to let him transmigrate to other worlds, and besides, this world might still have that Soul Energy he was interested in. That was why he had no plans to leave for now.

But even so, he had managed to drastically widen his horizons.

He also knew now that other than the Mother Stream System, there were actually so many more different systems. Each of these systems started from the basics and moved on to the higher level studies, but of course they all required uniform Contribution Points.

Garen also set up a martial arts teaching course there, in which he explained some basic and common tips for martial arts. It was very useful for some rookie Transmigrators.

And before he knew it, his physical fitness had increased as well. The nourishment of the Soul Energy and the way his Saber Art trained his internal organs meant that he was soon at this body’s current limit. Plus, his Soul Limit had long since been increased to an average of fifty thanks to his Soul Seed, so even after he achieved the physical limits of the human body in this world, Garen’s physical fitness did not stop increasing. Instead, it continued to surge upward.

The days passed one by one, and Garen felt unprecedentedly fascinated and relaxed. His nerves, pulled taut over the past few worlds, also began to loosen up somewhat.

In these days of meaningless rest and relaxation, he also discovered, to his surprise, that the rate of his Soul Energy production was slowly starting to increase. The Soul Energy in his Soul Ring increased in speed and volume. It was clearly a result of the holistic work-play, yin-yang balance he had achieved.

And before he knew it, the thing that those Transmigrators called the Plot of this world, that which Garen had once called the fate of the general trend, finally started to move again.

*******************

In a small, dark alley in Lily of the Valley.

Silver Chain wore a black coat, a mask, and a cap, hiding his face completely as he sat beside the trash cans all alone.

The cries of the wild cats and dogs rose and fell in the night, and only a few passersby walked past the entrance of the alley in the distance. Other than that, there were no other noises.

These were Lily of the Valley’s slum areas, and almost no one dared to just wander around the streets at night, because these streets were far from safe.

“Silver Chain.” A tall and slender blue-haired woman abruptly appeared at the alley entrance, staring coldly at Silver Chain, who was sitting on the floor.

Her hair was tied into a tall ponytail, her long hair tied into a bunch that cascaded down the back of her head. She wore blue pearl earrings, her long and narrow blue eyes giving off a contemptuous, arrogant air.

Tap.

The woman took one step forward. She wore a skintight, dark blue pants-suit, her tall black heels stepping down hard on the cement floor, clicking loudly.

“It’s you…” Silver Chain’s voice was hoarse, as he tilted his head to glance at the newcomer.

“You disobeyed my orders,” said the woman coldly. “You even killed the person sent to watch and warn you, so surely you must know what the consequences will be.”

“You wanna kill me?” Silver Chain stood up without a single hint of emotion. “I’ve been modified, do you really think you can still beat me?!”

“Of course, I won’t be the only one.” The woman’s smile was ice-cold.

Tap… tap… tap…

More footsteps came from behind Silver Chain.

He turned around, but he saw who had arrived, his pupils dilated abruptly.

Chapter 1171: Assistance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The next day

There was a large group of people surrounding the alleyway, and amidst the buzz of discussion, several police cars stopped at the entrance, pulling up the yellow police line.

A dozen or so cops were crouching down in the alley, apparently measuring something. There was also someone dialing a number on their phone.

Yuria was walking home with some of his classmates, chatting happily as they went. The setting sun shone down on them, turning the ground into a field of pale gold.

“What’s up over there?” One of his classmates saw the crowd over there, and asked curiously.

“I saw a police car, did something happen?” another student guessed.

“Let’s go find out.” Yuria was also constantly curious about everything, so he squeezed through the crowd with his two classmates, poking their heads inside.

From a distance, Yuria could already see the body on the ground. The corpse was facing him, and it seemed that many chunks had been taken out of his body.

But the moment he saw that face, Yuria instantly froze. It was as though he had been hit straight in the head by a bolt of lightning.

For a moment there, he could not hear or see anything. The only thing that entered his eyes was the face of that man on the ground.

“That’s… Silver Chain!”

That voice abruptly echoed in his head.

“Who killed him!?” The question kept bouncing around in his brain. The first time, he had beaten Silver Chain, but could not bring himself to kill his opponent.

The second time, he let Silver Chain go again.

But the third time, if it were not for the fact that Head Minister Kong Xiaofei just happened to be passing by, they might seriously have been in danger.

Everyone had clearly seen just how powerful Silver Chain was back then, so who could be strong enough to kill him?! And what faction could have sent out a strong killing machine like Silver Chain?

Back then, why did someone order Silver Chain to obey orders and leave immediately? He had won back there, and just a second would have been enough for him to kill the two of them. At such a crucial moment, he suddenly received orders to retreat, which meant that the other party did not seriously intend to kill them.

All these questions and suspicions took over Yuria’s brain. He could not even hear his classmates yelling his name beside him.

“I need to tell my sister about this ASAP!!”

He whipped out his phone, and rang his younger sister’s number.

Just then, he felt that familiar sensation again, it was as though he was being watched. He turned around abruptly, and just managed to glimpse the corner of some black clothes.

“So there really is someone following me?!” His scalp went numb, and he hurriedly dialed that number.

The call went through almost instantly.

“Hello? Brother? What’s up?” The instant Yurijie’s voice came in through the phone, Yuria released the breath he did not know he had been holding.

“Things might be getting troublesome here on my side…” he said softly as he distanced himself from his two classmates, lest they heard something they were not supposed to.

“Is it that gang again? Vulture?” His younger sister, Yurijie, immediately caught on. “Bro, where are you?!” Her voice grew frantic.

“I’m on the way home. The guy we met last time, Silver Chain? He’s dead.” As Yuria’s voice reached the other end, Yurijie’s breathing grew audibly heavier.

“Then what should we do?!” The two of them were just normal students, their encounter with Silver Chain had already been strange and frightening to them. After that, they heard about the organization called Vulture, and the shadow of trauma in their hearts grew. If it were not for the fact that they still retained some of those mysterious skills from their childhood, the siblings probably would not have been able to stay as calm as they did. Regular people would have long since gone to the police.

Of course, it was not as though the two of them had never reported it to the police. The result was completely predictable, in that the uncles at the police station did not believe anything they said at all, hearing out their testimony as though listening to a story. If they continued on about it, they would probably have been treated as schizophrenics.

“What the heck do they want!?” Yuria’s expression grew anxious. “They could be watching over our every move, even now, because I feel like someone’s following me again. Damn this all!”

“I’ll go get Cousin Lincoln!”

“It’s no use! Cousin Lincoln doesn’t know anything, we’ll just drag him into this mess for nothing!” Yuria said quickly. “Mom’s still overseas, so she should be safe. The ones in trouble are the two of us!”

“So what should we do?” Yurijie was starting to panic as well.

“We need help!” Yuria quickly calmed down. “The enemy could kill off Silver Chain, which makes them way out of our league. That’s why we need to find someone who can truly help us!”

“You mean–!?” Yurijie suddenly thought of someone.

“Although I don’t want to do this, we have no other choice,” said Yuria helplessly.

************************

Nighttime–

Kong Family Villa

“And that’s why you two are here now?” Garen sat in his seat, picking up a cup of green tea and blowing on it gently.

“My sincerest apologies. Head Minister!” Yuria and Yurijie hung their heads in shame. “We… just could not think of anyone else who could help us… We never wanted to cause you any trouble!”

Garen shook his head and did not deny it.

“A powerhouse, huh… and one that could kill off that Cyborg, too. That would indeed be very troubling. Don’t tell me you guys blindly believed that I could take on such a terrifying peak-level powerhouse all on my own, did you?” Garen retorted. “At the end of the day, I’m just a normal person with decent training in my Saber Art. If you’re facing a psychopath or something, shouldn’t you go to the cops?”

“A normal person…” The siblings’ features twisted slightly. You’re calling yourself a normal person even after you chased away Silver Chain, who could massacre a small-sized mercenary army by himself? If Garen was a normal person, then no one on this planet was normal anymore.

“So what, do you two plan to hide out here at my place forever?” Garen sipped his tea and looked at the two in front of him, especially Yuria. This was the guy known as the Savior, but even though he was one of the Four Cornerstones, Garen could not sense any Soul Energy Aura from him at all.

“…”

“…”

The two of them were rendered speechless, they could not just come out and say that they wanted him to join them in facing that powerhouse, could they? It was not right to just ask someone else to risk their lives by getting involved in something as dangerous as this case. This had nothing to do with Garen anyway, and the assistance he had given them before this was already more than enough.

All of a sudden, an awkward silence fell over the room. The two of them were too shy to actually ask for help, while Garen was completely at peace and unwilling to talk.

Both sides stayed quiet.

Tick tick tick tick… The clock on the wall kept ticking on. Time passed slowly.

**********************

On top of a distant tower, under the cover of the night, several people dressed completely in black were expertly propping a sniper rifle against the sides of the roof.

One of them brought his eyes to the gun and looked down through the sight. Through the crosshairs, he could clearly see Garen and the siblings chatting past the glass window, absorbing every detail with unnatural ease.

Garen was dressed in white, while the siblings wore T-shirts and jeans. There was a sharp contrast between the cleanliness of one and the sloppiness of the other.

“Test his powers, and see if he deserves to join Vulture,” said one of the people in black coldly. “Ignore the other two for now.”

“We’re not a club that any Tom, Dick, or Harry can join as they please,” laughed another coldly. “If it doesn’t work out, kill him. Scum who try to join us without the powers to match should just go die.”

“Are you guys sure?” asked the person behind the rifle in a deep voice.

“Of course.” x2

The other two replied in unison. They seemed to be twins, even their voices were the same.

“Then I’ll be executing my orders.” The person propping up the gun starting to load the ammo.

**********************

Garen sat in his seat, slowly drinking his tea.

“Don’t you think that your actions will cause me and my family a lot of problems?” he said straight-facedly. “Although I don’t quite believe what you’re saying, I can’t deny that the monster from last time remains fresh in my mind, reminding me that everything might just be as you say.”

“Sorry…” said Yuria guiltily. “I’m guessing that the other side does not really plan to kill us, it’s more like they’re testing us. But last time Silver Chain nearly disobeyed them, that’s why he was killed this time. That’s most likely how it happened.”

“What my brother means to say is that we don’t really know what they’re after, but they don’t plan to kill anyone. Maybe they don’t have the guts to go against the laws of reality face-on… I think…” Yurijie hazarded a guess.

“That’s just a lie for the little kids, and you’re buying it?” Garen shook his head with a laugh. “Are you saying that the person who could kill Silver Chain would not dare to kill two regular high school students?”

The two of them exchanged helpless glances and had nothing else to say. It was true, that was clearly illogical.

“I think your best option would be to report it to the cops,” Garen reminded them. “No matter what, since they’ve chosen to hide in the dark, that means they don’t want to be paraded around in the light. The more reluctant they are to be exposed, the more we stay in populated areas. That way, wouldn’t that stop them from making their move?”

“You have a point!” Yuria’s eyes lit up, and he instantly perked up. Immediately, something occurred to him. “But Head Minister, why aren’t you ever scared? You even look a little bored, and very calm. Isn’t it normal for regular people to freak out in the face of something like this?” His gaze on Garen was instantly curious.

“That’s private and confidential, unfortunately. You just need to know that I’ve experienced something similar before.” Garen smiled. Suddenly, his pupils moved slightly, as though he had sensed something.

“You guys should leave now.” He made it very clear that they had outstayed their welcome.

The siblings both sighed helplessly.

“Thank you very much for your guidance.” As the older brother, Yuria stood up and led with a bow.

“No problem, and don’t worry. We’ll get to the bottom of this eventually, and then your life will go back to normal,” Garen comforted them.

“Sigh… Hopefully.” The two of them bid him farewell and left the villa.

They walked down the nighttime streets slowly, clearly rather down in the dumps. They had anticipated that Garen might not accept them under his wing, because no one would go to such lengths only to invite trouble for themselves. This was completely natural, even if Garen did seem extremely powerful.

“What do we do now?” asked the younger sister, Yurijie, depressed.

“It doesn’t matter what their goal is, we’ll find out everything eventually.” Yuria sighed. “All we can do now is–” Bam!!!

All of a sudden, there was the sound of glass shattering behind them.

The two of them exchanged a glance, and instantly realized that the sound had come from the Kong Family Villa behind them.

“It’s the Head Minister! Something’s gone wrong!!!”

Yuria turned around, pulled his sister’s hand, and ran back the way they had come.

Chapter 1172: Assistance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There were shards of glass all over the living room.

Garen stared coldly at the gunshot hole in the floor, and felt an inexplicable rage rise in his chest.

“I never bothered you guys, but you’ve come knocking on my door instead…?” His voice was deep and low as he looked at the direction the shot had come from.

Whoosh!

He instantly transformed into a wisp of white smoke, floating out of the living room. He dashed out through the hole in the glass, and aimed straight for the top of the tower.

Not long later, Yuria returned to the villa gates, his heart heavy, and was just in time to see Garen shoot out, heading toward the distance.

“I’ll follow him, you catch up later, Sis!” Yuria was the faster one of the two, so he quickly allocated their roles and then gave chase.

*******************

“He’s coming.” On the tower, the man who had shot off that round stood up. “He’s pretty good at dodging gunshots, you guys might be in for some trouble.”

“It’s fine, this is the best chance for us to see if he deserves to become one of us. Hehe, it’s not that easy to get into Vulture!” Someone laughed coldly.

“Whatever. Those two kids are coming too, I’m off to complete my quest.” The shooter dismantled the sniper rifle with a familiar touch, and then placed the parts into a black box. He sealed and lifted the box, walking toward the only stairway that allowed descent from the roof. Soon, he vanished into the darkness.

Only the twins remained standing on the roof of the tower, patiently awaiting Garen’s arrival.

Time passed slowly…

But soon enough.

Bam!!

There was a dull thud, and the metal door at the entrance was kicked open. It flew off and spun toward the floor nearby, clanging and rolling a few times before it finally settled down.

A white figure walked out from the stairway entrance slowly.

It was Garen, his expression as calm as a lake.

“Which one of you ambushed me?” His voice was very even, but there was a hint of impatience.

“It was all of us.” One of the twins smiled strangely.

“If you got the balls for it, come at us,” the other one chuckled.

“You’re the one who said it!”

Garen did not waste any more time talking. Pulling out his long sword with a clang, he allowed the blade to reflect a clear arc of pure white light in the dark night.

Whoosh!!

A line of bright light instantly lit up in the gap between Garen and the twins, the silver light so bright it was almost blinding.

“Spider!”

The twins stretched out their right arms at the same time, pointing at Garen.

Whoomph!

In the blink of an eye, their arms burst open like a bouquet of blossoming flowers. Their entire arm was dismantled, forming a forest of spider-like sharp metal blades. The black blades gathered like so many Metal Flowers, unnaturally sharp and cold.

And just as Garen’s silver-white Saber Light lit up, the two Metal Flowers also exploded at the same time. The blades shot out in every direction.

Psst-psst-psst…

The many metal blades instantly burst forth, like an instrument that had been pressed against a coiled spring.

Garen’s silver-white Saber Light crashed into the black Metal Flowers.

Clang!!

There was the sharp sound of metal against metal.

The Saber Light took a turn and shot forward once more. It wove around the Metal Flowers and headed toward the man on the left, aiming for his waist.

“Interesting!” The twins laughed, and gently adjusted their Metal Flowers. With a whooshing sound, a long blade appeared from within the Flowers, perfectly positioned to stand in the blade’s way.

Garen’s Saber Light changed trajectory again, and the Metal Flowers continued to move as he did. The speed of their movement was faster than the rate Garen changed the direction of his attack. After all, Garen had to move his whole body, and they just needed to wave their arms slightly.

“It’s useless,” said one of the twins with a smile. “Our Spider Arms are the strongest form of local machinization ^1 . These are equipped with extremely powerful supermagnetism, you can tell that they’re attracting your saber even as we speak, right?”

“That’s right,” said the other twin cockily. “No matter how strong your Saber Art is, you’re still nothing without a metallic weapon, and our magnetism inhibits your metallic weapons. It’s useless…”

With a whoosh, the silver Saber Light finally stopped. Garen looked at his opponents, frowning slightly.

Every time his blade was about to reach the enemy, it would be blocked by that powerful magnetic force. That power interfered with his originally perfect blade trajectory, causing it to lose its mark. That way, his Saber Art would naturally be stopped. This was also one of his Saber Art’s flaws, it put too much importance in perfect accuracy, and that ended up becoming one of its weaknesses.

“Since metallic weapons are useless…” He tossed away his steel katana, and pulled out the other weapon he always carried around with him, the wooden sword at his waist.

“A wooden sword?!” One of the twins widened his eyes. “Are you kidding me? Is there something wrong with your head?! Or do you really think that a wooden saber can cut through the Spider’s defenses?!”

“Hahahaha…!!! This is killing me! You dare use a wooden saber, the most primitive of trash weapons, to face the Spider!!” The other started roaring with laughter.

But Garen ignored them completely. According to the Plot, everyone from Vulture was completely off their rockers. They had been modified until they were neither man nor monster, and they had lost all of their humanity, becoming instead violent, rash, mindless murderers.

Trying to talk to people like them was merely a waste of breath.

Earlier, he had only used his pure, basic Saber Arts in their simplest form, and it seemed as though his weapon was inhibited by the enemy’s magnetism, so he could not achieve anything with it.

But it was fine, he just needed to change his saber. He had prepared in advance for this, too, and brought a wooden saber with him.

Gripping the wooden weapon tightly, Garen immersed himself once more into the world of Saber Art, and strolled leisurely toward the two of them.

“I’ll finish him.” One of the twins stepped out first, his smile twisted.

He raised his hand, a hint of cruel killing intent flashing through his eyes.

“Spider!”

Bam!!

His arm burst open again, and the Metal Flower that had already been in full bloom actually expanded again, growing until it was more than a meter long. It was as though he carried a large bush of black grass on his arm, with a forest of actual blades that shot out in all directions.

Just like that, he waved his arm, swinging it at Garen nimbly and quickly.

“I’ll find a path in.” Garen’s Saber Light flashed, and as he dodged the sharp blades, the agile wooden saber carved out a path with many twists and turns, threading through the gaps between all the blades. “An unobstructed path!”

Psst!

The wooden saber stabbed one of the twins right in his heart.

The twins were both stunned, and Yuria, who had just arrived on the scene in time to see it happen, was also stunned.

A cold breeze blew past them, making their clothes flap in the wind.

“Ha! Hahaha!!” The twin who was stabbed suddenly started laughing madly. “It’s no use! A wooden saber is still a wooden saber! So what if you got me!?”

He tore a chunk of his clothes off the area he was stabbed, and revealed the metal vest that he wore on his chest, directly above his heart.

“See that! This is the latest stab-resistant armor! It doesn’t matter even if you stab me with that wooden saber until it breaks!” The twin roared with laughter.

Garen pulled back his wooden sword, slightly frustrated.

Whoosh!

His figure vanished for a moment, because he had leaped backward. The Metal Flower that swept at him suddenly missed completely.

Garen landed steadily on the floor with a thud, and glanced at the tip of his wooden sword. There was already some clear signs of wear and tear.

“Now this is troubling… I never thought I’d encounter interference like this.” He knew his own condition best. Right now, his physical attributes were at an average of just over two points, meaning it was about twice that of normal adults. Although that seemed strong, the enemy was far more powerful than him in terms of physical fitness. People who have been modified were usually at least four times as strong as a regular person, and they would also have fortified many of the body’s natural weak points. He was not surprised at all to see that the wooden saber appeared to have no effect.

Swinging his wooden saber helplessly, Garen watched as the two approached him, and released a long breath.

“Looks like I gotta take this seriously now.” He swung his saber somewhat grumpily.

“Take this seriously? You’re quite the braggart, aren’t you!” one of the twins said loudly. “I’ve got a reinforced metal membrane covering me from head to toe, why don’t you just try to penetrate it? And with a wooden sword? What do you think you are, a Sword Master from ancient times?!!”

Garen looked at the two men in front of him. If they didn’t ask for it, they wouldn’t get what was coming to them. So why was it so hard for them to understand that?

Annoyed, he kept those thoughts to himself and raised his wooden saber, walking straight toward the two of them.

“There are realms in Saber Art as well.”

“Spider!!” The two voices rang out in unison.

Amidst the renewed explosion and expansion of the two blade bushes, a light brown line twisted and turned, weaving through the forest of blades. There were two faint pops.

Garen had instantly swapped places with the twins, as though through teleportation.

“It’s over.” Garen turned around and looked at the two of them.

It was as though the two of them had frozen into motionless statues.

“You– How did–?” one of the twins spoke. His pupils had widened, his breath speeding up, as though he was feeling an intense agony.

Garen’s reply was a pitying gaze.

“Sorry, this is just the most basic Penetration Force, it’s nowhere near as fancy as you think it is…”

“Then you– you just said– that–!!” What he got in response was the twins’ glare, gone mad from their unwillingness to just let it end like that.

“But don’t you think it looks cool to do that before unleashing an ultimate skill?” Garen walked around them, and then pushed their backs lightly.

Bang bang!

The two of them fell to the ground and revealed Yuria and Yurijie, standing in the stairway with absolute worship in their eyes.

“Let’s go, we’ll let the police deal with this. These two won’t be moving for a couple of hours,” Garen said offhandedly as he pulled his cell phone out of his pocket. He considered it for a moment, and turned his gaze toward the siblings.

“What are you looking at? Go on, call the cops!” He yawned. “I’m going back to sleep now.”

“Big Bro!!!” Yuria dashed at him, hugging his leg. “Please, take me in!! Cooking, cleaning, I can do it all!!!”

“Me too!!” Yurijie also pounced onto Garen’s other leg.

“Don’t do that, what if someone sees us? It’s not good for the mood around here,” said Garen exasperatedly. He shook his leg, but could not shake them off.

Yuria and Yurijie’s mood had also relaxed considerably compared to how tense they were before. This time, they had witnessed Garen take down two of the men in black from Vulture with their very own eyes, so they were in a good enough mood to joke around.

After some goofing around, not one out of the three mentioned calling the police again. It was not yet time to go into open war with Vulture, so they decided to just ignore the twins on the roof and go straight home instead.

Putting aside what Garen explained to Kong Yuan and Kong Xinxue, this incident was enough to make it so that the siblings now had absolute faith in Garen. Every day, they asked for his guidance and practiced their Saber Art seriously and diligently. They were almost religiously dedicated to it. With this, they had successfully become loyal admirers of Garen’s Saber Art, but naturally, the truth was they had become Garen’s most faithful dogs.

The other members of the Unrestricted Combat Department were fully aware of this change, and it only served to further heighten their passion for learning. Even if Garen was not around for the daily routine training, they would not slack off in the slightest as long as Yuria and Yurijie were there. Even the previous Head Minister was impressed.

Chapter 1173: Watching the Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kong Family Villa

Garen sat next to Kong Xinxue on the sofa, surfing through the television channels disinterestedly. He did not turn on the sound, however, and just kept on switching channels aimlessly.

“You jumped into it so quickly? The rhythm of the Plot, I mean?” Kong Xinxue wore white silk socks, her legs pressed together as she sat on the sofa, a dark green student dress obscuring her thighs. Although her eyes were trained on the television, her attention was clearly on Garen.

“They were the ones who came to me first, it’s not like I could have just chased them away, right?” said Garen nonchalantly. “Besides, if we follow the Plot you guys gave me, it’s not as though you and I don’t know what Vulture’s aim is.”

“True. It’s just that this way, you have no choice but to enter their line of sight ahead of time. You sure you can deal with them?” Kong Xinxue frowned.

“I can probably handle the first five, but I’ve never met the last two or Slayer, so I don’t know about them,” said Garen simply.

“You sure? Just so you know, I can barely protect myself, all I know are some basic martial arts. They’re fine for dealing with regular people, but they’re nothing in the face of those half-machinized monsters.” Kong Xinxue sighed. “Hey.” She poked Garen with her foot.

“When the time comes, you better protect me.”

“Don’t you have Yuria and the rest?” Garen did not take that to heart at all.

“Savior is still just a rookie, I’d be better off putting my trust in you over them. Just be honest! Will you or won’t you!?” said Kong Xinxue unhappily. “Although the Plot says that I’ll just end up kidnapped, and nothing worse than that will happen, this feeling still sucks. I don’t like placing my safety in the hands of those green-horned brats.”

“If you already know that everything will turn out nicely in the end, why did you come to me anyway?” Garen was exasperated.

“Are you a man or not!” Kong Xinxue used every woman’s favorite killer move.

“No.” Garen averted his gaze. “I’m a boy.”

“Don’t try to be smart with me! Just tell me straight, will you or won’t you!” Kong Xinxue was annoyed now. “If you won’t, I’ll go look for Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest! Although I don’t like her, she’s still my friend, and I’m sure she’ll help me with such a trivial matter.”

“Fine, fine…” Garen turned his face around. “But you have to promise that you won’t stray further than twenty meters away from me, or else I can’t guarantee that you won’t be dragged away.”

“Relax.” Kong Xinxue silently heaved a sigh of relief. “I’ll move into your room tonight itself!”

“…” By now Garen had already noticed that Kong Xinxue was actually a very well-disguised brother-lover. She looked stern and distant to outsiders, but when they were at home, she was particularly fond of getting touchy-feely with her own younger brother.

“Forget it, no matter what, this body still belongs to your younger brother, it’s related to you by blood,” said Garen helplessly.

“Even if I sleep on your bed, would you dare touch me?” challenged Kong Xinxue. “I haven’t found any other man as utterly harmless to women as you, pretty sure you’re the only one.”

“Could you stop trying to rile me up all the time?” Garen was annoyed now, what did she mean by utterly harmless to women? This was an insult to his character that was already beginning to involve his views on life and personal sense of value. No man would be able to take that lying down.

“Although reality is cruel, you can’t deny that it’s the truth.” Kong Xinxue gave him another taunting look.

“Then what kind of man do you think is potentially harmful?” Garen gave her a sideways look. “Someone like this?”

Whoomph.

He suddenly reached out his hand and caught Kong Xinxue’s perky breast precisely. His fingers sank deep into the flesh, his grip exceptionally steady.

Kong Xinxue instantly flushed red. Her body immediately tensed up. Although she had been challenging Garen this whole time, she only ever treated it as a joke, a way to release stress. Ever since she realized that Garen liked to do things by the books, she had slowly begun to lower her guard around him. That was why it never occurred to her that he might make a move like that.

But now, she looked down at the large hand on her chest. It had almost sunk completely inside, with nothing but the dark green school uniform standing between his hand and her skin.

His fingers were even starting to pinch and knead shamelessly. Waves of soft numbness began to surge up from her chest.

“You– That’s enough!!!” She raised her hand abruptly, slapping Garen’s left cheek with all her force.

Smack!

Garen caught her upraised hand.

“Alright, enough with the joking.” Garen pulled his other hand away from her chest, and said lazily, “Looks like you’re all big talk, when in truth you’re still a virgin.”

“What do you mean, virgin!!” Kong Xinxue was instantly enraged. “You insolent brat, you don’t know how much more experience I have compared to you! Back when I was asexually reproducing, you were still in some cranny somewhere sucking on your pacifier!”

Garen watched Kong Xinxue throw her tantrum lazily, and just kept nodding.

“I know, I know… I get it, you’re very experienced…”

As he droned on, Kong Xinxue suddenly fell silent. She was all in a tizzy just a moment ago, but now she was unnaturally quiet.

“What’s the matter?” Garen glanced at her, confused.

Psst!!

A glint of cold light flashed past his eyes, stabbing straight for his throat.

“What are you doing!!” Garen was completely shocked, and quickly shirked backward, avoiding the cold light.

“I’ll kill you!” Kong Xinxue was expressionless, pouncing at him with a pen in hand. The sharp tip of the pen kept aiming for Garen’s vital spots.

Although this body of Garen’s was a lot stronger in physical fitness now, it was still a mortal’s body after all. It could not yet withstand the stab of a fountain pen, and it would definitely get injured if that pen scratched him.

The two of them decided to wrestle it out on the couch.

The final victory was overwhelming.

Garen pinned down her waist and arms with one hand. Her back was pressed against him as she lay face-up on his body, and she could only struggle with her legs as he had managed to suppress the rest of her body with his immense power.

“Let go of me!”

“Stay still, why don’t you.” Garen kept Kong Xinxue locked in place with one arm, and yawned.

“Let go!!” Kong Xinxue was still putting up a struggle, but the result was clear to see. Garen’s strength was at least twice that of a normal adult man, and she had a snowball’s chance in hell in the face of such strength.

“Struggle all you want, I’m gonna sleep for a bit.” Garen closed his eyes, his head lolling to one side as he fell fast asleep. To him, Kong Xinxue’s struggling was like the resistance of a little rabbit. Even if she jabbed him a few times with the back of her hand, she could not exert her strength properly with her back against him, so he barely felt any pain at all.

He decided to just treat her like a pet, embracing her with his other arms as well, applying some force to pin down her legs.

“Alright, be good now, sleep, and don’t fuss.” Garen fell right asleep. Way back when he was learning his secret techniques, he could already fall asleep standing and wake up in the exact same pose. A position like this was child’s play to him.

He heard Kong Xinxue’s struggles grow softer and softer in volume. With the smell of her hormones and the fragrance of her long hair in his nostrils, Garen slowly drifted off into sleep.

As for Kong Xinxue, she struggled for a long time before she realized exactly who had the absolute power here. She was tired, and with a boldness befitting someone who was single, she decided to just sleep there in Garen’s embrace. Curling up slightly, she also fell asleep.

Thankfully, Kong Yuan had gone out for overtime, or else who knows how he would have broken down had he stumbled across this scene.

The younger brother held his older sister on his lap, and they slept, wrapped up in each other’s arms. They were even closer and more intimate than some honeymoon couples.

After sleeping for some time, Garen slowly stirred. He felt something sticky on his chest, and a heavy weight pressing against his body.

He opened his eyes, and the first thing he saw was Kong Xinxue’s pretty fair face, just inches away from his own. And the second thing was… a veritable waterfall of drool…

There was a ton of it, almost an ocean’s worth, and it was still flowing down from the corners of Kong Xinxue’s mouth. It had flooded his T-shirt at the chest, and continued downward, drenching a large part of his jeans as well, such that his trousers stuck to Kong Xinxue’s own dress and white silk socks, turning them both translucent.

The place where their bodies touched already felt as wet as sticky from the saliva.

“Ugh…” Garen had not been intimate with a woman in many years, and now that he had a beauty in his arms, his blood was beginning to race. In his endless pursuit of even greater strength, he had always considered relations with the opposite sex an indulgence of the heart, and a waste of time. In order to make sure his determination did not falter, he never actively sought out anything of the sort.

But if the food was already at his mouth, he did not mind eating it.

For example, right now…

Just as Garen was about to make his move, Kong Xinxue woke up as well.

The way she awakened was slightly strange. Instead of opening her eyes slowly, her eyes just flew open in an instant. Her pupils were bleary at first, but they cleared quickly.

“Now can you let go of me?” she said coldly. Her body felt all sticky and gross, she simply could not stand it.

“Your dress is completely drenched.”

Garen was amused.

“It’s my own fluids, nothing to do with you!” Kong Xinxue retorted, turning bright red, but she did not notice that her choice of words made things seem even more suggestive.

“Alright, alright.” Garen finally relaxed his grip on her.

Kong Xinxue got up. Her dress and white silk were plastered together, pressed against her skin and revealing the exact curve of her bottom. She could clearly feel the hot, hard stick between Garen’s legs pressing against her dress, and instantly her face turned even redder.

“That’s as far as this goes!” She covered her butt with her hands, turning around to face Garen. “If you ever dare mention what happened today to Nine-Tailed Fox, I’ll kill you!!” she said fiercely, but in Garen’s eyes, she looked just like a little bunny acting all coy.

“Yes, yes…” Garen laughed.

*******************

Yuri family home

Inside the large brown-red house, the door to the first-floor living hall was suddenly flung open.

“I’m back, Mom!” Yuria’s black hair was refreshingly short, and he walked inside, dressed in white gym clothes. Removing the keys from the door, he tossed his bag onto the couch.

“Mom?!”

He yelled again.

There was no response from the second floor.

“Did she go out?”

Yuria closed the door, and poured himself a cup of water from the dispenser, chugging it down. Once his thirst was satiated, he ran up the stairs to the second floor.

“Mom?”

He pushed open the door to his mother’s bedroom, and his pupils dilated abruptly.

His mother’s orange-yellow room was a complete mess.

The clothes from the wardrobe were strewn all over the place, her cosmetics scattered on the floor and on the bed. A large chunk of the curtains had been yanked down, and there was a huge hole in the middle of her window.

There were also some white and yellow scratch marks on the ground, but he had no idea what left them.

Yuria walked inside, his expression solemn. Avoiding the marks, he crouched down and began to examine them.

“It does not look like a battle… or even if it was, there wasn’t much of a fight. The ransacking came later. The footprints on the floor overlap the marks from before…”

He deduced calmly.

“There were probably two different groups of people.”

Although he was crazy with worry, he knew that it was no use panicking. He had to stay calm if he wanted to get to the bottom of this and find any clues!

Pulling out his cellphone quickly, he dialed Yurijie’s number directly.

Beep… After just one ring, the call went through.

“Brother?”

“Mom’s missing.” Yurijie did not mince any words, going straight to the point.

Chapter 1174: Watching the Battle

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Mother…!” Yurijie’s breathing became heavy. “I’ll be back right away!!” She was participating in the Unrestricted Combat Department’s training exercise.

After hanging up the call, only then did Yuria feel that he was being a little impatient. He should not have called his sister before thoroughly verifying it.

He immediately called his mother’s working unit to inquire about the situation. He also called up the aunties who always hung out with his mother to ask more questions.

But no one said that they had seen his mother.

The hint of luck in his heart wore down with each telephone call. It was not until the last call that he was absolutely certain that his mother was indeed missing.

“Vulture…..!” He put down his phone and his eyes expressed hatred for the first time.

Whoosh… Suddenly, a cool breeze blew up the curtains.

The curtains rose and at the bottom of the edge of the covered window was a note of similar color to the window sill attached there.

Yuria rushed over with a stride. He seemed to see new hope again. “Hopefully, it is the clue left by Mother!!” His heart was anticipating.

Tearing off the note by the edge and reading it.

‘Go to Zhaotong City and look for someone named Owl. He will tell you everything.’

Behind it was an address.

“It’s Mother’s handwriting!” Yuria’s eyes suddenly brightened up. “So she must be fine!”

He breathed out a sigh of relief. As long as he knew that his mother was all right, everything could be easily handled.

Walking out of the bedroom, his eyes were dull as he stood by the fence of the second floor. Once his highly stressed spirit relaxed, he instantly felt a little tired.

“I really don’t know what’s going on with this world!” He murmured. The people who appeared to be normal were one by one becoming abnormal. If his mother’s message was true, then it was very likely that many things were kept hidden.

Why were he and others being trained together in various skills by his uncle from an early age? Now that he thought about it, those skills were very likely to be used against humans and were not the skills to hunt some kind of wild animal.

Moreover, the inexplicable emergence of the Vulture and how he became one of the Four Great Cornerstones out of the blue. Everything was becoming more and more mysterious.

He took out the phone again and dialed his cousin brother, Lincoln’s number. The only person he could think of at this time was his cousin.

Unfortunately, there was a busy signal on the phone.

“Whew…” He let out a long breath and felt extremely irritated in his chest. Unexplainable incidents were continuing to occur, making the doubts in his heart grow stronger.

Suddenly, an inexplicable piercing sensation emerged in his chest.

“This is…?” He panicked and abruptly rolled to the left.

Boom!

A small firecracker sound was heard. On the floor where he had originally stood, there was a small white hole which was pluming white smoke.

“Gunman!! It’s a penetrating sniper rifle!” The knowledge of various weapons taught by his uncle immediately emerged in his mind.

There was a sniper aiming in the distance!

All the exhaustion in Yuria was swept away, and his whole body entered into a state of high concentration.

He abruptly rolled to the left again and hit a vase, causing it to shatter into pieces all over the floor, but there was another clear hole at his previous position.

“The ability to shoot through the wall. It is definitely a thermal imaging device, and the distance shouldn’t be far!”

He recalled the Vulture gunman whom he failed to catch the last time. In the aftermath analysis, they had confirmed that it was definitely not fired by those two people. According to the traces left at that time, there should have been a third person at the scene, but only two individuals were spotted at that time.

One rush forward and then a roll on the ground. Yuria made an L-shaped route, and there was another bullet hole in front of his path.

The intense crisis threatened every cell in his body causing them to unleash his strongest potential.

After dodging two consecutive shots, he finally rushed out of the building and ran an S-route, dashing toward the gunman.

From far away, he saw that at the window of a building nearby, a man clothed in black was retracting his firearm and giving him a look from the distance.

On the way home from not far off, Yurijie was also quickly running over here.

“Pursue!” She had apparently heard the gunshots and was carrying a long saber on her back. She was well-prepared.

Without saying a word, they both rushed towards the building.

The surrounding environment was very strange. There should be many pedestrians at this time, but it was the opposite of that. Not even a figure could be seen. It seemed that someone had deliberately alienated the crowd.

There was an unpleasant smell in the air and there was no telling what it was.

The two gave a mad pursuit and finally intercepted the other party on the slope of the gateway of a residential road.

“Stand still!” Yuria roared.

The other party actually stopped in his tracks.

Turning around, this man in a black trench coat revealed his face.

Thick eyebrows and calm eyes which gave a feeling of calmness like water.

“What do you want to say?” The man asked faintly.

“Where did you take my mother to?! Speak out!” Yuria suppressed his anger and anxiously shouted.

The man did not answer immediately but looked strangely at Yuria and his sister.

“Looks like you two really don’t know anything…”

“Know what?!!” Yurijie slowly pulled out the saber from the side, and her look was solemn. Obviously, she was going to make it a quick fight. Her Saber Art had soared recently, and she had very strong confidence in her own skills. After all, she was also trained as a child. Now, she was just integrating the stuff from the combat area into her Saber Art. The essence had not changed.

“Enough with the talk, take him down first!” Yuria was disinclined to say anything more. He simply pulled out the dagger that he carried with him and lunged forward.

***********************

In another window far away.

Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox stood side by side at the window, each holding a pair of binoculars and watching the battle between Yuria and the gunman from afar.

Nine-Tailed Fox was wearing a black blouse and a short white skirt with long black stockings. Her slim and long legs stood closely together without a gap. Coupled with the young appearance of a beautiful girl, the combination of purity, loveliness and sexiness revealed a peculiar temptation.

“That is Hai Feng,” she grinned and said. “So how is his strength?”

Garen did not answer and watched for a little while more before putting down the binoculars in his hand.

“What is his half-mechanized part? Why does it feel a little weird?”

“His ability could not be noted by the general people. Those who do not know the inside story will think that he has no ability at all and did not accept any modification,” Nine-Tailed Fox revealed a fox-like smile. “But in actual fact, he has the most secretive ability in the Vulture – Floral Scent.”

“It’s smell?!” Garen was enlightened.

“Yes. It’s smell,” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded. “It’s neither a harmful gas, nor it is poisonous. It’s just a catalyst.”

“A catalyst?”

“Yes,” Nine-Tailed Fox turned around and leaned back against the window sill. “A special gas that can accelerate the opponent’s physical exertion. At the same time, there will also be a certain hypnotic effect. It’s very subtle.”

“It’s impossible to guard against it,” Garen said as he nodded. “His own combat level is also very strong. This way, the opponent will unknowingly slip into the effect of his scent and lead to excessive physical exertion.”

“Hai Feng is a relatively cold person in the Vulture, but he is also a very special person,” Nine-Tailed Fox laughed.

“Special?”

“You will know as you continue to watch.”

She quietly approached Garen and the thighs wrapped in black silk gently rubbed against Garen’s right leg. The same faint hint of sweetness was emitted, slowly filling the air.

*******************

Yuria punched Hai Feng’s abdomen, but it was avoided by the other party. Instead, he himself was almost cut at the arm by his sister’s saber.

The three people fought together in the middle of the slope. From time to time, there would be flashes of swords, reflecting bright white lights.

Yurjie’s saber continued to sweep across Hai Feng’s body again and again and they would be just millimeters away from him but never actually hit him.

Yuria’s fists and legs were also synchronised as if they were acting together. He would come into contact with the other party just by a little bit more every time.

“You only know how to dodge?! Damn!!” Yuria shouted and was rather mad. He was a person who was calm on the surface but actually rather impulsive on the inside. Otherwise, the last time his cousin brother was kidnapped, he would not have rushed to rescue him without saying anything.

Now that he felt like being played by the other party in the combat, his anger began to rise.

“Dodge?” Hai Feng said plainly, “I just don’t want to kill you all.”

“What purpose do you have?!” Yurjie gave a vertical slash with her saber, but it was easily avoided by him.

“Hasn’t your teacher taught you not to use all your strength when you slash?” Hai Feng calmly said and was actually not short of breath at all.

“No need for you to tell!” Yuri was furious, and she slashed even harder. But still, she could not hit the person.

“Second-rate Saber Art, third-rate talent,” Hai Feng evaluated coldly. “Learning this kind of Saber Art means that you will only be at this level for the rest of your life.”

****************

“This guy… is rather annoying,” Garen remarked unpleasantly.

The Saber Art was taught by him. Although he did not put much heart into it, being rated by other people as second-rate made him somewhat less than pleased.

“Hehe… Isn’t what the person said the truth?” Nine-Tailed Fox covered her mouth and teased. “Who asked you not to teach seriously? You didn’t even teach in accordance with the student’s aptitude.”

“They will be on their own paths sooner or later anyway. I was thinking that since there wouldn’t be much use with what I teach, it would be better to just simply give some pointers,” Garen shrugged.

“How about you go and teach him some lessons, let him know what the real Saber Art is like?” Nine-Tailed Fox probed Garen’s strength.

Since they did not intend to escape from the development of the Plot, the Transmigrators who practiced martial arts would become the targets everyone would seek out for.

Among them, Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox were naturally one of them. Nine-Tailed Fox seemed to have a good impression of Garen and intended to take him in to join her force. Now that there was another reason, it was all the more justifiable to come into direct contact.

Garen also understood that it was either Kong Xinxue or Nine-Tailed Fox who were the so-called sacrificial bodies who lured him in so he could be labor for them. He would not be that stupid and swallowed the temptation. As for taking action, he decided to look at the situation before doing anything.

He was now planning to check out what the Four Great Cornerstones’ Soul Energy Aura was all about and to see whether they could be used. The other was to complete some quests to earn some quest points and to go to the Lighthouse Headquarters to have a look. Everything else must concede to these two goals.

Chapter 1175: Naval Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!

There suddenly came an explosion from the fierce battle over on Yuria’s side. The sound traveled far away and it immediately attracted many people to look out of their window.

“It will be over soon,” Nine-tailed Fox whispered.

“Yeah… Vulture wouldn’t want to attract too much attention,” Garen nodded. “We should also go check it out.”

“You want close contact?”

“Why not?” Garen smiled and turned around to walk toward the door.

************************

Cough cough cough…

Yuria coughed violently with his head down. His entire body was covered with the dust from the explosion.

His sister, Yurijie, was still fine, holding the saber and covering a side of her nose.

Hai Feng had disappeared. He threw out a ball-like thing and instantly disappeared like a ninja. This caused the two to be completely unable to react in time.

“How did this guy flee?!” Yuria said helplessly.

“What do we do now, brother?” Yurijie approached him and asked feebly.

“It’s alright. You have me,” Yuria recalled the writing on the note. “Zhaotong City. If Mother is really there, let’s go find her!” He said earnestly.

“Leave here?” Yurijie was a little saddened.

“Yea… We have no choice now, this is the only thing that can be done,” Yuria smiled wryly. “Let’s leave this place first and talk later.”

He took his sister’s hand and quickly ran in the other direction.

Too many things had happened today. They had to find a place to collect their thoughts and think about what to do next.

They ran a few streets, took a cab, and went home.

Standing outside of their door house, Yuria and his sister were somewhat hesitant as they did not know if they should live there. Obviously, the other party had already found their home, so it was no longer safe.

“Take our money and passbooks, let’s go to Zhaotong City!” Yuria spoke assertively.

“We can go to cousin brother….” Yurijie hesitated.

“Don’t involve other people!” Yuria shook his head. “This is our own matter.”

Yurijie bit her lip, and her cheeks slightly blanched.

“Brother, I’m afraid…” She gently leaned on Yuria’s body.

Holding her sister in his arms, Yuria’s face showed unprecedented steadfastness.

****************

In a coffee shop in the distance, Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox sat together.

“They want to leave,” Garen frowned.

“Rest assured, they will come back,” Nine-Tailed Fox replied without any concern.

“I’m not sure about the details behind, but since we are now involved, I am afraid that the general trend of the events will be affected and changed,” Garen said frankly.

“What can happen just by following them?” Nine-Tailed Fox curled a lock of her hair with her right finger. “In any case, you just have to stay here. He is now replacing the initial Unrestricted Combat Head Minister, Xian Tuguan’s character, who is also super strong in Sword Art and has given out many pointers to Yuria and his sister in the enlightenment of martial arts. However, it’s a pity that he went missing later on. He probably went to university after graduation and did not appear in the original Plot anymore.”

“Alright then, since you said so.” Garen nodded casually.

However, even though he replied as such, as he watched Yuria and the sister embrace each other, he kept feeling as if something was amiss.

“The feelings of these two little fellows are a bit too much…” He rubbed his chin. “Am I too sensitive in this area?”

“Waiter, two more pots of boiled water,” Nine-Tailed Fox began to call out again.

“Nonetheless, aren’t you the head of the biggest gang in the country? How come you appear to have nothing to do all day and just follow me everywhere?” Garen asked with a slight curiosity.

“What do you mean by having nothing to do?” Nine-Tailed Fox’s eyes opened wide. “Without your knowledge, I have already conducted a high-level exchange of information with the waiter, who is an intelligence officer. Through the simple act of asking for two more pots of boiled water, I have briefed the way to manage thirteen tasks and given the review comments of two major resolutions! It’s just that you don’t know!”

“Do you dare brag even more?” Garen was speechless.

“Thank you for your compliment,” Nine-Tailed Fox lifted her head like a cute little hen and laughed heartily.

“Actually, it is not like how you think it is. I mainly have two very reliable deputies who are helping me with all the affairs. That is why I can go about this idly,” she replied properly.

“Is that so?” Garen raised the coffee and sipped it.

Wumpth wumpth!

Suddenly, the cafe’s door was pushed open.

A figure that made Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox slightly startled walked in. It was actually Kong Xinxue!

This fellow was wearing a white T-shirt and skinny jeans and dressed in a sporty look. Her long red hair was hung down loosely behind and her eyes were proudly glancing around in the café before finally locking in on Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox.

Her expression was solemn and her chest was a little breathless. She seemed to have ran over here and was a little fatigued.

“You two!” She strode over and slumped into the seat beside Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox. “When did the two of you get together? So intimate and inseparable still, for fear that others don’t know that you two are a couple. Tsk tsk, even the cups used are the same couple’s cup!”

She picked up a cup and made an expression of disgust.

“Such intimacy disgusts me.”

“Hey, how did you make this out to be a couple’s cup? All the cups in this place are the same, alright?” Garen held the cup and did not see any connection between his cup and Nine-Tailed Fox’s.

“She just simply loves to be garrulous. Couldn’t speak a single word in her last lifetime and could only use the flagellum. Do you know what a flagellum is? It’s those kinds of long, thick, hard…” Before Nine-Tailed Fox could finish her words, her mouth was immediately clamped by Kong Xinxue’s hand.

“Alright. I’ll cut to the chase now. I represent the other people who are looking for you guys to comprehend the situation,” The most intolerable thing for Kong Xinxue was to have someone mentioning about her reincarnation as an E. coli in her last lifetime, and unfortunately, Nine-Tailed Fox loved to bring up this matter.

“How is the situation now? From what I heard from them, you two have been following the situation.” She looked at Garen and asked.

“Still alright. It didn’t change much from the original Plot. Although there were a few differences, they were quickly corrected,” Garen frankly replied. “Besides us, who else is following this closely?”

“There is also an old uncle who lives in the suburbs of the city and is a combatant. He wants to get the mechanical modification technology from the Vulture, so he had contacted me asking for help,” Kong Xinxue said as she let go of Nine-Tailed Fox. “As you know, the mechanical modification technology has a wide range of application and belongs to the low restriction technology that many worlds can use freely. So what that uncle means is that we cooperate and then put it on the forum to trade. The contribution points acquired will be divided into half.”

“He can dream on. Why half the profit? Will the forum be lacking this kind of technology?” Nine-Tailed Fox responded disdainfully. “It’s he himself that wants it but is just looking for an excuse. How did you reply him?”

“That person’s strength is quite good. I intend to borrow his power to follow up the Plot together and pass the intelligence back at any time to prevent any sudden danger from happening,” Kong Xinxue replied in a low voice.

“That will work too. After all, with only the three of us, it’s still a few too little. With only five in total, there are really too few combatants in this area. The ones that can be really deployed are the three of us,” Nine-Tailed Fox shook her head. “Sigh… This is the kind of thing I would just need order countless do. Unfortunately, that was in the past and now I can only do this by myself… Sigh…”

“Zhao Wenzhen, don’t think that I don’t know that thought of yours. All of my younger brothers from their head to toes belong to me, Kong Xinxue, alone! You go back to where you came from! You are not qualified enough even if you wanted to snatch my things!” Kong Xinxue’s threat appeared weak and feeble no matter how one looked at it.

“Yo… How mawkish?” Nine-Tailed Fox giggled. “All belong to you? Have you…done that already?”

“None of your business!” Kong Xinxue’s face reddened.

Garen sat by the side and watched the excitement like a spectator.

Nine-Tailed Fox shifted her gaze. “Younger brother Garen, don’t be fooled by this pure look of Ah Xue’s. What she loves is not your heart, but your body. This fellow is a profound brother controller and will only control all your actions. When she lived with me back then, the number of rotten girl novels could be piled up into a mountain! All she reads is bromance stories!”

“It’s alright. I don’t mind,” Garen replied lavishly. “The body is fine too.”

“I mind!” Kong Xinxue smacked hard on the table. “Alright, back to the point. Zhaotong City, are you all going?”

“Not going,” Nine-Tailed Fox said calmly.

Garen also shook his head. “It’s too far and I don’t feel like moving…” His indolent look made Kong Xinxue furious.

Pap!

“I’m going to go!” Kong Xinxue smacked the table fiercely.

“You’re going?” Garen asked puzzlingly, “What can you do by going there?”

“Overseas business! The original Plot is that she went out at this time and was taken away” Nine-Tailed Fox put in from the side. “Our younger sister, Ah Xue, is actually crying out in the depths of her heart. Come on~~ Come on~~ I beg you to quickly come and protect me!” She giggled. “She is really suggesting that you go with her. Although her mouth won’t say so, her body is very honest~~~”

“Is that the case?” Garen immediately looked at Kong Xinxue and blinked.

“Is your head!” Kong Xinxue’s cheeks suddenly reddened until they were like bleeding. “As soon as I think about being taken hostage by the bad guys, feelings of anxiousness take over, which indicates that I am still in the category of the normal person’s psychological state. Is there something wrong with this?”

“Of course there’s nothing wrong with that, but the way you express it is too lovey-dovey as opposed to your initial cold and hostile stand,” Nine-Tailed Fox purposefully hit the nail on the head.

“Younger brother Garen will definitely be happy to accompany you. As he sees you in this amorous look now, he is already unable to hold it in any longer,” Nine-Tailed Fox’s malignant tongue was no different. “Once I think of the both of you enjoying the world of two people alone in the vast sea, doing the ** and ** things every day, I will be so happy, it would be unbearable! Tell me, cute little Garen, is what I said true?”

She shifted her gaze to Garen who was beside her.

“Absolutely right!” Garen gave a thumbs-up and joined in resolutely.

“You guys! Both of you!!” Kong Xinxue was so mad that she stood up, her face quickly flushing.

Chapter 1176: Naval Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Us? What’s with us?” Nine-Tailed Fox loosened her fingers around her long curly hair with a triumphant smile. “You want to fight me without letting your inner personality out? Don’t bite off more than you can chew. Well, don’t stand there like a defeated hen. Bring into play your cute little mind, let us see the situation you’re in control of.”

“The situation she’s in control of? What situation? Ah Xue has some kind of special ability?”

“Don’t you know?” Nine-Tailed Fox stared widely. “The reason Ah Xue could become a territory leader is because she can collect a lot of special intelligence that ordinary people cannot grasp through her powerful intelligence gathering-capabilities.”

“Special intelligence?” Garen was piqued.

“Of course, Ah Xue’s special ability is… mhmm!!” Nine-Tailed Fox was once again fiercely clamped by Kong Xinxue’s hand.

Garen shook his head speechlessly and looked at the two good sisters. Although they appeared to be in disharmony, they actually still cared and valued each other deeply on the inside.

“If you’re talking about protection, I think you’d better not go. Wait for us to come back from Zhaotong City and go with you,” he gave it some thought. “Don’t be restricted by the original Plot. You are now an independent individual, no longer the original Kong Xinxue, so your every move can affect the situation.”

“That’s settled then. Wait for us to return and then we’ll go together with you, no problem?” Nine-Tailed Fox decisively called the shots.

“Whatever!” Kong Xinxue snorted.

******************

Zhaotong City.

The trading city by Red Nation’s seaside had a prosperous economy and more or less foreign-style buildings. It was the foreign trading city which ranked third in Red Nation.

Every day, hundreds of thousands of huge containers were constantly being transported from here into the mainland.

The containers here were much larger than those on the Earth, and each one was transported by a large ship.

Yuria’s and his sister’s eyes were wide open as they stuck their head out of the car’s window. Looking at the huge container that was being lifted up on the dock, their faces were clearly filled with amazement.

“So big…”

“That is,” the uncle driver laughed. “This kind of container is only available in Zhaotong City. There are very few such huge things that could be transported into the rest of the area.” He said with pride. “Are you here for tourism or visitation? Since you’re here, you should roam about the fun places in the vicinity.”

“We…are here to visit our relatives,” Yuria hesitated and answered softly.

He held Yurijie’s hand tightly. The two sat together and all of Yurijie was almost stuck to his body.

“Don’t worry,” he whispered.

The uncle driver did not notice it and was still talking loquaciously about some of the local features.

Soon, the taxi stopped at the address left by Yuria’s mother on the note.

No.178, Tingshan Road.

It was an independent small bungalow with a seaside villa in front and behind it. It had a very foreign feel, but it seemed a bit quiet.

After getting off the taxi, Yuria paid for the fare. He then took out the note and looked at it again.

“It should be here. Let’s knock on the door.”

“Yea,” Yurijie nodded, went forward, and lightly tapped the door. She also pressed the doorbell.

Very soon, there was movement by people on the inside.

A woman in a white maid dress walked out quickly. She reached the iron-gate and looked at the two siblings.

“May I know…who are you looking for?” She asked with some hesitation.

“May I know if this place is…” Yuria did not know how to ask, whether he should directly inquire if this was Owl’s house? What a joke that would be. What was written on the note was clearly the nickname instead of the person’s name.

“We are the children of Ms. Mafelle, and we’re here to visit the owner of this place. Please pass the message,” It was the sister on the side, Yurijie, who reacted quickly instead and immediately changed to another way of saying.

“Ms. Mafelle… I will go and ask the owner…” The maid nodded, turned around, and ran to the bungalow.

**************

“Do you think this is that Owl’s address?” Nine-Tailed Fox stood in front of Garen with her buttocks jutted out. The short black skirt and legs with white stockings were uncovered before Garen. One just needed to angle the phone correctly and would easily be able to capture the scenery at the bottom of the skirt.

Even Garen’s hand was only one slap-width away from the white silk legs in front. He could touch Nine-Tailed Fox’s thigh and buttocks with just a slight lift of his hand, and he could even feel the faint heat of the body temperature from his partner’s legs.

“This woman…is absolutely seducing me,” Garen resisted the impulse of his body. He always had absolute vigilance for this woman, Nine-Tailed Fox. Compared with the slightly simpler Kong Xinxue, he felt that that the person with Dissociative Personality Disorder might be safer instead.

“What did you just say?” he asked.

“I said, do my legs look good?” Nine-Tailed Fox turned her head around and made a pure and cute expression.

“Looks good,” Garen nodded.

“Want to touch?”

“Yea.”

“Then why don’t you do it?” Nine-Tailed Fox cocked her head puzzlingly.

“Because you are different,” Garen smiled.

Nine-Tailed Fox pouted her mouth and wanted to say something, but there was already someone coming out from that side.

The two of them were hiding on the edge of a large container, sneakily sticking out their heads to watch that side. Seeing that someone had come, they stopped chattering.

Garen watched from afar and saw a fat man coming out of the bungalow, swaying his way and opening the door to invite Yuria and the sister in.

“Is that Owl?” he asked.

“Yea. His nickname is Owl, but his real name is Galouro. He’s a weapon merchant,” Nine-Tailed Fox straightened her back. “Oh, how exhausting!”

“Nine-Tailed.” A man’s voice suddenly came from behind the two people. It was very bright, giving people a happy and eager feel. “Finally, I have found you.”

Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox turned around and saw a man getting down from a red sports car behind them. He was tall and the sunny type. He had a crew cut, bronzed skin, and was wearing sunglasses, giving off a strong sense of a black man.

His eyes glimmered as he stared at Nine-Tailed Fox and strode over.

“What are you doing here? You didn’t say anything after coming to my territory!” The man walked to the front of Nine-Tailed Fox and was all smiles.

“Is there anything? I am chatting with my friend,” Nine-Tailed Fox showed a sweet smile.

“This is?” The man looked at Garen and revealed a hint of hostility.

He was also very young, probably in his twenties. With black earrings, a strong body, and striking and clean features, he was very handsome.

“Garen,” Garen reached out and shook hands with him. He noticed that the other person’s line of sight stayed on the two sabers worn around his waist.

“Reid. Nice to meet you,” The man had a very graceful smile.

“Likewise.” Garen also smiled. Although this body of his was only a juvenile, it had been strengthened by the Soul Energy. It was not the little muscles he originally had and he was stronger than before and not weaker than the other party. Except for his height, the rest were more oppressing. Even though he had an ordinary T-shirt and jeans on, the double sabers from his waist made his whole person emit an upright dangerous sense.

“You speak succinctly. Serve in the army before?” Reid asked casually.

“No.”

“We could have some exchange of communication when there’s time. I have served in the Razer Special Forces before. You look like you have been trained,” Reid smiled and was somewhat hostile.

“Sure.”

Only then did Reid impatiently turned his gaze and looked at Nine-Tailed Fox.

“Since you’re here at my place, you should allow me to entertain you at least once? Otherwise, you’re not giving me face!”

“I was thinking of going out to the sea alone with my friend… Would it be very troublesome for you?” Nine-Tailed Fox whispered, showing an embarrassed expression.

“No, absolutely not. With such a beauty like you by the side, no man would feel troubled. Hahaha…” Reid chortled.

“My sister and Nero the rest are still waiting for you to have fun together. This is a good opportunity now that you’re here, we’ll all go out to the sea together! The yacht at home has not been touched for a long time, and it will rust if left unused,” Reid spoke with alacrity.

“That’s too kind of you…” Nine-Tailed Fox spoke affectedly. Her voice was so soft and gentle that Garen had goosebumps all over after hearing that.

“That’s settled then,” Reid waved his hand. “Brother Garen will come along. Everyone just be happy. Which part of the sea do you want to go to? I’ll be in charge of operating the yacht!”

So, at Reid’s kind invitation, Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox got into the sports car and went to Reid’s family’s villa. They went aboard the yacht together with a group of boys and girls who were dressed up sexily and went out to the sea.

The weather was sunny and bright. There were also a few single-person motorboats on the big yacht. Occasionally, there will be people riding the motorboats beside the yacht shouting about and laughing out loud.

The white yacht under the direction given by Nine-Tailed Fox was covertly following the merchant, Galouro, who had just set sail ahead of them.

Galouro the weapon merchant brought Yuria and the sister together out to the sea, or in other words, they went out to the sea first, while Nine-Tailed Fox and Garen followed behind.

The two ships sailed directly to a tourist island in the nearby sea region – Squirrel Island.

************************

Whoosh… Whoosh…

The blue seawater dashed against the wall of the yacht and turned into white splashes again and again. It was extremely rhythmic as if it would never stop.

Garen was topless as he lied on a sun-lounger wearing a pair of brown sunglasses. His fair skin and his strong and well-proportioned body figure caused every pretty lady who passed by to stop their gaze on him for a few seconds.

Nine-Tailed Fox had a pink swimwear and looked like the little sister next door. Her long hair was tied up into a bun, and her skin was more delicate and whiter than milk. Reid stayed by her side with the utmost concentration. The two talked and laughed towards the front of the yacht alone. No one knew what they were doing.

Garen had also just found out that Reid was the local big household disciple who was collaborating with Nine-Tailed Fox. He had been one of the suitors of Nine-Tailed Fox since long ago.

He also understood that a woman like Nine-Tailed Fox would definitely have more than one man. Compared to Kong Xinxue, although her mouth was spiteful, her private life was very pure. Feeling careful, he still preferred the kind of cleaning-living girl.

“Sure enough, I am still a good juvenile with a pure soul,” Garen could not help but sigh. He took the juice from the side and had a sip.

“Which part of this body of yours look like a juvenile?” A smiling female voice came from the deckchair beside.

Garen opened his closed eyes and pulled his sunglasses downward slightly.

What appeared in his vision was a black-haired girl in a traditional conservative black swimsuit.

The dark swimsuit was equivalent to a dress, and the skirt even covered half of the thigh. The chest was slightly raised, giving a very cute feeling.

The girl herself had a little baby fat. She walked towards Garen and sat down by his side. Her black hair that was let down was tied up again.

Chapter 1177: T-Rex 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I am a juvenile in the first place. There is no need to disguise that,” Garen replied casually. He glanced at the other party’s swimsuit. “Isn’t your swimsuit too conservative? It doesn’t fit the style on this ship.”

The girl smiled. “The same goes to you. I have seen several pretty ladies giving you the eye, but you are not tempted. You’re just honestly lying down and sleeping here.”

She took a sip of the drink.

“I just don’t like an environment that is too noisy.”

“Likewise.”

Garen replied.

The two looked at each other and felt a little relaxed. It was only when one got along with the same kind of people would they relax a little.

Ah!

Someone on the ship was thrown into the sea. It was a girl. Her chest strap was removed and thrown directly into the sea. Obviously, that person could swim, and she did not resist. It seemed that someone was yelling that a bet is a bet and one must honor it.

The girl floated in the sea and chided the other party, but she was being more coquettish. Her breasts was faintly visible in the sea, igniting the imagination of others.

“I don’t like their lives,” the girl beside Garen said, “If it weren’t for them dragging me over to make up the number, I wouldn’t have came”

“The same goes for me. If it isn’t because I have something to take care of, I wouldn’t want to waste time here,” Garen shrugged.

“My name is Annie, what about you?”

“Garen,” Garen picked up his drink and gestured for a cheers.

The two clinked their cups gently.

At this time, the sound of yachts came speeding over in the distance. Several small yachts encircled from three sides.

Garen stood up from the deckchair. He exchanged glances with Nine-Tailed Fox who was at the bow.

“Pay attention to protect yourself,” he casually said to Annie.

Before Annie had reacted and understood what was going on, she saw Garen pulled a slightly curved sword from under the deckchair.

Hiss…

The sharp blade was pulled out slowly and held in both hands. Garen pointed the tip of the saber to the ground and slowly walked in the direction of the on-coming yachts.

Sizz sizz sizz sizz…

More than a dozen dark things were thrown at a great rotating speed at the big yacht.

“Winds of Four Directions.”

Garen bent a little. Clank clank clank clank!

Four consecutive white lights lit up around him in the blink of an eye. Like a white line that was erected, it was fleeting.

More than a dozen of the dark things were cut in half as they fell onto the deck of the yacht. At this time, only did the people see clearly that they were all black grenades!

Ah!!!!

A burst of screams rang out.

“!!!” Anne was so scared that she hid behind and her mouth was barely shut.

“Hide well,” Garen casually said and looked at the bow.

Over on the other side, Nine-Tailed Fox leaped a few times and threw over a gun from the bow.

“Catch!”

“I’ll be at the front and you be at the back!” Garen said, catching the gun.

“Change position!”

The two rushed to their position with tacit understanding.

Reid roared loudly, quickly reacted and began to command his men to counterattack. On the yacht were also bodyguards whom he had brought along. When they realized the situation they were in, each of them quickly took out their guns to fight back.

He himself actually took out a submachine gun and started to fire across.

“Forewind!”

Garen rolled and leaped, thrusting forward.

Sizz sizz sizz! Three consecutive rounds of saber sounded. Three grenades were once again split into two halves and there was no explosion. At the same time, the pistol in his hand sounded. Three people in the distance were hit in the blink of an eye.

“Good marksmanship!” The bodyguard captain could not help but praise loudly.

Reid’s face was slightly darkened and he swept his submachine gun across even fiercer.

The bullets from both sides continued to rain. With Garen taking charge at the bow, he was actually able to suppress the shooting of dozens of people from the other side just by himself.

From time to time, the rebounding and ricocheting stray bullets would be simply deflected by him with his long saber. Now and then, there would a person from those who were opening fire going down. As he calmly moved his steps, the opposite was actually misfiring in the few tens of seconds, causing the bodyguards who were watching to be in a daze.

Boom!

There seemed to be a grenade explosion at the stern. After all, there were still too many people and the distance was far. The other party used a grenade gun to shoot out a grenade. The range was very far. Even if Garen was powerful, he was only one person with a gun.

One could clearly feel the yacht sinking. Obviously, there were kelpies under water chiseling the ship.

“The ship is sinking!” Reid ran out and yelled anxiously. Immediately, he was beaten back by several bullets.

Garen was expressionless and exchanged a look with Nine-Tailed Fox at the back. “Kill and grab their boat!”

At this moment, the tacit understanding between the two was astonishing. Clearly, both sides were the type who would use unscrupulous means to achieve a purpose.

In this extremely restrictive world, even Garen could only protect himself. To deal with the long-range shots, only the same long-range shooting could be used to retaliate.

The two jumped down simultaneously and plunged into the seawater. They sped toward a yacht quickly and were as fast as they would be on the ground in the water. All who were watching were stupefied.

“Catch Nine-Tailed Fox alive!” The enemies on the opposite were shouting.

“No need. Just kill!” Someone roared out loud.

Dhak dhak dhak…

The submachine gun swept across the water and stirred up lots of splashes.

Garen lifted the tip of his saber and prodded the wall of the yacht a few times, utilizing the force to fly up and land on the deck of the yacht.

With a clank, the saber moved in a flash, and a full silver arc was drawn. The three men clothed in black who were guarding the deck and attacking the opposite side were directly swept at the neck by the tip of the saber. They looked up and dropped dead.

Blood splattered all over the ground. Springs of fresh blood were gushing out of the headless bodies.

“Get rid of him!”

The other people on the other boats turned their muzzle around at the same time.

With a whoosh, Garen disappeared from the spot and suddenly appeared behind a person. The tip of his saber pierced through the other party’s chest with a whish and was retracted again.

Then there was the second, the third, the fourth…

Undefeatable.

Just a few seconds later, blood flowed like a river on the deck. Garen carried his saber and slowly walked toward the navigation room. In it was half-lying a frightened helmsman.

“No you devil! Devil! Oh God! Save me…!” The man screamed, and his voice halted abruptly.

The tip of the saber plunged in from his chest, almost like the feel of a fork plunged into a steak. It was hard at first, but with a little effort, it would be unimpeded.

“Boring,” Garen pulled out the saber and looked at another yacht. Over there, Nine-Tailed Fox swung a ribbon-like weapon and made an OK gesture to him.

After replying with a sign, Garen slowly put the saber back into the sheath.

The sound of police siren was faintly heard in the distance and it was apparent that the maritime patrol boat was arriving. He knew that it was time for the Plot to be played out.

“This level of confrontation is not even enough to warm-up…” He stood sideways and looked at the police boat approaching from afar. The blue-and-white police boat was constantly playing the harsh siren. It was also spinning a colorful light, like a children’s toy, evoking a comical feel.

The police boat quickly drew near the several yachts that exchanged fire and a large number of police motorboats scattered and rushed toward each big yacht.

What was weird was that the attacker did not escape at all but stayed on the same spot waiting to be arrested. The exchange of fire came to a halt.

The police officers boarded the ship and went straight to both sides of the yacht. They seemed to begin to negotiate and communicate.

Reid’s face was stone-cold as he talked to a chubby man with glasses on.

Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox glanced at each other and covertly hid to the side at the back of the yacht they were on.

There was no one on the back of the yacht, and the seawater was constantly striking against the hull, making crashing noises.

Garen leaned back against the wall of the boat and obtained a black paper clip from the inside of his pants.

“How? Situation?” He asked at the paperclip.

“There will be a situation right away,” Nine-Tailed Fox’s sound came from within the paper clip. This was a short-distance contact device that Nine-Tailed Fox had given to him. One could communicate directly through a wireless signal, and it consumed very little power. It was the classic artifact among the covert walkie-talkies.

“What do you want to do with Reid?” Garen smiled and asked.

“What? Are you jealous?” Nine-Tailed Fox simpered. “Rest assured, you’re still the one whom I adore most. He is not a person of the same world as us.”

“Who you adore is none of my business. In comparison, I still like the type like Kong Xinxue,” Garen frankly spoke.

“Come on… Am I really not tempting enough?” Nine-Tailed Fox pouted. “But if Ah Xue hears this, I am afraid that she will dedicate herself to you any minute.”

Garen smiled and did not answer anymore. He pressed the paper clip and disconnected.

A helicopter was slowly flying to this side from a distance.

“Here they come…” He placed his saber against the side and arbitrarily played with the pistol which had no bullets in it.

Whup whup whup whup!

The sound of the helicopter’s propeller was getting closer and closer.

What was surprising at this time was that the police on the several yachts actually disarmed and arrested Reid and others. They were still talking and smiling earlier on, but in the blink of an eye, all of them had taken action. Without any delay, everyone including Reid were detained.

“Bring them back!” The team captain’s expression was cold.

“Lieutenant Wang, what do you mean by this!?” Reid shouted as his arms were restrained at the back by someone.

“What meaning?” The fat lieutenant sneered. “Endangering the safety of the country’s territorial waters, dare to rebel against the enforcement officers of the National Security Agency, openly killing people with guns, and ignoring the law! If I don’t arrest you and have you confess, then I’m a lieutenant for nothing!!”

“National security enforcement officers?!” Reid’s heart was stunned. Looking at the people who had previously opened fire with them, they were actually putting on the national security uniform. Suddenly, he realized that he was probably being deceived.

“Tell me, where is Nine-Tailed Fox? Where?” The fat lieutenant continued to snigger.

“You guys!” Reid gritted his teeth.

Before more words were spoken, the helicopter in the distance flew straight toward the crowd.

“Which unit is that from?” The fat lieutenant looked up at the helicopter.

“No idea. I don’t think we mobilized a helicopter?” One of the subordinates spoke up in doubt.

“Didn’t mobilize?” The fat lieutenant looked at the clear and obvious police logo on the side of the helicopter. “If it was not mobilized, how can there be our logo on it? You idiot, don’t you recognize the pattern?” He yelled.

“This…” The subordinate had not reacted in time.

Boom boom boom!!

Suddenly, the helicopter fired, and the sound of cannon thundered, drawing out two clear cannon bullet chains.

Something dark was dropped off from the helicopter. It fell into the sea with a boom and seemed to have sunk directly.

Chapter 1178: T-Rex 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“All members, fire!!” The fat lieutenant squawked and went looking for cover.

Whoosh, a police officer used a shoulder-held rocket launcher to blast at the helicopter.

The rocket launcher actually exploded directly in mid-air with a boom.

A tall black figure floated up from the sea below. It was a two-to-three-meters tall, black metal robot. One could say that it was a Cyborg. However, this Cyborg had a much larger area of modification than the kind Garen had previously encountered. With the exception of half the side of the head, his entire body parts seemed to have modified into metal bodies.

The most conspicuous thing was that this guy had a small white flag behind his head with a word on it: Dragon.

“Dragon?” Garen peered through the gap and looked over. When he saw this Cyborg appear, he instantly had some doubts. “Is that him? The legendary mechanical Tyrannosaurus?”

“…What a cold sense of humor,” Nine-Tailed Fox’s voice came from the paper clip. “Although I don’t want to admit it, he is the one whom we are waiting for. Vulture’s T-Rex.”

“That is to say, these police officers who were first here are actually all imposters?” Garen could not comprehend.

“Not imposters, but they originally…” Bang!!

Nine-Tailed Fox’s voice was submerged by the violent explosion and was not clearly heard.

Garen made nothing of it and watched T-Rex, who was in the distance on the sea, ejecting several small missiles with wave trajectory from his chest. A yacht was directly blown into two by the missiles, slowly tilting and sinking in a huge red fire.

Fortunately, that yacht was the one last steered over here by the police officers, not Reid’s yacht that Garen and others had set sail on.

“Scatter Flowers,” The mechanical T-Rex coldly uttered. He spread out his right hand, and on the palm there erected a disc like that of an antenna disc. The silver disc slowly opened up like a flower blossoming.

Endless streams of bullets could be heard coming from his body. The policemen and the previously apprehended anonymous attackers were madly firing back, but only fire sparks were seen on T-Rex’s body surface. Other than that, there were not any other traces.

The slightly larger rocket launchers and howitzers were easily evaded by T-Rex.

Sizz!

The antenna dish on his palm suddenly shot out a little white light from the center of it.

The white light rose into the sky, like a rocket launcher. It burst into a mass of white light in the air over this sea region.

Garen suddenly felt a sense of danger, pulled out his sword, and struck out in a lightning manner.

Whoosh!

A silver arc emerged in front of him.

Clang clang clang… A dense collision noise sounded in front of him. Numerous ox hair-like steel needles were deflected and nailed to the deck of the yacht.

Garen’s arm was almost completely blurred. Only a little gray shadow was seen moving, while the rest was an incessant variety of cling-clang sounds.

On another yacht in the distance, Nine-Tailed Fox’s body was spinning and it seemed that she was well-prepared. Her rotating body had a ribbon-like white cloth strip around it, directly attracting a vast amount of the steel needles to her. The cloth strip obviously had a strong magnetic force. It was more than twice as easy for her as compared to Garen.

Farther away on a yacht, the swarm of police officers clothed in black and the so-called national security personnel all suffered. They almost fell in response. The vast number of steel needles descended from the sky and savagely pierced through most of their bodies. They were extremely accurate.

“Watch. This is the legendary Tyrannosaurus!!” Nine-Tailed Fox’s laughter traveled over. “Rainstorm Dragon, this is the strongest masterpiece of some powerhouse in the Vulture.”

“It really is amazing,” Garen was also feeling it. “I am thinking about whether to create something similar as well,” he recalled the series of biochemical technology he had mastered. If he were to try it out, he might find some suitable parts in which he could apply.

“You better forget it. How nice it is to just diligently practice your Sword Art. Sword Master? You know? This is the comprehensive evaluation given to you by the inside of Vulture,” Nine-Tailed Fox seemed to have gotten the latest news.

“What use is that?” Garen was speechless. “Can it be used against the Slayer?”

“Far from that,” Nine-Tailed Fox replied simply. “The Slayer, as the strongest individual existence of this world’s Plot, is the best masterpiece of the human being’s killing consciousness. Whatever sword techniques or saber techniques you know, he also knows. Even the gone-extinct ancient top killing skill he also knows. Even if it is the skill you have just created, he can master it completely with just a glance and could bring it into play much mightier than you!”

“So freakish!” Garen was speechless.

“Of course it is freakish! How else can he be called the Slayer?” Nine-Tailed Fox said helplessly. “That is why we are pushing others to collect contribution points to hire powerhouses.”

During their conversation, there were not many of those who could still move in this sea region. There seemed to be a huge magnetic force under Rainstorm Dragon’s feet. He straight away walked on the wall of the boat in a ninety-degree manner, boarded the yacht, and began to resolve the remaining recalcitrant police officers and resistors.

The sound of gunshots and flames continued to shine from his arms.

The blood on the yacht converged together, almost tainting the entire deck red. It was extremely gruesome.

The fat lieutenant who wanted to jump into the sea to escape on the motorboat had a bullet accurately shot through the back of his head and died on the spot.

In just one minute, more than half of the police officers and national security who were present were killed, leaving only Reid’s bodyguards who did not open fire and the beauties on the yacht who had no resistance.

“Your little lover is in trouble. Aren’t you going to rescue him?” Garen teased.

“I was just playing with him,” Nine-Tailed Fox simply said. “Don’t you know that the one you can’t get is always the best?” She raised her chest from far and used one hand to knead one side of her breast.

“You are as abominable as Kong Xinxue,” Garen breathed out a puff of air and held back the incitement in his heart. “It’s just two kinds of appearance in different aspects.”

“Which is why we are good friends,” Nine-Tailed Fox actually began to shed off her swimsuit. She took out black clothes she had gotten from who-knew-where and began to change her clothes right in front of Garen.

There was no intention of concealing the body and the angle she stood at was so happen to be visible only to Garen.

Out of courtesy, since he did not really want to touch this woman, Garen turned away and did not look at the other party. However, the wave of incitement in his heart was getting more intense.

With the last shot over that side, T-Rex had resolved the last police officer. He walked to the front of Reid and others. The remaining people were all shocked and afraid, not knowing what he was going to do.

“All of you…” T-Rex slowly opened his mouth.

Clang!

Suddenly, his right arm was raised, blocking the side of his head. A golden spark sputtered on his arm.

“Are there still survivors?” His voice was as hoarse as air leaking, and he turned his head around in the direction of the shot. There was a small pleasure boat headed over here.

On the bow stood a man, and it was actually Yuria!

He was dressed in tight-fitting black clothes and looking at the tragic scene over here, which was like hell. There were police and national security corpses everywhere.

A chubby merchant with a beard was standing next to Yuria, looking over with a smiley face.

“It’s him!” The merchant took out a cigar and lighted it. “Vulture’s T-Rex, Rainstorm Dragon.”

Yuria fixed his eyes on T-Rex with a solemn face. He did not know why but when he saw the gruesome scene in front of him, he did not feel nauseous and afraid at all. Instead, he had quickly accustomed to it.

“Super gravitational bomb basically does him no harm, but it can temporarily paralyze all his body’s firepower ability. You can finish this guy off with just hand-to-hand combat,” The chubby merchant grinned.

“Uncle Galouro,” Yuria calmly said. “Please take care of my sister for now.”

“No problem. Don’t worry!” The chubby merchant nodded. “I’m here, and it’s not just me alone,” He looked back at the bodyguards who came out from behind.

“That’s good,” Yuria jumped down and dived into the sea. A motorboat approached from the side. He grabbed it, rolled over and rode on it.

Rainstorm Dragon turned around and looked coldly at the on-coming Yuria.

He stretched out his arm and the machine gun loaded on it was not working anymore. It was not just the machine gun but all the fire controls on his body seemed to have failed.

“Is it super gravitational bomb? That’s interesting.”

He strode forward, walked to the wide deck of the yacht, and stood still, waiting quietly for the other party to arrive.

The super gravitational bomb had a limited time of only twenty minutes, and it would weaken with time. Therefore, the purpose of the other party was very clear, which was melee combat!

He just needed to stand here and quietly wait for the other party to come.

******************

“It’s going to begin…” Over this side, Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox who had changed her clothes had gathered together.

“Why would Yuria dare to engage with Rainstorm Dragon? I am very clear about his combat strength. He shouldn’t be strong enough to beat that fellow?” Garen was puzzled.

“Really?” Nine-Tailed Fox smirked slightly. Her arm naturally wrapped around Garen’s arms. “If you’re just thinking as such, you’re in for a great surprise.”

“Oh?” Garen did not doubt the authenticity of Nine-Tailed Fox’s words. He did faintly see something queer from Yuria’s posture movement at this moment.

It was a little like something he had never seen before.

“It seems to be a new kind of battle skill?” He guessed.

Nine-Tailed Fox smiled and did not reply.

“If it is a special weapon add on, which has the same powerful effect as that previous thing, then the odds are indeed there,” Garen nodded, clearly having ascertained some clues.

“You have a good eye,” Nine-Tailed Fox laughed. “The level of Rainstorm Dragon is considered to be not-too-bad in the Plot,” Her tone was very high, and there was a kind of condescending attitude.

Among these Transmigrators, which one of them did not have their own unique accomplishments in various fields before coming to this world, except for a few special ones? This was the accumulation of the worlds, time, and energy.

Garen understood that although he was powerful, Nine-Tailed Fox, who was once a top great monster existence, was definitely no less than him. It was just that he did not know how powerful she was and to what extent.

Glancing at Nine-Tailed Fox, this fellow seemed to have concealed a lot of intelligence and did not tell it out. But from her concern about the Slayer, it was clear that that fellow was far trickier to be handled than imagined. He would have at least risen to the mighty level of unnatural powers.

Garen was also beginning to worry a little whether his previous relaxing state was too optimistic.

He had not seen the Slayer with his own eyes. Unlike these Transmigrators, he understood the general trend, which was the so-called Plot method, and was different from them. He did not see the Slayer killing with his own eyes, but he had seen a few images in the general trend scenes and was not clear about his specific strength.

“Should I consider whether to enhance my Sword Art by one level with the Soul Seed?” Garen contemplated. Now that he saw the state of Rainstorm Dragon, he began to wonder in his heart. If Rainstorm Dragon’s kind of level could only be evaluated as not-too-bad, how powerful then would the Slayer be that Nine-Tailed Fox and others were fearful and had to be this cautious?

Chapter 1179: Becoming Stronger 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Yuria used the claw on his arms to climb up to the yacht and he looked extremely miserable. He was in an all-black attire and had a short knife which looked like a short fish bayonet held tightly in his hand. He looked like he had his fair share of experience in handling a knife.

As he managed to stabilize himself just for a moment, T-rex raised his hands as two machetes were unsheathed while he ran towards him.

Thud thud thud. The low pitched footsteps gave off an anxious vibe as its pace increased.

He crossed his machetes as she swung at Yuria, drawing two cold light in the air.

Yuria panicked as he rolled out as he attempted to evade the machetes.

“Too slow!”

Then, he relaxed his mind. Galouro had reminded him that this strange robot was the one that was ordered to capture him and his sister before he came to this place. As this robot had just caused a bloodbath, killing and leaving behind between fifty to sixty corpses in the scene, he had already viewed this killing robot in front of him as an extremely evil person.

“Pierce!”

The bayonet-like short knife pierced forward without mercy.

The knife came in contact with the opponent’s abdomen and it tried to pierce into T-rex’s abdomen. It was only then Yuria realized what he had done as his body moved and executed such a cruel technique on its own. He could not help but feel shocked as he loosened his grip.

Clank!

Unfortunately, while the tip of the knife had indeed came in contact with T-rex’s abdomen, it was blocked by the extremely tough shell on his body and the damage was no more than a small white scratch. Instead, the huge recoil that came from the defense almost made Yuria let go of his short knife.

“Fool!” T-rex said as he revealed half of his mocking expression on his face. Although his movement was not fast, his arms were very agile as the machetes came striking down from above.

Boom!

He stared at the machetes striking the yacht’s rail guard, cutting the metals in white paint into half. His enormous strength sent the debris flying about everywhere. Some of the debris landed on Yuria’s body, causing him to flinch.

“He has such a high defense and strength!” He swiftly took a few steps back to distance himself away from him. It was fortunate that the yacht was larger than usual as it was a middle-size boat that could accommodate dozens of people. Hence he had enough space to move about freely.

“Is this all you got?” T-rex sneered as he kept waving his machetes towards him.

Boom!

The rail guard on the other end was destroyed. Yuria rolled away horribly from his original position as blood started to flow down from his face which was caused by the debris’ cut.

Boom boom!

Two additional holes were created on the yacht’s battering wall. The steel that had been bent into the holes became as sharp as the machete.

Yuria kept evading T-rex’s pursuit like a monkey. Everyone could not help but feel anxious and sweat profusely for him as he would be sliced in half if he were to be careless.

********

“The situation looks very dire…” Garen rubbed his chin as he said. “The opponent’s weapon is not that threatening and he can not do anything but to evade all of his attacks. The battle is over the moment he is struck even once. I don’t think there is a need to fight one on one in this battle. Won’t it be better if multiple people attack him at one go?”

“This is where T-rex’s quality shine,” Nine-Tailed Fox said lazily as she placed her arm in front of her chest.

“T-rex’s quality? What would that be?”

“His strength is simply too overwhelming. He installed many more engines in order to gain more strength but this has caused him to be very slow in attacking. Hence, it was natural that this situation where he could not keep up with Yuria’s reaction happened,” Nine-Tailed Fox explained. “However, he has one advantage in this condition. he can immediately go oof if he were to face against multiple enemies at once!”

“Oof? What is that suppose to mean?” Garen asked curiously.

“It’s oof~” Nine-Tailed Fox looked at him as if he was supposed to understand her.

“What is it? Can’t you be clearer on this?” Garen felt speechless.

“It’s that thing!”

“Brother’s Saber Killing Move! Four Directional Winds!!” Suddenly, Yuria’s scream could be heard from afar as he used Garen’s Saber Art Technique with the fish bayonet.

Hopelessness could be seen written all over Garen’s face.

“This guy… Shout as much as you like, but the first sentence of the scream is unaccounted for!”

Boom!

There were only three slashes from the Four Directional Winds which Yuria had executed. Although all three slashes had landed on T-rex, it was unfortunately ineffective. Then, he continued evading T-rex’s ferocious attack miserably once more.

“I’m not done yet!!” Yuria screamed. “I’m betting everything including my reputation as Saber Two in this match!!”

“You’re not infamous at all!” Garen could not hold himself back as he shouted.

Nine-Tailed Fox covered her mouth as she laughed at the side.

Clunk!

Yuria’s latest attack finally had an effect on him.

Yuria fractured one of his arms in exchange for landing a critical attack on T-rex’s joint.

T-rex lost his balance and kneeled on one knee as he fell.

Then, it was at this crucial moment!

Thud!!

T-rex shot out a wide net which covered a wide area in all directions. It was shot out from his back and covered an area of at least ten meters square around him, completely shrouding Yuria in it.

“Xiaojie!” Yuria started shouting loudly.

Boom!

A gunshot could be heard from afar as a javelin-like item carried the net which had yet to completely fall to the ground far away from them and plunged it down into the sea at high speed.

“That’s a close one…” Yuria wiped off the sweat on his head as he got up, looking at the Cyborg T-rex who only had one leg left.

Although this guy looks very ferocious, he’s just an idiot with big muscle after losing his power. He’s very easy to deal with.”

“Is that so?” T-rex scoffed.

“Still acting arrogant?!” Yuria was filled with fire. “Do you realize what you have done?! You’ve killed so many people! Do people like you from Vulture not care about the innocent people’s lives?!”

A sense of mockery could be seen in T-rex’s gaze.

“Do you really think you’ve won against me?”

“You can’t even move your leg anymore. What else can you do?” Yuria tensed up as he looked around so that he would not be ambushed by the others.

“It’s over,” the biological side of T-rex’s face slightly opened his mouth.

Buzz…

An indescribable shockwave was shot out towards Yuria’s direction as circles of ripples spread out.

“This… This is!!?” Yuria felt his body turning soft as if he had lost all of his strength at once and he felt unease and dizzy.

Thud. He kneeled on the ground with a very pale face.

The silent buzzing vibration reached Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox who were far away. It managed to travel up to hundreds of meters away.

Both of them frowned slightly as they felt a little bit uncomfortable.

“Infrasonic wave?” Garen whispered.

“Correct,” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded. “What would you do if you’re in this situation?”

“Me?” Garen frowned as he pondered. “I think I would give my opponent the opportunity to keep using this infrasonic technique.”

Nine-Tailed Fox smiled and she did not say a single word.

“It’s time for Yuria to activate his true strength.”

“His true strength?” Garen was somewhat shocked. “What are you talking about?”

“The Four Great Cornerstones are the only four with supernatural powers on this planet. You wouldn’t think they would only have one ability, right?” Nine-Tailed Fox started to curl her hair with her finger. Her black hair started moving up slowly until the end of the hair was curled up.

“Soon… You’ll see.”

Garen nodded his head gently as he wanted to see what kind of ability Yuria would activate as well.

Time ticked by as Yuria’s face turned even paler and started to sweat even more. He then started to curl his body up on the deck. He did not even move at all as it kept trembling. It was obvious that he was in agony.

Boom!

A huge gunshot was heard from afar. It was from Yurijie.

She was holding up her gun as she stared calmly in that direction.

“Brother! Do you remember what Brother Saber had said?!!” She shouted. Although her expression was calm, anxiety could be seen in her gaze.

Yuria, who was curled up on the deck had awakened from his fading conscience from this gunshot.

“Brother… Brother Blade…”

His memories kept playing back in front of his eyes. It was the memory of Brother Blade giving him a cruel lesson. The images quickly flashing across him soon stopped at one of the frames.

It was Garen’s gentle smile.

“I am the Great Saberm,” it was as if that gentle voice was ringing beside his ears and the background was filled with a beautiful golden light, which was made up by the brain.

“Don’t you know that you need to retreat if you can’t win!! You’re as dumb as a pig!!!” Garen’s expression turned for the worse. “Idiots like you who would even sell your ass away need to know that staying alive is the utmost priority if you can’t win against an enemy. As the head minister, this is the first rule that you need to obey for the rest of your life!!!!!!”

The end of that speech seemed to reverberate in his mind as Yuria could still remember his shocked expression upon hearing it.

“This… This is… Ridiculous!!” He and his sister were stunned.

“Saber One, Saber Two. Do you know the true essence of combat?”

“… No …”

“It means that you have to create a scenario where your opponent is weaker than you,” Garen looked at the sky and sighed. “Do you know what it takes to create such a situation?”

“No…”

Garen then turned around and showed his big and tall back.

“The trick is to shock your enemy!!”

“Shock??!!”

“Shocking… If your opponent had taken off his pants to surprise you, you’ll then have to take off more clothes to counter him back!!!” Garen turned his head around and said loudly.

“…”

“Why do you need to use the example of taking off one’s pants…” Nine-Tailed Fox laughed loudly.

“It felt entertaining at the time…” Garen felt innocent as he did not expect he had landed such a huge psychological impact towards Yuria and his sister. If he recalled correctly, the siblings started calling him Brother Saber after that lecture and they looked at him with respect.

Now that he thought about it… He could not help but sneeze.

“Could it be that this is the Sword Master’s essence! To become more b*tchy than everybody!?” Nine-Tailed Fox held onto her stomach as she laughed to the point where her spine could not stay straight.

“Brother Saber! Ahh!!! Power! Power is flowing out from me!!!” Yurian stood up, shouting at the sky as his voice traveled to the distance.

“F*ck. Why am I involved in this!” Garen could not help but shout out. He felt that it was pointless for Yuria to shout out his nickname in such a serious environment.

Tear!

Yuria’s shirt was torn apart!

Tear!

His pants were torn apart as well…

Ah!

A few screams could be heard as the women watching from the sideline turned their line of sight away embarrassingly.

Yuria did not seem to realize it at all. His skin was purplish red and he was holding the short fish bayonet tightly with his hand. His lower body was censored with mosaic as he rushed towards his opponent. His posture had carved its way into everyone’s memory forever.

T-rex was stunned by his impudent actions and the sound waves were instantly weakened.

Yuria was extremely delighted as Brother Saber’s battle strategy was effective!!

He was convinced by Brother Saber’s warning during the battle from the very bottom of his heart. He had finally placed the idea of shame behind his mind in order to achieve victory.

Chapter 1180: Becoming Stronger 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Everything seemed to slow down as Yurian rushed towards T-rex with a short bayonet in his arm. It was obvious that he had borrowed the strength from the others as he used Savior’s ability. However, no one knew how many people’s worth of strength he had borrowed this time around.

He took the opportunity and stepped forward and slashed T-rex’s left shoulder when T-rex had lessened the intensity of the soundwaves.

Thud!!

There was a huge thud as the bayonet in Yuria’s hand gave off a unique sound.

Yuria had activated the Savior’s ability in which strength was borrowed from the others and finally landed a critical hit on T-rex’s electrical supply’s central pivot point, which was his left shoulder.

It was finally over.

T-rex fell as he stared at him with dissatisfaction. The soundwave was cut off and he was nothing but a shell without an energy source.

On the other hand, Yuria finally revealed a bright smile while his skin stayed purplish red with his buffed body.

“Indeed… The essence of combat is to see who is more shameless…” He looked at the sun as he committed Brother Saber’s sacred advice in mind even though he did not realize his life was heading towards a twisted path no one had set foot on before…

“Idiot!!”

A cold voice came from the helicopter above him.

The voice put Yuria who had relaxed down back into the anxiety phase.

He looked up to realize that the helicopter which sent T-rex here had unknowingly arrived just above him. Inside it was a silver-haired man with a black eyepatch who was slowly wearing his white gloves.

“What a disgusting victory!” The man said coldly. “Let me show you what a real combat looks like…” He stood up as he prepared to jump down from the helicopter.

Slap.

Suddenly a huge hair hand grabbed onto his arm from behind.

“Let me handle it,” a middle age uncle in white shirt squeezed to the front. He had shoulder-length brown hair and the edge of his lips were arced in such a way that he seemed to be putting on a smile on his fully bearded face.

“Yindu,” White Coat said with a smile on his face. “You have more important things to do.”

The one-eyed man did not oppose him as he scoffed and sat back down.

White Coat gently reached out one of his hands and revealed a twisted smile.

“How dare you, toying and destroying my puppet to such extent…” He looked T-rex in a deplored manner. “I have spent a lot of time and energy to finish modifying him…”

Puppet!!?

Yuria, Yurijie and even Reid who had been numbed by the chains of events felt their heart sinking.

T-rex, that monster who had almost massacred everyone in the scene was just a puppet?!

“Do remember my name?” The middle-aged man in the white coat clenched his fist. “I am Jiatai, the Root Doctor.”

Pew pew pew pew…

In a blink of an eye, countless of Steel Needle flew up and went straight towards Yuria. These Steel Needles were spread out previously by T-rex and they had become a controllable weapon to this weird man!?

Pew pew pew. It headed towards Yuria as if it was a heavy rain, hitting every single spot of Yuria’s body.

“Brother!!!” Yurijie screamed as she panicked.

The moment his sister’s voice reached him, he had already felt pain. He knew that the moment he heard her, he had already been struck by the needles.

Not a single spot on his body was not in pain.

“At times like these…” He knew that this was the result of having a huge gap in strength. His opponent’s attack was too fast and he was not able to react in time at all. “What should I do?”

Garen’s face appeared in front of him once more as he closed his eyes.

“Brother Saber… Tell me. What should I do…”

“I have been extremely shameless to the point where I can’t be worse than I currently am. I still couldn’t close the gap even if I try to be as shameless as possible…”

“At times like this…” Garen spoke. “You have to play dead!”

“That’s right! Play Dead!!!” Inspiration flashed across Yuria’s eyes as he bit the tip of his tongue and spit the blood out of his mouth.

He then slowly fell on his back and shut his tired eyes up.

The blood flowed all over the place…

“I guess I have yet become the most shameless man if I didn’t immediately think of playing dead…” As Yuria closed his eyes, a thought flashed across his mind. “This is all thanks to the Head Minister!” A sense of respect filled his heart once more.

“If you’re still this weak and boring the next time we meet,” the middle-aged man uncle in white coat spoke once more. “I’ll kill you,” his undoubted confidence was embedded in his tone.

Then, the sound of the helicopter going into the distance could be heard.

*********

“Is he dead?” Nine-Tailed Fox covered her mouth.

“He’s playing dead,” Garen concealed his face as he seemed to have taught a normal man into a shameless man that the world had never seen before…

“Well, you’re the one who taught him…” Nine-Tailed Fox laughed again.

Both of them knew that it was impossible for Yuria to die. Afterall, he was one of Four Great Cornerstones. He would at most reincarnate if he lost his physical body and it is the perk of being the Four Great Cornerstones. Only the other Four Great Cornerstones could absorb their strength and ensure that they would not be revived.

Then, they stopped their banter as they looked at Yuria who was laying on the deck from afar.

“Something is off,” Nine-Tailed Fox frowned.

“What’s wrong?” Garen was not as informed as the Nine-Tailed Fox in terms of the Plot.

“According to the Plot, Yuria should have released his new ability here…” Nine-Tailed Fox said softly.

“New ability?”

“Yes. It is a type of Hydra-based ability,” Nine-Tailed Fox’s eyes were brimming with skepticism. “However, it didn’t happen.”

“What would the end result be if we were to go with the original Plot?” Garen asked.

“He should be seriously injured by T-rex in the original Plot. Jiatai the Root Doctor shouldn’t appear this early as well.”

“Oh? Is that so? Garen then recalled those policemen who appeared out of the blue and the man who initiated the attack. Those people seemed to be working in a group and were most likely related to the Nine-Tailed Fox. However, she did not seem to plan to talk about it.

On the other hand, the people from Vulture, regardless if it was T-rex, the Root Doctor or even Yindu who appeared at the end of the scene most likely viewed the policemen as their enemies. It would not make sense since they killed them without any hesitation.

“Is Vulture an organization that rebels the government?” Garen whispered.

“That’s not possible…” Nine-Tailed Fox shook her head. “Even I am not sure what is going on at the moment. Vulture is the largest military organization in the Red Nation. Why would they go against the government? They are part of the government after all.”

“If they are not a rebel, why would they kill these policemen?” Garen continued his questioning.

“This is something I can’t make sense of as well,” Nine-Tailed Fox shook her head.

“Let’s continue observing then,” Garen said softly.

“Alright.”

Then, Yurijie and the others soon arrived the yacht and started saving Yuria’s life.

Yuria was quickly covered in clothes and brought over to their own yacht. The weapon merchant, Galouro ignored everyone and left the area as he brought the two siblings away. Soon, they disappeared from the crowd’s line of sight.

“Alright. It’s time for us to head over and clean up the mess,” Nine-Tailed Fox dusted her shirt and walked forward.

Garen laughed and followed her lead.

********

There was no news of the siblings for a few days ever since the attack.

Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox stayed in the Zhatong City for two days before returning back to the Lily of the Valley. He was fortunate that Kong Xinxue had covered up the entire thing up with her lies as she said that Garen had gone to participate in some sort of a last minute summer camp to experience the learning activities. Fortunately, Kong Yuan bought his exceptional and dazzling daughter’s surreal story and there was not much of a problem from this end.

Once they had returned, they gathered once more with the rest for a meal as they discussed the issues regarding the Plot’s deviation.

Garen then went back alone as he started to ponder on the issue of raising his own Combat Power.

He felt that it would be too exhausting to face against Vulture purely with Saber Art. If he were to battle on a troublesome terrain such as in the sea, he would no longer have a focus point and it would be extremely disadvantageous towards his Saber Art.

This was because his Saber Art required extreme precision. The lethality of his attack would lessen if the deviation increased.

Furthermore, he did not have any good solutions for dealing with long-range attacks.

“What technique should I use to deal with fighting on the sea? Which is a very disadvantageous environment,” Garen sat on his knees in his room as he pondered.

“It’s best to stick with what I’ve been doing in the past when it comes to fighting against long-range opponents. Firearms is a good choice but I won’t be having it with me all the time. The best way is to evade and reduce the distance between my opponent and I. Unfortunately…” It was indeed very troublesome when he thought of fighting in a sea and he felt that this method was very exhausting.

“It’s rather exhausting to fight against them purely with his Saber Art. If there were ten more monsters as strong at Vulture’s T-rex going after me, I would find it too difficult to handle them as well,” Garen felt that the Steel Needles Technique was too powerful as it rained upon him. He would be in great trouble if it was combined with the infrasonic waves. The infrasonic waves were strong enough to crack the walls, hence it would be worse for him who only had a small, fragile body.

“Whatever. It’s best for me to enhance my Saber Art the hard way. Since my Saber Art has reached Full Completion in the Realm of Sword Master, it would solve the issue of fighting straight up against them if I can go above another grade.”

The next day, Garen went to class as usual as he led and trained a team of people from the Unrestricted Combat Department at noon. The group of people kept waving their wooden sabers about as they shouted like an idiot swinging their sabers wildly.

Garen was sitting on his knees at one side alone as he pondered on something. Suddenly, a dark shadow blocked the sun away from him.

Garen looked up and it was Yuria who had disappeared for the past few days.

“Saber One?”

“No Brother Saber. I am now Saber Two and my sister is Saber One,” Yuria said with a stern face.

“Alright… Saber Two,” Garen analyzed Yuria’s physical condition. “You haven’t come here for training for a few days already, right?”

“Yes,” Yuria was covered with bandages from head to toe and he looked extremely wounded. The rest of the group who were training not far away from him showed their curiosity as they saw his terrible condition and they would most likely rush towards him to ask for an explanation.

“Judging from your terrible appearance, I assume you’ve been assaulted by someone?” Garen said as he guessed. Although he knew what had happened to him, he still had to act dumb. “Why are you here when you’re supposed to rest at home?”

“Brother Saber!”

Yuria then bowed down. His actions were so drastic that it would make anyone surprised.

“Please train me!! I want to become stronger!!”

“Oh?”

Garen squinted.

Chapter 1181: Becoming Stronger 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At the outskirts of the Lily of the Valley, in a deserted mountain area.

A group of people parked their car just beside a small forest. Garen, Kong Xinxue, Nine-Tailed Fox, and the two siblings who wished to be trained, Yuria and Yurijie, a total of five people had got down from the car.

All of them were in the dark green camouflage military uniform with all sorts of items hanging on their bodies. They were also carrying a huge backpack, which looked rather packed.

Nine-Tailed Fox led them deep into the forest once they had gotten down from the car.

“This is an emergency base where my subordinate would use to train. Feel free to stay as long as you like and I’ll let you use it for free,” Nine-Tailed Fox said generously.

“Thank you,” Garen nodded as he looked at Yuria. “My training towards you will start from here.”

“Understood!” Yuria replied loudly. He felt that Garen was filled with mystery. He, who was just a normal secondary school student was able to come in contact with so many mysterious things. Furthermore, he seemed to strangely have a very wide network as well and his powerful Saber Art seemed to be trained out from an actual battle.

“Let’s go…”

Garen then followed Nine-Tailed Fox as they headed forward swiftly.

Yuria and his sister followed tightly from behind and Kong Xinxue was the last one walking behind everyone else.

They walked passed a few Tripod Surveillance Towers which had swivel surveillance systems with red lights coming out from it.

“This is the scanning system installed for this base. It can scan and detect any movement in an area of up to two hundred and fifty meters,” Nine-Tailed Fox explained. “I’ve spent tens of millions on this system.”

She explained as she walked further in.

Soon a jade-green pond appeared in front of the forest. The oval-shaped pond looked rather sticky and one could even smell the faint stench coming off from it.

“This is it,” Nine-Tailed Fox pointed at the pond.

“This is the location?”

Garen walked towards the pond, turned around and looked at Yuria as if there was nothing wrong with it.

“This is where you’ll train.”

“Huh?” Yuria walked towards the pond and looked into the water confusingly.

Then, Garen revealed a mysterious smile.

“This is the best place for your training, where you can enhance your actual strength within a short amount of time.”

“Is that so?” Yuria looked at the stinky water inside the pond and could not figure out why this place suited him at all.

“Don’t believe me?” Garen smiled as he gave him a strong kick on the back.

Yuria immediately plunged into the pond and a huge splash followed along.

Yurijie and the rest were stunned but they suppressed their doubts within themselves. They knew that Garen would never harm Yujia, hence, this action was definitely part of the training.

“Brother Saber?” Yuria surfaced his head out of the water with a confused look on his face.

“This is your training,” Garen laughed.

“My training?”

Yuria was confused. It was not just him as the rest were confused as well.

Garen then hinted him on what his next action would be.

“Try and raise up your right arm.”

Yuria then raised up his right arm confusingly as he heard the instruction.

His entire arm that was exposed was densely filled with black leeches, These black brown leeches were attached to his arms with their tails hanging freely downwards. they swung about freely like a bunch of black ropes…

Yuria then swung about the leeches on his hand.

“Are these… Leeches?… Ahhh!!!!!” He started screaming madly as his face turned green and then purple before his face became distorted. “My God!!!”

He immediately tried to swim up towards the shore.

“Hehe. There’s at least thirty four of them. Pretty popular,” Nine-Tailed Fox was impressed.

“That’s right…” Garen nodded.

Yurijie looked at him from the side with a worried look as she covered her mouth with her hand whereas Kong Xinxue was just crossing her arms and observed coldly as if she was looking at a circus act.

“What are you afraid of?” Garen moved forward and tried to kick Yuria who was almost out of the pond back down into it. “Haven’t you realized?”

“Brother Saber! I’m dying! For real, I’m about to die…! This is a murder, not a training!!” Yuria was on the verge of crying as he fell back into the pond. This time, his entire body which was exposed to the water excluding his face was covered in leeches, which could not be pulled off.

“Looks like you have not realized it,” Garen shook his head. “Enjoy yourself inside.”

The Nine-Tailed Fox took out the ropes that she had prepared beforehand with a crafty look on her face.

Ten minutes later… Yuria was entirely tied up and thrown into the pond. What was revealed was his face so that he could breathe

“Help!!” He cried out loudly, but Yurijie did not come and attempt to save him at all. Instead, she was pulled to one side by someone and gave up after a few moments of hesitation.

“Enjoy your bath. We will head in and have our meal,” Garen waved his hand as he brought the rest into a small house which could be faintly seen.

****

Two hours later…

Yuria was on the verge of dying…

Three hours later…

Yuria was on the verge of dying…

Five hours later…

Yuria was really about to die…

It’s dark…

Yuria was…

“Eh? It’s already dark…” He opened his eyes as he realized he had fallen asleep.

There was a person squatting beside the pond. It was Garen.

“Are you awake?” Garen said calmly. “How’s the sleep?”

“Pretty comfortable. Despite it being rather smelly, it was the best sleep I have had for a long time,” Yuria responded truthfully.

“Have you realized?” Garen asked calmly.

“What?” Yuria was shocked as the horrible memories came back to him where he was still inside a leech’s pond!!

“Ahh!!!!” He started screaming again.

“Stop screaming!” Garen slapped his head. “If the leeches are able to suck your blood, do you think you would be still alive?”

“Uh…. that makes sense,” Yuria reacted. He raised his hands up and looked at his arms, where all the leeches were still densely attached. However, none of them were swollen and it was obvious that none of them had sucked his blood out at all.

“What is the meaning of this?” He finally calmed down and asked.

“What’s going on? You’ll have to answer it yourself.” Garen stood up. “Feel it carefully. Your body is currently rejecting the leeches from sucking your blood and the leeches seem to see you as some sort of a host. A host that they can attach onto.”

“A host?” Yuria did not understand the situation.

“Yes. Try and feel it. Feel your body’s abilities. This is the essence of your training,” Garen walked away slowly as he ignored him. Yuria was gifted with this ability and all he had to do was to awaken it.

The sky gradually became darker and dimmer.

The water had become colder as well but Yuria was not able to perceive it as his entire body was covered in a thick layer of leeches.

“Ability? I have a natural ability?”

He muttered softly as he realized that something was off since the leeches were not sucking his blood at all. They were just hanging by his skin as if they were a bunch of short ropes.

*********

“Will he succeed? With this idea.”

Kong Xinxue asked softly as she and Garen stood near the pond, peeking at Yuria who was in the pond.

“Perhaps he will. Perhaps he won’t,” Garen did not have a definite answer. “He had already awakened this ability from the previous battle and all I’m doing now is to making him realize how to utilize this ability.”

“However, it sure seems very disgusting,” Kong Xinxue covered her nose. “I couldn’t help but have goosebumps just by seeing him with so many leeches attached on his skin.”

“You’ll get used to it,” Garen sat on the floor. “I’ll take a rest. Just give me a shout when he realizes that he could use the ropes to escape to the shore.”

“Sure,” Kong Xinxue nodded.

Garen had something planned for himself as well, where he planned to take this opportunity to use the Soul Ring to forcibly increase his Saber Art.

From the moment he had decided to increase it until now, he had accumulated enough Soul Energy to increase his Saber Art by one grade.

The amount of Soul Energy required for this upgrade was actually very little. However, since this world’s restriction towards this pure energy was so great, it took Garen a very long time to accumulate to this amount.

If it were the past him, he would not even bat an eye to spend this small amount of Soul Energy as the amount of energy that could not be sensed meant that he had only spent a very minute amount of it.

He then stared at his Skill Pane and locked his sight on the Saber Art option.

‘Unnamed Saber Art – Third Grade. Thorough Comprehension Realm. Full Completion.’

It was a simple introduction since it was a foundation of all the Saber Arts that he knew. Hence, it was just a simple derivative technique.

Garen attempted to guide the Soul Energy to connect it to this skill slowly.

The Soul Energy then slowly but surely moved towards the Skill Pane in the form of transparent threads.

Pew!

The vague noise started ringing inside Garen’s ears as he witnessed the Skill Pane absorbing the Soul Energy greedily and crazily.

He was still sitting on his knees with his eyes closed on the outside. Kong Xinxue leaned against a tree as she looked at Yuria from afar and did not notice Garen’s situation at all. She could not realize, to begin with.

There was nothing strange going on in Garen’s body.

The Soul Energy’s Threads were soon absorbed completely by the Skill Pane and disappeared.

Hence, there was a new modification to the Saber Art in the Skill Pane.

“Unnamed Saber Art +1 – Unnamed Realm, effect: All Saber Art techniques would have a +1 in speed, strength, precision. Has an unknown effect.’

Garen was looking forward to it as his body had already reached the pinnacle of this world. Only the Ancient Endor’s civilization had this unique ability to forcibly enhance his Saber Art by a grade and caused an unknown effect, forcing a mortal’s power to a realm where one had never seen before via the Soul Ring Energy.

“It’s unfortunate that I couldn’t find any Potential Points here since it is also one of the ways to increase my skill,” Garen stood up remorsefully.

He saw that Kong Xinxue had already fallen asleep as she leaned against the tree.

Chapter 1182: Becoming Stronger 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He lifted his arm to look at his watch, and couldn’t believe that it has been over three hours. He did not realize or sense the flow of time.

“How tiresome,” Garen got up and walked to Kong Xinxue.

Swoosh!

The eye-opening movement of this woman seemed to have some sort of a sound effect.

Her sense of alert was strong, startling Garen the moment he went near her.

Garen understood that everyone was focused on Yuria because he was the actual, main character. He had heard Nine-Tailed Fox mentioned once before. Even though it was not mentioned in detail but he knew more or less of it. The entire plot revolved around Yuria so following up on his movements was what they had to do.

Currently, Yuria has yet to awaken the ability that should be done so. It may be the effect brought about by them as transmigrators, hence they would have to make up for this.

And since Yuria discovered by chance the energy that Garen was looking for to help him grow strong, Garen went with the flow and agreed to it.

“How is it?” He asked gently in the darkness.

“Quite alright. Seemed to have come to a realization,” Kong Xinxue nodded and stretched her arm out to tidy her long hair. Her fiery red, long mane emitted a dark red glow under the moonlight. Paired with her bright eyes and alluring body figure, it boasted a sort of temptation filled with mystery and purity.

“I heard from Nine-Tailed Fox that no matter how she tempted you, you were still adamant to choose me?” Kong Xinxue said calmly. “Is it true?”

“What do you think?” Garen replied rhetorically and smiled.

“I think it’s very possible so I’m here to ask you,” said Kong Xinxue. She had one arm akimbo as she continued. “Honestly speaking, I was really, really satisfied with my original brother, Kong Xiaofei. Too bad I found at the end it’s been changed to you. Can you understand that contradicting feeling of dissatisfaction yet understanding?”

“I understand. Everyone’s the same. The original Kong Xiaofei must have the same revelation of you occupying Kong Xinxue’s body,” Garen nodded.

“Yes,” Kong Xinxue nodded. “That’s why I probed into your attitude. I did not think you were the gentle kind, and without realizing it myself, I have fallen deeply for you. I enjoy teasing you, watching your every smile, every gesture. Oh, right, it’s not suitable to use every smile here. Of course, you could comprehend the sort of person I am. It’s not in my nature to fall for a maniac but it is in my instinct to do so. It was when I found out about your perverted attribute, that I fell in love with you.”

“…”

“Do you believe what I just said?”

“I don’t…”

“I don’t believe myself too actually. I’m only prying into your perverted side, that’s all,” Kong Xinxue’s revealed her true personality again. “I thought that with the both of us alone in such a dangerous environment, all you had to do was make a move and a weak young lady like me wouldn’t be able to fend off from being pushed to the grass and forced to ** and **. I honestly thought you’ll get all riled up to take action but now it seems like you are a safe, harmless being. I am relieved, but also saddened by the defiance.”

“So, are you saying this because you want me to do it, or you don’t want me to do so?” Garen laughed. “To push you down on the grass, rip off your clothes and underwear before I ** you violently with my **, giving you absolute pain and pleasure. I feel that this is not a bad idea after all.”

“What a vile nature. See, it’s coming out…” Kong Xinxue made a tsk sound, took two steps backward and stared at Garen intently.

“Wasn’t it you who tempted me? Xiao Xuexue…”

Swoosh!

Garen lurched forward suddenly and with one arm, grabbed Kong Xinxue by the waist.

It was obvious she went back and changed into a tight, black miniskirt and black, long stockings over her long, slender legs. She was taken aback by Garen’s sudden movement and turned to run but was seized by her waist.

Ah.

Before her scream could make its way out, Garen covered her mouth with his other hand. Her white, t-shirt tightened with the movement, emphasizing the outline of her bountiful bosoms, making her more alluring under the moonlight.

Sniff…

Garen took a big whiff of her hair.

“You smell so good…” After coming to this world and deciding to completely relax here, he suddenly realized many of his suppressed urges were being aroused more and more.

“What are you up to?” Kong Xinxue was tense. She might have a foul mouth and was constantly using filthy language, but it is the first time for her to have a guy to be in such close, physical contact with her. As Garen’s muscular body hugged her, she was overpowered by the smell of his musky pheromone.

“What do you think I’m going to do?” Garen laughed. “Weren’t you the one who told me that during the dead of night beneath the raven moon, I should push you onto the grass and do ** and ** to you? You are powerless to resist anyway,” he leaned in and whispered into Kong Xinxue’s ear.

“Shouldn’t this kind of thing…be of mutual consent?” Kong Xinxue’s body stiffened. “A pervert like you would act so common? Even before you are able to think of a more extreme and perverted act, such a common way is definitely an insult to your noble identity!” She started to give in…

“Still acting tough?” Garen’s wormed his finger into her mouth, stirring and playing with her silky saliva, emitting a squishing sound.

“You uh…” Kong Xinxue could not say anything anymore.

“Relax,” Garen beamed. His other arm moved up slowly, viciously grabbing her protruding bosoms made apparent by her tight shirt.

“Aiyaya… Am I seeing something that I’m not supposed to?” Suddenly, a listless, female voice came from the side of the forest.

It was Nine-Tailed Fox.

She was dressed in a tight, white leather suit, walking slowly out from deep within the forest.

Garen’s actions halted, and he released Kong Xinxue gently.

“Did you record it?” He asked, smiling. “I displayed classic moves which I thought of earlier!”

Nine-Tailed Fox smiled sneakily and devilishly and gave a thumbs up.

“Nice posture!!”

At the side, Kong Xinxue was gasping for breath. She felt sticky with her sweat. Seeing this, she knew she had been schemed by these two.

“You… You adulterous couple!!” She yelled in rage.

“Didn’t I say before? No matter an extrovert or introvert, you can be defeated by a woman’s body facing this sort of thing,” Nine-Tailed Fox laughed with delight. She was truly a fox.

Garen walked over from the other side. Both of them took out a miniature compact camera, turning it on to view the recording while gasping with admiration.

“What are you up to?!” The camera was playing Kong Xinxue’s voice. She looked like a poor little girl who was about to be **.

“Alright,” Garen held the camera while smirking coldly at Kong Xinxue. “Hand over the remaining negatives. As an exchange, I can hand this to you.”

Kong Xinxue had almost calmed down. She stood up.

“Such a despicable tactic…”

“But I am a pervert!” Garen said matter of factly, “shouldn’t I resort to despicable tactics?”

“Yes, Garen is known to be the lowly lord. Who asked you to underestimate him? Nine-Tailed Fox exclaimed with her sweet voice.

“…”

“I found it…”

“Out of the blue, Yuria’s voice came from afar.

“Oh?”

The trio immediately put away their joking mood and walked out of the dark forest.

From far, they could see Yuria standing alone in the middle of the lake. Half of his body was in the waters, there were groups of black leeches surrounding him.

“Leeches…” The leeches around Yuria suddenly plummeted down like raindrops. Each of them dried up as if something had sucked them dry.

Seeing Yuria’s situation, Nine-Tailed Fox was dumbfounded.

“He’s that powerful? It looks like he has gained something significant.”

“Now onto the next event,” Garen strode forward and stood by the lake to watch Yuria.

“Next event?”

******

On an empty field of green grass was a base surrounded by various monitoring and interference infrastructure.

There were two large dirt colored circles right in the center of the field, looking like two large pits.

Sunlight shone from above as Garen stood silently in the center of one of the pits, with a hand wielding a wooden blade. Dressed plainly in white t-shirt and jeans, his soft red hair fluttered with the wind.

“The main purpose of this training and your mission task is to use the blade in your hands to strike me,” Garen looked at Yuria, who was getting into the pit slowly.

“Strike you…” Yuria looked at the wooden blade in his hand. It was a wooden knife over a meter long with a slight curve. It was fine and long. “Does touching your sleeve count?”

“Yes,” Garen smiled. He didn’t mind him being smarty pants.

He snapped his fingers and Kong Xinxue who was not far away appeared by the pit, gnashing her teeth. She was holding a timer.

“Now, I will not move and stand here for two hours,” Garen dully said. “You will use your sword to touch any areas of my body. It’s considered a pass even if it’s my hair.”

“Isn’t that very easy?” Yuria chuckled. He saw his sister, Yurijie, appearing by the pit. She looked worried.

“Brother, you have not fully recovered…”

“It’s alright,” Yuria waved his hand. “I’m almost completely healed.” He turned to look at Garen. “Brother Saber, shall we begin?”

“Yes,” Garen’s lips curled. “Anytime.”

Yurijie shook her head.

“Brother Saber is underestimating Brother. He could face off such a terrifying skilled guy earlier at the ocean… I hope Brother will be careful and not hurt Brother Saber.”

“It’s you who are looking down on your Head Minister,” Nine-Tailed Fox smiled saying as she stood by the side. “Although I don’t know what sort of a cruel battle you have experienced, but…you won’t be able to fathom the true greatness of Kong Xiaofei…”

Clang!!

Just as she finished her words, Garen maintained his posture of holding his blade in reverse in the pit as if he never moved.

Yuria, who charged forward towards Garen earlier, was tossed high up and fell on the dirt ground not far away with a bang. His black, training tight suit was full of dirt and stained mustard yellow in color.

Cough cough…

He climbed up and stared at Garen who was still motionless. His earlier relaxed demeanor disappeared without a trace.

Chapter 1183: Becoming Stronger 5

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What… was that?” Yuria replayed the earlier scene in his head.

He dashed forward again swiftly and struck the wooden blade on Garen’s thigh.

He felt the wooden blade struck empty air, and he was tossed up high and cast a few meters away.

“Again,” Yuria patted the dust off his body and dashed over.

“Forewind!!” He yelled. His wooden blade drew a streak of round arch heading at full speed towards Garen’s waist. That was also the spot where the slanting wooden blade held by Garen was undefended.

Wham!

An odd noise was heard. Yuria saw a blur in front of his eyes, was thrown into the air and felt his world spinning. His butt hurt, and coming to his senses, he once again crashed onto the ground not far away.

“Again!”

He shouted before making charging forward.

Wham!

“Again!”

Wham… Wham! Wham! Wham!!

Rounds and rounds of tossing and crashing noises were heard. Without feeling weary, Yuria charged at Garen in the pit again and again yet each time he was thrown away peculiarly.

Every time he got up, he tried to charge at different angles but unfortunately, he has not been able to get close to Garen within a two-meter range. He would only be able to stride into the area before he was hit and tossed up again.

“What the hell… is this?!” Yuria played back the entire process of him being thrown up over and over in his head.

He was bruised all over and was pained all over. Beads of perspiration dripped down from his forehead and temples, sliding down his face with an itchy feeling. A few drops almost seeped into his eyes.

“Damn it!”

He was flustered.

“Don’t tell me I can’t even see his moves clearly?”

Flashes of newly realized energy slowly released from his body. It was ripples of boundless soul power.

Yuria crouched down and arched his body like a predator about to strike his prey, sharp yet calm.

“Brother Saber… Better be careful. I’m about to get serious. I can’t really grasp this newfound power.”

Garen did not speak. He smiled, and with one hand, held the wooden blade horizontally in front of him. He looked like an unmovable mountain.

“Hydra!”

This word instinctively flashed before Yuria’s eye. His soul power released by his body became bug-like crawly lines, sticking onto Garen’s body. It seemed to absorb something out of him.

Yuria felt his body becoming a lot lighter.

It was useful!

His heart flashed with glee.

He charged forward and struck with his wooden blade.

Swoosh… Clang!!!

The wooden blade drew an arc and stabbed at a speed doubled from before. It was then pushed upwards and struck in its body by Garen’s blade tip.

A large force flowed from the body of the blade through its handle and into Yuria’s body.

Fu…

He was thrown away again without any sense of control.

Wham!

His body crashed heavily on the ground. It was still the same area he had crashed multiple times earlier. Pressures of pain surged into his brain.

“Why?…” Yuria’s vision became blurry.

“Why…” He struggled to lie on the ground and stared at Garen’s direction. He could not hear anything. He has overexerted his willpower and could not handle it any longer.

“Why… did I still fail…?”

Hydra’s ability had allowed him to see clearly how he was tossed away.

It was just that once the tip of his blade hit the body, he was prised and thrown away.

“What’s going on?” Head Minister’s voice was heard. “Can’t do it anymore? It’s only been an hour.”

“Brother…!!” His sister’s voice was heard coming from far away.

By the pit.

Yurijie covered her mouth and looked at Yuria with worry as he struggled to get up.

“Brother… How could it be?” He was the person who fought off the half Cyborg T-Rex!! For someone who could slaughter a cyborg, how could he end up here…?

Nine-Tailed Fox was fixated at Garen who was in the pit. Her eyes flashed interest and seriousness.

“I told you, you underestimated Kong Xiaofei.”

Kong Xinxue gasped in admiration but was quickly suppressed by her strong pride.

“That’s all he can do, bullying a young child!” She snorted coldly with disdain.

“Relax, he’s fine. Your Brother Saber knows when to stop,” Nine-Tailed Fox comforted when she saw the worry in Yurijie’s eyes.

“Mm…” Yurijie could tell that although her brother was tossed away multiple times, he did not actually suffer any wounds. Her worries eased up a little.

******

In the pit.

“Based on the opponent you described,” Garen spoke, “the opponent you want to defeat trumps on speed during attacking. In other words, he’s good at instant eruption of power.”

He drew his wooden sword gently, making a light swishing sound.

“So I will use a simple, hastened eruption of attack against you. Channel your energy well, observe my movements clearly, try to avoid them and hit me. This is what you should be doing.” Garen’s voice transmitted into Yuria’s ears. He was still crouching on the ground.

He lowered his head, no expression could be seen.

He initially thought that after a series of combat exchange, the difference between him and Head Minister wouldn’t be that big but now it seemed as though as Head Minister’s capability was as deep as a bottomless pit.

The figure standing there was an indestructible mountain that he couldn’t go beyond.

Fu… Shh… Fu… Shh…

Every deep breath he took inhaled and exhaled got longer. He rested shortly and regained his energy.

Yuria picked himself up from the ground and placed his wooden blade vertically against him, clenching it tightly with both of his hands.

“I’m in debt of your teaching…”

“Go full force,” Garen responded lightly. “I don’t know where these strange power of yours come from but I only see two outcomes during battle, life and death.”

“Life and death…?” Yuria knew these words were a warning to him. If this was a real combat, he would have died several times already.

“Come forth,” Garen placed his wooden blade horizontally.

Yuria’s hands grasped tightly on his blade’s handle. Finally, the soul power was raging all over him and slight peculiar changes were appearing on his body.

The savior’s power was finally fully activated!!

His muscles started to expand while his skin bruised purple and red.

Puff!

The first step. The first step that was stomped on the ground struck tremors in Yuria.

Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam…!!

With the continuous footsteps, Yuria was a fearless warrior, unafraid of death. The soul power gathered in his body and was roaring!! His body and mind charged towards Garen without turning back.

Like a hero charging at a giant.

Watching the changes he underwent, especially his eyes, Garen finally smiled. He stood there silently, watching him approaching closer like a roaring, attacking tiger.

“Forewind!” X2!

The two, same yells were heard simultaneously.

The same move was played by both their hands. Using the same technique, the wooden blades drew the same route of arc.

Cling!!

The wooden blades’ tips were held against each other for the very first time.

The blades were touching tip by tip accurately and held against without slanting on either side!!

Yurijie covered her mouth, her eyes widened to its limit.

Nine-Tailed Fox was visibly moved. Her earlier casualness disappeared.

Kong Xinxue clenched her fists lightly and looked at Garen with complicated feelings.

The wind was blowing gently. It was not by Mother Nature but rather a breeze wielded by the two wooden blades.

A saber art that seemed to be as fast as or faster than the wind. The Forewind of the Four Directional Winds was a move that proved to be of an essence of Garen’s created saber art.

And now this move was blocked by a student of his that he had taught for no more than two months.

He did not hold back.

Garen was clear on this.

“Interesting…” Garen’s lips curled wider. He looked at Yuria whose blade was locked against his. This little guy who he thought he could easily torture had surprised him time and time again.

Should he say no wonder he was the main character of this world?

Even he couldn’t help but feel envious.

Although it was a saber art that he casually came up with, to face off his move of unrestrained Forewind would take at least the Thorough Comprehension Realm to achieve the Sword Master state.

Yuria never received any formal saber art training and his Martial Arts Realm wasn’t that high yet he possessed battle instincts and intuition that far exceeded wild beasts. His inhuman instincts enabled him to instantly capture miraculous breakthrough points. And that was the only part he could catch up on, the tip of Garen’s blade.

This was also the only flaw of the Forewind.

There was nothing perfect in the world. No matter how perfect a thing was, perfection itself would present a flaw as perfect meant fulfillment, and fulfillment meant self-sufficient and sealing out any exchange from the outside world without able to advance any further. This was an absolute taboo in any path.

And so Garen placed the only flaw on the tip of the blade that has the fastest speed in the Forewind. This was an area where enemies would find it hard to capture and even experts that shared similar agility as him wouldn’t be able to discover this.

But Yuria was able to achieve it.

Using a series of action that was far slower than his.

Cling!!

The two wooden blades flung away, giving out a crisp sound of colliding metals.

Yuria took a few steps back while Garen remained where he was without moving an inch.

Between the two of them, one of them was gasping for air in desperation and perspiring endlessly, his sweat dripping on to the dirt ground; while the other was standing there quietly like a statue as if he had never moved at all. The two extreme end of situation drew a vivid comparison.

For a moment, the entire field fell silent that even the three spectators did not make a sound. They were afraid to disrupt the duo. Anyone could tell that Yuria was at a crucial moment. If he could grasp that strike more accurately, he would instantly diminish the gap between strength and reach directly to Sword Master state. Even though it was after he activated all his ability that added up to his in-the-moment burst of talent, it was still breathtaking enough.

Even for Garen, he realized this realm at the end of the first world. The Sword Master was in actual fact the equivalent of the King of the Century from the Secret Technique world. Above that would be a stage that could trigger superhuman strength but this world was restrained so the highest level in this world would be the Sword Master state.

Chapter 1184: Becoming Stronger 6

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Are you done resting?” Garen said lightly.

Hu…

Yuria took a deep breath and halted his body’s movements. His eyes gleamed with never-before-seen flickers of fighting spirit.

“I’m done.”

“Come then,” Garen showed a sense of seriousness.

The first time.

For the first time, he placed his left hand on the handle.

It was then that everyone realized that Garen had only been using one arm at the beginning. Just one, right hand to merely push Yuria to breathlessness.

An unyielding pressure was emitted by Garen, mounting Yuria to the point of slight asphyxiation.

“How powerful…!”

He gathered up his energy, no matter if it was the borrowed force from the savior or the newly realized Hydra, he turned all of it to his own.

Puff!

He took a step forward dramatically, before lunging towards Garen.

In that instance, the two wooden blades collided onto one another.

Clang!!!

******

The summer’s breeze was warm and the leaves rustled from the wind. The sun rays quavered with the flow.

Golden fragments appeared in sight as though the entire forest turned into a golden ocean with clear ripples.

Yuria lay flat on the ground with open arms in the pit, gasping for fresh air. He couldn’t be bothered with the sweat drenching the dirt ground and staining his body. He was exhausted beyond words.

He felt an endless weary sweeping him away.

Yurijie hurried to him, carrying a basin of water and a water bottle. She kneeled by her brother and carefully wiped the sweat and dirt off on Yuria with a towel.

Pat…

Sounds of footsteps drew near and stopped by Yuria.

It was Garen.

With complicated feelings, he looked at Yuria on the ground. The wooden blade in his hand was broken in half and only the lower half was held.

“I… Is that considered…a pass?” Yuria asked breathlessly.

Garen was silent for a moment before closing his eyes in contemplation.

“You’re still far from that.”

He answered in a low voice.

“Oh…”

Yuria smiled bitterly.

“But this time, you passed…” Garen suddenly turned and walked away. The remaining half of the wooden blade was stocked on his shoulder. He did not even notice Yuria and his sister sharing a smile of joy and excitement behind him.

Nine-Tailed Fox jumped into the pit agilely and walked towards Garen.

“How proud. You’re really dead set on keeping your pride.”

Nine-Tailed Fox whispered in glee as they crossed by.

“Say whatever you want to,” Garen wasn’t in the best of moods. “Your time is up next.”

“Of course,” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded and treaded lightly towards Yuria.

“See what you did, starting at such a high point. Don’t you know it’ll be hard for me to teach you?” She walked towards the siblings and looked at both their puzzled faces.

“Alright, your Head Minister had handed you over to me. I will be guiding you on far-ranged attack training,” Nine-Tailed Fox gave a sneaky smile.

******

One day later…

After resting for a whole day, Yuria and his sister were brought to an empty basement by Nine-Tailed Fox.

The four walls of the basement were of a black metal surface. There were tiny traces of bumps and hollows all over the walls. It was unknown what was the place used for.

There was only one entrance and the door was a three-meter thick, heavy metal conveyor.

The sibling duo wore bullet-proof vests and stood in the center of the basement. Each of them was holding a high-power gun. They both had a dull and absent look on their faces. It seemed that they didn’t think Nine-Tailed Fox, a young lady who looked like a student, would fiddle with such a horrifying, killing weapon.

They had labeled Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox as mysterious students and these impressions were crushed so badly by these two guns.

Nine-Tailed Fox stood opposite them with her back against the wall. She was wearing a black, tight suit that outlined her bosom and lower half body finely. The sort of sexy, tight outfit that sent little student blushing.

Both Garen and Kong Xinxue stood and watched by the side.

“And now,” Nine-Tailed Fox spoke gently, “I will train you on how to react to an intensive quick-range attack. Base on the opponent you described, he seems to be fitting to this style.”

“Mm,” Yuria focused his mind and nodded solemnly. “Yes, large-scale magnetic pins attack. He would first lay down a large number of pins so that he could draw them to attack anytime.”

“Then it’ll be easy,” Nine-Tailed Fox smiled. “What you need is how to avoid this sort of quick and mass attack, how to find out a way out from the storm.”

“So what should I do?” Yuria was earnest to learn.

“What should you do?” Nine-Tailed Fox lifted the gun in her hands. Her smile became eerie.

Seeing the gun in her hands, the sibling duo suddenly thought of a discouraging possibility.

“Don’t tell me…” The duo’s faces darkened.

Bang!!

The gun fired.

“As expected!!!!” They turned as pale as ghosts. No wonder they were required to wear bullet-proof vests. Firing a high-power gun in a secret lair with highly reflective metal walls was plain murder!!

“Hehe, you guessed it right!” Nine-Tailed Fox beamed, revealing her small, canine teeth. “Too bad there are no prizes for that.”

Ding Ding… Clang!

The bullet ricocheted in the basement. Its trajectory was too fast to be captured by the eye, only ricocheting shots could be heard and the marks of golden fiery sparks were seen scattered on the walls and ground.

The sibling duo crouched down with their hands over their head, laying flat on the ground. They didn’t dare move an inch. Their faces were distorted with fright.

Clang!

A ricochet bullet landed on the floor not more than half a meter away from them.

Ah!!!!

The duo screamed out of fear. Their faces were pale as they hugged each other tightly.

Standing by the side, Garden was speechless at the sight of both of them.

“I was still envious of this young fellow. I spent quite a long time to realize the realm yet this guy caught up using some mess of an ability. But now it seems…” He shook his head helplessly as he sighed.

Kong Xinxue also went pale. She retreated discreetly behind Garen in an attempt to use him as a shield. Ricocheting bullet has aimless targets. Whoever was hit only had bad luck to blame.

“You maniacs, can’t you give a warning before opening fire.”

“Scared?” Garen looked at her teasingly.

“No!”

Kong Xinxue would never admit that. Suddenly, she saw the change in Garen’s face as he looked at the wall behind her.

“Careful!”

He shouted.

Ah!!!

Kong Xinxue rushing into Garen’s embrace as she gave a blood-curdling scream.

“Hahaha!!” It was when she heard Garen’s guffaws that she realized she was fooled.

“You!!” She immediately broke away, wanting to curse.

Swoosh!!

Out of a sudden, a flash of silver appeared between them.

Garen nonchalantly sheathed his long blade into its scabbard.

A black bullet was slashed in half and dropped by their feet with a clang.

Kong Xinxue was startled. The chill in that instance and seeing the flickering silver light, she thought that Garen was raising his blade at her. She would never forget that undismissable sense of suppression.

“What a saber technique!” Nine-Tailed Fox clapped. “But our Ah Xue seemed to be frightened off her wits,” she teased.

“You’re the one scared off your wits!!” Kong Xinxue has actually never experienced such random, dangerous combat world in the past few worlds. It has been a peaceful journey for her. Although she knew Nine-Tailed Fox back then, she knew they were different from her but she did not take it to heart. This time was different. Having witnessed first hand of that saber art, she felt fear.

“Head Minister… Are you sure you’re human!?”

Yuria got up in disbelief.

Yurijie nodded with force. If it weren’t for her seeing it with her own eyes, it would be hard to imagine a human being taking down a bullet with a cold weapon. Even if the bullet ricocheted a few times, causing the speed to decrease, it was trajectory that could be caught by the naked eye.

Garen smiled.

“Focus your mind on it. After the first ricochet, the bullet isn’t as hard to catch anymore.”

“Yes,” Nine-Tailed Fox clapped. “Now you two fire at me. Don’t worry, I have changed the bullet to a special kind. Those that are hit will not die. At most it will cause this huge of a wound,” She gestured circles about the size of a knuckle.

“This is what you call a special bullet?!! What difference is this from an explosive bullet!?” Yuria was absolutely terrified. “No… This is not considered a bullet anymore? This is a cannon…”

“I’m sure it’s not a cannon,” Nine-Tailed Fox could guess what he was trying to convey. “So, to avoid death and to protect your sister, young man, bring your strongest instinct to full play!” She gave a thumbs up, “do your best!”

“Do your best my ass!” Yuria wanted to scream but Nine-Tailed Fox did not provide him the chance. She held her hand up to the ceiling and fired the gun again.

Bang!

The bullet started ricocheting.

Bang bang bang bang bang!!

This time it wasn’t just one bullet. Nine-Tailed Fox knew they both of them were unwilling to open fire so she blew six shots continuously, finishing a round and tossed the gun aside.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Four of the ricocheting shots rebounded towards her.

A white ribbon appeared in her hand. Nine-Tailed Fox agilely made a turn and dodge the bullet at ease like an acrobat dancing on the tip of a sword. The white ribbon fluttered gently as though she was presenting a beautiful dance.

The sibling duo watched with eyes wide open.

Garen paid close attention to Nine-Tailed Fox’s movements.

“Awesome… Her speed has already surpassed that of human…”

“She once said that although her demonic arts couldn’t be used, the monstrous body attribute has left behind some superhuman abilities such as this speed,” Kong Xinxue said in a low voice. After that blade-slash by Garen, she has calmed herself down. Although she was still nervous, she was not as afraid as before.

“Oh, really?” Garen fell deep into his thoughts.

Chapter 1185: Business Talk 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Swoosh!

A specially made bullet swept by Nine-Tailed Fox’s ear. In that course of direction, the bullet seemed to slow down, gently brushing her hair before firing off.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh!!

And then in a blink of an eye, it resumed to its hastening speed. A few ricocheting bullets leaped past her without touching her body, clothes or even the ribbon on her hair.

“Shoot me!” Nine-Tailed Fox suddenly gave a dazzling smile and yelled at the sibling duo.

Ah!!!

Yuria and his sister jumped in surprise. They couldn’t help but pulled their gun’s trigger.

Bang bang bang!!

Ah!!!! There was no safety catch!!

With pale faces, the sibling duo was visibly shaken by the enormous counterforce. But how could the gun shoot just like that? There was no safety catch whatsoever…

The bullet ricocheted everywhere. This time it rebounded here and there without any pattern, increasing its possibility of danger.

Even Garen who was standing on the side grew solemn.

“She’s really at it recklessly… This sort of specially built gun is big trouble using it on people.”

Kong Xinxue couldn’t be bothered with her pride. She hid tightly behind Garen.

Pat.

Suddenly, Nine-Tailed Fox snapped her fingers. Her lips curled into a peculiar smile.

“Open.”

Buzz!

The wall behind her trembled violently, a large magnetic force appeared out of nowhere.

Clang!

A bullet was sucked into it.

But more ricocheting bullets were still drawing a winding trajectory and all heading towards the direction of Nine-Tailed Fox.

“Nine-Tailed!”

The white ribbons around Nine-Tailed Fox shot out in all directions. With swooshing sounds, nine, white ribbons spread out like a fox’s nine tails, fluttering and waving swiftly. The instantaneous display embodied a peacock fanning its tail.

Reacting promptly, Nine-Tailed Fox stepped forward and dashed towards the flying bullets.

“Watch carefully!”

In a white flash, she bent down slightly and landed on a surface not far away. The white ribbons behind her were retrieved.

Everything went completely silent and all that was left was her down on one knee.

“Where are… the bullets?” Yuria hugged his sister, still frightened. Hearing the silence, he regained his composure slightly and looked at Nine-Tailed Fox. He could not bear to watch earlier. The image of such a beautiful, young lady being blown in the head was something he would never want to come by. It was simply too cruel.

He just closed his eyes.

Swoosh. Nine-Tailed Fox stood up with a gentle smile on her face.

Extending her arm, there were nine bullets of various sizes in her palm. Some bullets were crushed to a few pieces but she caught them all.

“Did you watch carefully?” Nine-Tailed Fox’s turned her palm down, letting the bullets to fall freely onto the ground.

“…!”

Yuria swallowed his saliva. He was totally oblivious of what happened earlier.

Yurijie lifted her hidden head from his embrace. She was puzzled by the silence. Although she was baffled, she felt relieved. She was not clear what had happened.

Only Garen who stood beside watched the entire process. He applause.

The clapping was crisp, loud and clear in the space.

“What a skillful ribbon art… more so on your dodging skill,” he complimented. “Such a dodging level of ability really surpassed that of human…”

Nine-Tailed Fox’s evading speed was far beyond any regular being. She must have used some special tactic to enhance it just like him. This sort of ability that did not belong to mortals would require a heavy price to pay.

Garen himself has the Soul Ring Power while Nine-Tailed Fox should possess something similar. She was a thousand-year-old demon after all and who could tell for sure for those who transmigrated and experienced various worlds.

With the flow of time, a few hours clocked in quickly.

Nine-Tailed Fox had already drawn out more than ten guns and fired them nonstop. Shell casings were scattered on the ground.

The sibling duo had many bullets scraped past them. Sweat drenched their frightened bodies. Their faces were pale white to the point of dehydration.

“How is it?” Nine-Tailed Fox maintained her composure without breaking a sweat. She treaded lightly around them. She was playing with a white ribbon in her hand, like a child playing with a toy. One could not tell she was the same person who dodged multiple bullets.

“Just how do we… dodge…?” Yuria carefully observed Nine-Tailed Fox’s figure, “I… I really have no clue!” Sweat dripped from his forehead into his eyes. He wiped it away quickly opened his eyes. Nine-Tailed Fox’s face was in close proximity, so close that the distance between their noses was only a finger’s width.

He was startled and quivered.

Swoosh!

Nine-Tailed Fox leaped back a few meters, as agile as a deer.

“Looks like there’s no realization. Let’s continue then. Ah Xue, please help to collect some bullet cartridge. It’s piled up at the passage just outside the door.”

“Alright!… Alright!” Kong Xinxue ran out to the opened passageway. Not only was there a strong smell of gunpowder, her life was at risk. It was not the place to be. She couldn’t wait to get out of there and now was the chance.

Garen carried his blade and walked to the side of the wall, laying against it to rest. Seeing Nine-Tailed Fox’s figure, her dodging postures was on play-back in his mind.

“Such a strange, evading ability. It is not at the level of humans. She definitely depended on some sort of special ability to enhance it. That maneuvering speed is faster than mine. My instant attack is quicker than hers but dodging and maneuver are unlike hers.”

He compared between them and felt that he and Nine-Tailed Fox has their own pros.

In the next session, Nine-Tailed Fox held a gun and fired at Yuria without holding back. She aimed at dangerous areas such as Yuria’s clothes and hair each time.

This frightened Yuria to the point that he dared not move at all.

A day of training quickly came to an end. Bullet casings and bullet fragments scattered around, densely covering the entire ground.

The night was near and the secret room was getting dark. Sunlight was fading from the bullet-proof window on the top, sinking the secret room into darkness.

The first day of bullets-dodging training ended officially. Yuria felt he came up empty-handed except that his heart was about to fall off.

Yurijie was a nerve-wreck. She collapsed on her bed as soon as she reached the central resting bed in the base. She didn’t even think of showering before she hit the sack.

The base has a specific showering area but it was hogged by Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue. Garen lay in bed, his sharp ears could clearly hear the two ladies fooling around.

Bam bam bam.

Suddenly, there was a knock on the door.

“Come in,” Garen didn’t need to guess who it was. “The door’s not locked.”

Hesitating for a bit, the door opened with a creak.

Yuria walked in. His body reeked of scents of ointment and medicine. A band-aid was stuck on his nose. That was evidence of a bullet scraping the bridge of his nose during the day.

“Brother Saber.”

“Sit,” Garen did not get up. He continued lying in bed. There was only one chair in the room for Yuria to sit down.

“I’m here to seek your advice on the matter that happened during the day,” Yuria was direct.

“Day?” Garen replied non-committally. “Didn’t you train the whole day? Still not gaining anything?”

“You can tell,” Yuria gave a bitter smile. “I really learned nothing! I have tried to use all my power to trace the trajectory but it was no use… If it weren’t for sister Nine-Tailed Fox avoiding the vital organs, I don’t know how many times I would have died.”

He sat down in the chair and took a deep breath. A sense of sorrow surrounded him.

Garen didn’t even bother to lift a finger.

“Whether you gain anything or not, won’t you know once you put it to test?”

“Put to test?” Yuria was stunned. He did not know how to try it out.

Clang!

A silvery chill slashed towards his neck, striking a streak of arc in the dark room.

Chills went down his spine as Yuria didn’t think twice to throw himself backward. He saw the blade hacked no more than one centimeter from his forehead, severing a fringe of his hair in half.

“Not bad, young man.” Garen sheathed his blade and returned to lie in bed.

Yuria was in a daze. He sprawled down on the ground in an attempt to evade the stab. Now, even the cold ground could not hide his pleasant surprise.

“I… dodged? Did you hold back, Brother Saber!?” He immediately reacted to it and got up shouting.

“No,” Garen yawned. “It was the same as when I tackled you. This is my normal attacking speed.”

“…” Yuria’s expression was strange. Surprise, joy, pain, struggle, everything was on display in his face. “… Really?”

“Yes.”

Garen closed his eyes and replied listlessly.

Yuria stood there flabbergasted for a moment before decisively giving a bow salute to Garen. He turned and left in a hurry. The energy released by him was entirely different now.

If what Garen said was true and he did not hold back, that means he started from struggling to block against Garen’s strike to evading his ambush. This level of improvement was quite evident.

Hearing Yuria running out in joy, Garen who was lying in bed, opened his eyes.

“The fruition that I worked so long to achieve… was caught up by this young fellow in a few days… isn’t he the main character?” He had a complicated expression in his eyes.

It would be uncomfortable for anyone whose many years of fruition be caught up in a few days. This was envy, an envy that saw his years of work and sacrifice not to be worthwhile.

******

The training was the same on the second day. The difference was that Yuria went on site alone while Yurijie stayed on the sidelines. Only Yuria could tackle such high difficulty level of evading training so Yurijie who possessed no special powers was off the hook.

Nine-Tailed Fox changed her tactic.

The two metal walls top and bottom interchanged to release large magnetic force.

Wham!!

Countless bullet casings on the ground fired up into the air in extreme speed.

Yuria stood in the center.

“Winds of Four Directions!!” He yelled. Four white blade lights appeared around his sword. He cast away a large number of shell casings amongst clanging sounds.

But many bullet fragments still penetrated the defense net and hit him.

Chapter 1186: Business Talk 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Wham!

A pry bar that was sucked up and stuck with countless bullet shell casings on the wall suddenly dropped from above crashing towards him.

“Upwind!!” Yuria defended with his saber art.

Garen stood on the side watching, yawning at times. The training has been going on for a few hours. Once the defense was missed, Yuria would receive an inhuman punishment, that is to run naked…

The bullet fragments pulled by the giant magnetic force have sharp edges. Under the high velocity, it easily tore Yuria’s clothes, especially when the bullets flew from the bottom up… sounds of his pants tearing up could be heard.

Nine-Tailed Fox chuckled as though she was watching a comedy as she manipulated the magnetic force to open and shut. It seemed like she was playing and having fun rather than training him. Yuria really had the worst of luck to have her as an instructor.

Finally, the training came to an end.

Yuria improved at the speed of light. From being punished to run naked at the beginning to not being bothered about it anymore. His dodging ability also improved from being a mess to only a small amount of fragments escaping from his defense.

“Hydra!” Yuria suddenly yelled. His skin became purplish red. His muscles expanded. His body thickened. He activated the force of Savior and Hydra at the same time.

“Four Directional Winds!!” He held his saber with both hands and four blade sparks rose in connection by him, instantly blocking a large number of bullet fragments flying upwards from the ground.

“Almost there,” Nine-Tailed Fox clapped and stopped the magnetic force. She treaded over. “If you meet that opponent again, your current state should be able to catch up to his attacking speed as well as other large-scale dense and far range shooting.”

“I feel it too,” Yuria nodded heavily. “Thank you for your guidance!” From these recent days spent together, he now knew that Nine-Tailed Fox wasn’t as young as she looked. He began to address her respectably in replacement of the earlier casualness.

“Now, you should do what you should be doing,” Garen got up and walked near.

“Do what I should be doing…” Yuria smiled bitterly. He did not know how he should answer.

He only meant to look for his mother but after meeting Galouro and learning about a series of events, he wasn’t that worried about his mother’s whereabouts. The only thing he was concerned was when that self-proclaimed root doctor, Jiatai, would come and seek trouble.

The Vulture’s capabilities were too powerful, and he felt asphyxiated with the pressure and stress.

But they didn’t let him off the hook just once. They bore no murderous intent when they had the absolute upper hand, there must be some unknown reason.

“Brother, it’s all on you to take care of the person from the Vulture,” Yurijie walked over and whispered. Witnessing the training for the past few days, she had attempted to catch up on brother’s progress but unfortunately, she possessed no special abilities. She couldn’t keep up with this explosive type of improvement. She could only back down and watch at the sidelines.

“Relax,” Yuria regained confidence. “Comparing our lower limit, he can’t possibly win!” He clenched his fist.

“…”

Garen, Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue could do nothing about it. Garen’s seemingly joking combat ideology has been deeply embedded into Yuria’s heart and now it was to see if the original script would continue to roll on.

******

After the special training, everything resumed to normal.

Yuria and his sister remained in Lily of the Valley, without leaving again.

Garen and Kong Xinxue ‘traveled’ back home, reuniting with the transmigrators to discuss the plot’s current trend.

Garen managed to pick up intel about the Four Great Cornerstone from these people.

Savior, Mind Reader, Illusionist, Slayer.

Four main characters forever transmigrating and rebirthing. They would naturally experience overlapping lives each time, whether against each other or as alliances. There was some sort of magnetic force between them, attacking them together.

A group of people gathered in Nine-Tailed Fox’s seaside villa to discuss the upcoming strategy.

“So you’re saying that the remaining three Great Cornerstones have yet to appear. The only one we can confirm is Yuria, the Savior?” The female cop, Li Hua asked. She has a quick temper and was proficient in the snatching type of close combat wushu. She could be considered an expert but compared to the Vulture… her capabilities were similar to Silver, perhaps inferior. However, combat was not her strongest but rather her marksmanship. It was said to be revered of.

“What about Yong He? What do you think?” Uncle Technician looked at Nine-Tailed Fox.

Garen was sitting on the side and it was the first time he heard someone calling Nine-Tailed Fox Yong He. This seemed to be her other formal name.

“That’s easy…” Nine-Tailed Fox beamed, “Why don’t we just help Savior? We lend our powers to him and the more he’s powerful, the safer we are.”

“Getting involved in this and following the original plot, many who lent their power to Savior have died. Is it really a good idea?” The young lady with the ginger hair, Yuan Xing, frowned. She was a mature uncle in the past life. The steadiness characteristics of the uncle and the background of the beautiful young lady mixed together gave a peculiar paradox.

“Or I’ll arrange everyone to go to other countries by sea to avoid the disaster.” Her family has an abundant financial resource in this life, charting the top hundred in the world. Arranging this matter would be a cinch.

“What about my pigs?” Xu Yuan, a brunette beauty, curled her lips, “I have just invested three hundred million in the new farm.”

“Pigs pigs pigs! Is there anything in your brain other than pigs?” Yuan Xing smacked her.

“But…”

“No buts! I will compensate you on your pigs,” Yuan Xing was annoyed.

“Now the problem is to first ascertain when the remaining Four Great Cornerstones are arriving. Although we, as transmigrators, are not within the control range of the Four Great Cornerstones’ ability and will not be manipulated by the Mind Reader and Illusionist but on the contrary, this sort of attribute would definitely trigger their attention and get them alerted,” Nine-Tailed Fox explained calmly.

“Everybody pitch in, how do we help?”

“I will cover the expenses,” Yuan Xing flung her arm in generosity. “A budget of fifty billion at the very least!”

“I will take care of the firearms and provide an emergency special task force of around two hundred manpower. They are military elites discharged from various nations! They can handle a few T-Rex sorts of experts without any problems!” Nine-Tailed Fox was confident.

“I can handle the logistics of biochemical drugs,” Pan Pan said. Seeing Garen’s unwitting eyes, he smiled. “Although I am a chef, I have researched a lifetime of biochemical and medicinal my past life. I was a top academician hired by the country. After all, I have lived a few generations and can’t simply do without any capability.”

“I’ll be in charge of intel,” Kong Xinxue spoke with confidence. “I will settle any possible intel turning up on the web, as well as offense and defense.”

“We will be counting on you for head-on combats, Yong He and Li Hua,” Yuan Xing looked at Nine-Tailed Fox and female cop, Li Hua.

“No problem. Leave the far range to me, and close combat to Yong He,” Lu Hua answered solemnly. She then glanced over at Garen.

“Come to think of it, Garen’s ability is quite good. He can take on the mid-range cadres of Vulture. We need a base for our logistics and when the time comes, we’ll depend on you to defend and sound the alarm.”

The way they saw it, although Garen was strong, it was only limited to ordinary people. Taking on the real experts in this world would be beyond his reach.

This level of playing field could only be tackled by Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua as an aid.

Only with Nine-Tailed Fox in all her seriousness was the strongest existence among the transmigrators.

“Once Slayer appear, we’ll depend on you, Yong He,” Li Hua solemnly told Nine-Tailed Fox.

“Relax,” Nine-Tailed Fox expression grew stern. “Once it’s that time, I will unleash that.”

“I don’t have a problem here,” Garen did not push it. He wasn’t in the know on how strong Slayer would be, being the finest in this world and judging by Nine-Tailed’s tone, she still has a stronger trump card in hiding.

The transmigrators who were present could deduce that Nine-Tailed was the strongest and holding them together. With her on the top, the others could take a seat back and relax.

“Apart from me, if Slayer were to really appear and go against us, aren’t there still Demonic Lamp and Sea God in the front line? With two almighty blocking in the front, we can be at ease a little,” Nine-Tailed Fox said in a low voice.

“It would be great if they could take part, but I contacted friends from the other two continents a few days ago,” Yuan Xing smiled bitterly. “Demonic Lamp went to another world for a mission. He won’t be able to return for another three to five years. Sea God’s whereabouts are unknown. If he went to another world, then it would be troublesome.”

“Demonic Lamp, Sea God?” It was the first time Garen heard of these two names.

“Mm, these two elites hit it off the best in this world,” Kong Xinxue whispered explaining to Garen. “Demonic Lamp is now the vice president of Slann as well as military head minister with military power over the country. If he could dispatch the troop to encircle and annihilate then Slayer may not stand a chance no matter how strong he is. He’d have no choice but to reincarnate.”

“Savage!” Garen nodded. This planet was a lot larger than the few planet worlds he had experienced. It was indeed savage to be able to make it thus far in a world with huge restrictions.

“What about Sea God?”

“The leading expert of the Manatee Clan. It’s not human but a large animal being and live in the oceanic trench in the deep sea. Its body is tough beyond imagination and stretch as long as a few thousand meters, about the size of an island. One sweep of its tail could overturn a million ton-class vessels.

After it reincarnated to a manatee, it focused on cultivating martial arts. Moreover, he had once reincarnated into the world of heroes and now he has become an overlord of the entire ocean,” Kong Xinxue introduced briefly.

“Not human huh… Tsk tsk,” Garen’s competitiveness died. With the existence of such a huge being, he in his current, tiny state could be killed with just a sneeze. He thought that he had developed fast in this lifetime but he did not think that there would be someone crazier. Those who trained to such level in this world were really true maniacs.

Chapter 1187: Duel 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I’m just going to focus following up on Yuria then. After all, the Savior’s friendship must be continued,” Garen said.

“That’s not a bad point. You and Yuria have a natural, master and disciple relationship, just take advantage of this,” Nine-Tailed Fox agreed. “However… I still feel that something is wrong. Ever since the plot has changed, I’ve already felt this.”

“You too?” Li Hua frowned. “Same here. When we were tracking down Vulture’s deployment staff and we fought hand in hand with the two long-range gunmen, I’ve already sensed that the situation seems to have derailed from the original plot. Shouldn’t Vulture’s main focus be on the Saviors at the moment?”

“We should look into this.” Right now, Nine-Tailed Fox really seemed like a big shot and not that common, mischievous and adorable little girl.

Garen sat in the corner looking at everyone discussing every possibility. His mind, on the other hand, had drifted far away.

“I’m going to go wash up a bit.” He was a bit bored and whispered to Kong Xinxue. She was currently in the midst of a discussion with Yuan Xing regarding staff placement issues and nodded her head in acknowledgment.

Garen got up and left the room, closing the door softly behind him.

The door was definitely soundproof. Not far away, two stalwart bodyguards decked in black uniform glanced over, then retracted their stares swiftly.

Walking on the thick black carpet, Garen soon came to the washroom. He stood in front of the golden-rimmed mirror and sized himself up.

Staring back in the mirror was Kong Xiaofei’s figure. His short, red hair, his features firm and delicate, his strong physique, his stocky and imposing build, and his solid muscles bulging beneath his white shirt.

He turned on the faucet, hot water streamed out and washed into the sink beneath it.

Garen splashed water on his face a few times, and took deep breaths, feeling much better and relieved.

He could still hear the vague engine and honk sounds from the boats out in the sea. There were people messing and playing around with each other, which made quite a bustling scene.

“Staying on in this world is not an idea, I should go on some missions and earn some Contribution Points. I guess I’ll drop by the Lighthouse Headquarters and have a look.” Garen had this sudden thought in his mind. This world had already confirmed the battle among the Four Great Cornerstones and with huge organizations like Vulture involved in it, the safest choice would be keeping his distance from the hub.

As for Li Hua and the others, perhaps they were the only ones who knew the real purpose they forcefully included themselves in the plot. Contribution points would be one thing, and the second purpose would be gaining benefits from it.

After all, the Four Great Cornerstones were the most mysterious beings in this world, possessing such extraordinary powers in a world with such strict restrictions. If Garen was able to gain a clear idea of this cause and master the principle, he would then be able to achieve this world’s lowest grade of martial powers if he transmigrated to other worlds.

“Perhaps some of the people here were also pulled into this and so they had to take the initiative, like Yuan Xing, Kong Xinxue, and even Pan Pan; whereas some others might be here merely for beneficial purposes, like Li Hua and Nine-Tailed Fox.”

After having a rough understanding of the current situation, Garen decided to put himself in earlier on due to the Soul Energy Forces. Fully adapting to this identity was probably one of the centers of the whirlpool. Later on, Kong Xinxue would basically become Athena who would be constantly kidnapped in the plot. The part where the mind reader fell in love with Kong Xinxue was the most crucial part of the original plot.

“But now, I’m afraid I can’t just join out of boredom anymore…” Garen forced a smile as he turned the faucet off. Lifting his head, he analyzed his face in the mirror.

All of a sudden, a black figure walked by the corridor outside behind him.

“?”

Garen frowned slightly. The reflection he saw from the mirror was a short silhouette and it seemed like a girl. Due to her speed and he was not paying attention, he missed it.

Turning around, the empty corridor stared back at him.

“My hearing shouldn’t have degenerated to this point, should it?”

Other than his sense of sight, he was slightly doubtful about his two other senses. With his Sword Master grade of sense, there was definitely no way he would miss anyone nearby.

He recalled the black figure from just now. It seemed to be a little girl dressed poorly in tattered clothes, she had long hair, but aside from that, the rest was sort of a blur to him.

“Perhaps there are other transmigrators? There are guards stationed everywhere here and people standing guard front back left right, there’s no way anyone can just casually enter and leave,” Garen’s inner intuition was ringing.

He walked out and stood at the golden corridor, he noted the attentive guards on duty at both ends of the corridor.

Frowning as he made no discovery, Garen returned to the washroom to dry his hands with the hand dryer. Then only did he go back to the room where everyone was discussing the problem.

*********************

Sweeping across the blue sea, the seagulls screeched loudly and together with the sounds from the waves, it gave off a refreshing feeling.

The sun shone on the sea’s surface, standing on the beach one could see sparkles of gold on the sea’s surface.

“How wealthy…!” Yuria was strolling on the beach with his sister. Passing by the beach umbrellas, he could not help but gawk at the beautiful ladies under the umbrella sunbathing with their bare naked chests.

“Brother… Can you not embarrass me?” Yurijie could not help but pinched him hard. Both of them were wearing orange colored swimsuits, just that hers was a bikini. However, her figure was obviously overshadowed by most of the beauties on the beach. As she observed Yuria’s gaze constantly fleeting toward the ladies, her heart was full of jealousy.

“Why is it embarrassing!” Yuria was like a legendary who had no clue on how to conduct himself with dignity, he did not even feel guilty for stealing a few more glimpses. “Aren’t I just fulfilling their original intention of dressing up by staring? Think about it, these gorgeous ladies spent so much effort to doll up, but if nobody even enjoys or appreciate their effort then what’s the use of it.”

“Well, you could at least be a little more discreet! Such an embarrassment!” Yurijie complained as her face turned a bright shade of scarlet red.

“Why is it embarrassing?” Yuria shook his finger, “Xiaojie, seems like you have yet to truly realize Brother Saber’s essence!”

“Essence?” Once the topic related to Garen was brought up, Yurijie’s face instantly turned solemn. “What essence?”

“I remember Brother Saber once said, if you want to achieve victory, you have to use some sort of secret technique or an unexpected attack to catch your enemy by surprise. Shock them so much that they can’t react on time, and then you’ll be able to succeed.” Yuria was getting slightly proud as he spoke about his feelings. “So I came to a new realization of this principle.”

“What principle?”

“That is…” As Yuria was about to talk about the true meaning of Sword Master, his eyes suddenly stared at a lone pleasure boat out at sea.

The white pleasure boat was straight towards the both of them swiftly. Two figures could be seen standing at the bow of the boat from afar.

One of them had his arms crossed around his chest. He was tall and muscular with a doctor’s white coat draped over his suit that was being blown by the sea breeze, which made him neither fish nor fowl.

“That’s very fast…” Yuria’s expression panicked.

“What?”

Turning around, Yurijie saw the two people on the pleasure boat.

The other person was selectively ignored by the sibling duo as their focus was entirely upon the Root Doctor, Jiatai.

Faraway, Root Doctor greeted them with a wave of his hand, smiling.

“No, not here! There are too many people here! The innocent will be hurt!” Yuria looked around. The horrible sight of police’s corpses lying everywhere came to mind and his heart fell. The unscrupulous behavior of Vulture’s men definitely left an impression on him.

“Xiaojie, go find Brother Saber. Give Galouro a call too and tell him the situation over here, I’ll handle the Root Doctor!” Yuria said firmly.

“No!” Yurijie was alarmed, “I want to be with you…””Listen to me!” She was straight away cut off mid-sentence, and Yuria had never looked so serious before.

“Don’t worry, I’ve been through so many miserable trainings just to be ready for this day!”

“Brother…!” Yurijie exclaimed with concern.

“Go quickly!”

Yuria pushed his sister and started marching towards the part of the beach in the distant where there were lesser people.

Yurijie gritted her teeth, this had already happened, all she could do was to find Garen and the others as soon as possible to save her brother on time.

Getting up, she swiftly ran in the direction of Nine-Tailed Fox’s villa by the sea.

********************

“What! The Root Doctor is here?!” Garen stood up, blurting out in shock. He stared at Yurijie who was panting in front of him. Nine-Tailed Fox and the others were still in the room discussing details as he leaned against the doorframe outside to take a breather. Just when he was starting to feel bored, he saw Yurijie, who was invited along, running towards him. The moment she approached him, she blurted out the distressing news.

“Yuria went alone?” He pulled out two of his long sabers and asked solemnly.

“Yeah, Brother says he’ll be fine himself, but I’m still worried…” Yurijie’s face was full of concern.

“Lead the way.”

Garen was silent. It was still uncertain whether the Savior really did grow up. In the event they were unexpectedly messed by Vulture’s men, all their previous hard work would be wasted. One of the reincarnation characteristics of the Four Great Cornerstones was that once one dies, one would have his or her memories wiped out and would not remember one’s identity.

Therefore, the only way to maintain his relationship with the Savior was to ensure that Yuria did not die.

Both of them left the villa quickly. On the way, Garen used his mobile phone to contact Nine-Tailed Fox and the others. They, too, soon caught up.

Not long after, sounds of metal clashing from a distance could be heard.

Without hesitation, both of them darted straight in the direction of the sound’s source. They were getting nearer to the place where the battle was going on.

Whoosh!

All of a sudden, waves of sand blew up in front of Garen, nicely blocking his and Yurijie’s path.

They instantly paused in their tracks and raised their hands to block the sand from getting into their eyes.

After the sand fell to the ground, a one-eyed man dressed in a blue, military uniform appeared before the two of them.

The man was expressionless and had silver, short hair, the white gloves he was wearing was illuminating under the midday sun.

“Vulture No.7, Yindu.”

He bowed his head slightly, it was a sort of etiquette, a courtesy to an opponent.

“Get out of the way or die!” Sword in hand, Garen’s face darkened.

“Die?” The corners of Yindu’s mouth raised slightly into a smirk. “You can try.”

Hiss…

In a flash, Garen lunged forward, dragging a long print on the sand with his feet. In a blink of an eye, the saber appeared in his hands and lashed out.

Swoosh!!

The silver arc instantly struck Yindu’s neck.

The breeze from the blade blew the short hair on Yindu’s temples. He raised his arm suddenly and grabbed the saber’s blade.

Chapter 1188: Duel 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clang!!!

Yuria held up a gold stool and grudgingly deflected the silver needle flying towards him. He was rolling around and jumping about on the beach like a monkey.

The Root Doctor, on the other hand, stood firm as he twitched his fingers. He seemed quite relaxed.

“Looks like you are more agile than before.” He yawned and continued saying, “but you are still extremely weak.”

“That’s just because I haven’t shown you what I’m capable of yet!” Yuria shouted while dodging the almost invisible steel needles. “What are you conspiring?! I haven’t done anything wrong, so why are you purposely… Hu… Coming after me?!”

“Conspiring?” Root Doctor Jiatai lit up a cigarette casually, took a puff, and exhaled smoke rings. Under the scalding sun, it was almost impossible to see traces of the white smoke rings.

“I have no interest in explaining to someone who’s about to die. Instead of using this time to talk, why don’t we settle this quickly so I can go back to drink my milk? Apparently, milk strengthens chest muscles, recently I’ve been feeling that my pectoral muscles seemed to be drooping…”

(Pectoral muscles? Aren’t you sure they were not breast enhancements?)

Yuria was at a loss whether to cry or to laugh. As he was about to speak, he did a backflip just in time to avoid another attack of a row of steel needles.

The entire row of steel needles flew towards where he stood, causing a racket as it came into contact with the sand.

“Alright,” Jiatai looked around. “That’s about it, time to pack things up.”

Just like before, he reached out his right arm slowly, aiming it in the direction of where Yuria was at.

“This move again!!” Yuria’s whole body began to shake.

“Brother! Catch!” Suddenly, a voice sounded from afar.

Yuria turned around, just in time to see a long item spinning towards him. It was his sister! She had managed to make it on time and even brought along his saber!

It was as if he was on an emotional rollercoaster. He was so close to giving up all hope, but now the hope had returned.

With a leap, he dove toward the saber.

“Grab.” At this moment, Jiatai’s hand tightened up slowly.

Buzz…

The sand on the ground began to vibrate from deep within.

Boom!!!

In that instant, countless sand particles flew up. A mass amount of needles rushed upwards, all aimed at Yuria in the middle.

“It’s over.”

Jiatai said lightly.

“Winds of Four Directions!”

Almost at the same time, four rays of gold light appeared midair.

In an instant, the countless needles as fine as an ox’s hair were blocked by the golden lights, bent, broke and smashed out into all directions.

Whoosh!

One of the broken needles brushed Jiatai’s cheek, drawing blood.

He was stunned. Absolutely stunned…

His frame of mind now was probably as perplexed as Garen back then. Not everyone could relate to this feeling of seeing a bastard who took only ten or more days to crack a technique one had been pouring all of his heart on for the past several years. The mixed emotions of jealousy and grief aroused a deep, concealed feeling.

When the person first told him, he did not believe the person at all. That was why he decided to personally make a move, all to prove that the person was wrong.

“But now…” Jiatai reached out and caress the wound on his face, his fingers dabbing on the blood that was trickling down. “It really is…blood.”

One by one, droplets of blood continued dripping on to the sand, dyeing the sand blood red from its original golden.

Garen held his saber with one hand as he stared silently at the figure standing a couple of meters away.

“Still not giving way?”

Yindu had on gloves that seemed to be made of gold or iron, his hands were still intact. However, the gloves that supposed to block weapons were currently covering his mouth.

Droplets of blood continued to drip down from between his fingers.

Cough cough…

He coughed a few times.

Slowly, he tried to recall the scene that just took place.

He did manage to grab the blade, there was no hidden surprise. The saber did not get through his gloves, and neither did it touch any other parts of him. So why? Why!

“Why…!” Yindu did not expect himself to be fatally injured as the battle had just started. After all, he was Vulture No.7, ranked number seven among the tens and thousands of elite troops of human armed forces!

“Do you think I’m as silly and stupid as the others and explain to you the profound mystery of my ultimate move? Save it.” Garen said impatiently. “Alright, listen up, let me pass through, I’m in a rush.”

“Are you humiliating me?!” Yindu struggled to stand and keep his body straight, “Or are you saying that you’re definitely going to win!?”

“Well, is that not it?” Garen asked, pointing his saber towards the ground.

Suddenly, he caught a glimpse of his opponent smirking. It was not a good sign.

Boom!!!

A ball of flames suddenly exploded where Garen was at. It was a bomb!

The bomb ignited a ball of scarlet red flames on the sand, its massive impact exploding in all directions, sweeping up scorching hot air.

Among the flames, the burning smog suddenly started to spread.

A loud slam sounded.

A golden spark of saber divided the flames into two, like a golden crescent, which was orientated at Yindu.

Boom!!!

Another violent explosion broke between the saber and Yindu. The gravel rushed up into the sky along with the massive impact of the explosion turned the small grains of sand into countless hidden deadly weapons, landing on the saber smashing the tracks all over.

“Hmmph!”

Garen grunted. His body was still midair in the midst of a somersault, his saber a total miss as it was shaken by the explosion’s gigantic force of impact.

Hu hu hu hu…!

Together with his saber, he started spinning like a wheel, slowly forming a huge golden wheel saber and crashed towards Yindu.

Yindu’s expression changed swiftly and started backing down fast. After a match like this the first time, he already knew close-ranged battles with someone like Garen, a Sword Master-Level person, would be the most idiotic thing for him to do, hence why he was badly injured before he could even exert his best advantage.

However, he would not repeat the same mistake again!

“Super-miniature.”

He casually dug through his shirt pocket and scattered the items outward.

Numerous spores-like tiny bomb particles rushed over to Garen. In a flash, hundreds of super-miniature bombs formed a hemispherical shape and rushed towards Garen to cover him.

Whoosh!

Right at that moment, Garen’s figure darted to the side in midair, slanted his saber and spearing it into the beach nearby.

Boom boom boom boom!!

Countless sparks of flames blocked Yindu’s sight as continuous sounds of the super-miniature bombs exploded. He had an extremely bad feeling all of a sudden.

Just as he was turning around to leave, he saw a silver-white saber directed straight at his neck.

“What a pity.” Garen peeped out from behind the saber. “You lost.”

From the beginning to the end, he only had one hand on his saber, even right this moment.

Yindu raised his head slightly, beads of perspiration seeped down his forehead but he dare not wipe them away. As an agile sort of powerhouse, he was still tricked by the opponent and being played around like a monkey. Even his strongest point could not be exerted to try to get a hold of his enemy, and that was no doubt the biggest irony to him.

“How did you do it?” He asked dryly.

“How did I do it?” Garen was speechless. “You’re someone who uses explosives, yet here you are in a close-range battle with me competing for our speed. Wouldn’t it be ironic if I, a Sword Master, was to lose to you? Do you even know what are the main cores for Sword Techniques and Saber Techniques? Speed! Ruthless! Accuracy!”

“I can make seven shots in one second, there’s no way you can be faster than me!” Yindu was slowly losing his calm.

“I can do sixteen in one second,” Garen said lightly.

“…”

********************

On the empty beach.

Yuria both hands were on his saber, facing the Root Doctor Jiatai.

His whole body’s center of gravity was slightly sinking. He seemed like a cheetah, arching its back searching for its prey, his sharp eyes dead fixed on Jiatai, his hands continuously adjusting the silver saber to its position and angle.

Both men took small steps as they walked around in a circle, trying to find out their opponent’s flaws or loopholes.

Both parties were high-killing powerhouses, so one measly loophole that they discover would instantly determine one’s win or loss.

The scorching sun shone unrelentingly on the both of them. Whether it was Jiatai or Yuria, they sweating more and more. Jiatai was sweating so much so that his clothes were thoroughly wet.

As for Yuria, his sunburnt skin was starting to peel off. He could feel a burning sensation when his sweat trickled over the wounds.

On the other hand, Yurijie was standing far away watching the battle. She was totally hung up on Yuria, her eyes wide opened and only blinking it when they were really dry.

“Good boy… Long time no see… So… It’s actually…” Jiatai’s physical exertion was almost breaking the scale. He could not even remember how many years had he not been in such a high-intensity battle. His chest was beating so fast it seemed to be on fire. Turns out, the suit that was pretentiously used as a bragging tool had now become the heaviest burden and it was consuming his energy by the second.

Sweat continued to flow into his eyes along the strands of his hair, but still, he did not dare to wipe them away.

This highly concentrated standoff crushed people’s energy the most.

“You’re the one, last time you had me… Poorly beaten up, you don’t know anything about respecting the elders and loving the younger ones…” Yuria heaved heavily as he glared at the other person.

Suddenly, he saw a loophole and rushed forward.

Whoosh!

His golden saber lit up and almost sliced Jiatai by his side, scaring the latter to near death.

Clang clang clang!!

Three continuous needles darted out, forcing Yuria to react in defense and to not continue his attack.

Their standoff had been going on for some time already.

Once Jiatai used his large-area steel needles to break out, Yuria activated his Hydras and Savior ability, the perfect block of Winds of Four Directions, directly switching both ultimate moves into consumption.

“Well, I say… Can’t you just… Respect an elderly?” Jiatai could no longer hold himself.

With such a never-ending consumption, there was no way he could compare with this young lad. After all, he was already sixty-four years old.

“Why can’t you respect my youthful fifteen-year-old mind then!” Yuria could feel the skin on his back hurting more and more. His head was getting a little dizzy as well, a sign that he was close to falling into a heat stroke coma.

At this moment, Jiatai’s heart ached. If he had known earlier that this would happen, he would not have accepted this mission voluntarily and saved himself from all these embarrassments.

“The person behind… She’s your sister, isn’t she?” He suddenly asked, trying to divert the attention of the other party. “Seems like I’d have to be a little more despicable then…”

Chapter 1189: Plot 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Crack…

Garen’s leather boots sank into the sand as he stood in the distance, staring at Yuria and the Root Doctor Jiatai in the midst of battle. Both of them have already reached the point of exhaustion.

“Now as soon as I join in, the battle will end immediately.”

Garen spoke casually. Sensing there were people behind him, he could tell it was Nine-Tailed Fox and the other’s footsteps.

“Then why don’t you?” Nine-Tailed Fox and a group of her men dressed in black swiftly walked toward Garen’s side and stood still, also staring at the battle that was happening on the beach far away.

“Why should I? From the beginning to the end, Vulture had never shown malice s any of us, no?” Garen asked in return, slowly keeping his saber into its sheath. “I’ve already let the rascal go, I just wanted to probe them.”

“So now they know our capabilities then, right?” Nine-Tailed Fox stood beside him with her arms crossed around her chest, she seemed to agree with his method.

Garen was unsure of her thoughts. Her active participation this time around probably had something to do with other intentions.

He already knew now, even if it was among the transmigrators, nobody had the same talent attributes as him in terms of abilities, so the only thing in each world that could make himself stronger was to grasp the familiar plot and obtain benefits that he needed from it.

Garen did not know what the others want, if it was the same as what he wanted, something related to Soul Seeds or Soul Powers, perhaps the final hostile list would be even longer…

At this moment, it was clear who was the winner and loser of the battle on the beach. After Jiatai continuously threatened Yuria verbally, he decided to retreat.

A submarine emerged from the sea, bringing him away from the beach and disappeared quickly into the waters.

It was only then Garen and the others walked over slowly. Nine-Tailed Fox quickly brought people over to treat the wounded. This was the best opportunity to build relationships. After all, a savior’s friendship would be one of the greatest advantages of the plot.

Garen stood far away as Nine-Tailed Fox brought people over. Li Hua and the other transmigrators were still nowhere to be seen, even Kong Xinxue had disappeared.

“I don’t know why, martial power grades in this world clearly exceeded my expectations, but I still don’t get any sense of crisis at all. What is this?” He fondled his chin, thinking that he must have been too relaxed and slacking too much recently.

*******************

Nine-Tailed Fox looked on as Yuria and his sister were taken away when Li Hua suddenly appeared beside her.

“How was it? What’s the situation?” Li Hua whispered.

“Something is not right,” Nine-Tailed Fox frowned slightly. “The plot is a bit out of control, I feel that something is really wrong!”

“Does it have anything to do with Yuria? Or is it that newbie, Garen?” Li Hua frowned too. She knew Nine-Tailed Fox’s hunch had always been extremely accurate.

“It seems that… No.” Nine-Tailed Fox walked further away to prevent eavesdropping, the sea breeze ruffled up her hair but she was not bothered at all.

“I just feel that something’s wrong and it’s not the way as it is before, yet I can’t tell what exactly.”

“Perhaps it’s a misconception?” Li Hua asked.

“No…” Nine-Tailed Fox shook her head. “Nevermind, I’m not going to think about it anymore. We will take one step at a time for now. All we need to do is stay close to Yuria, the Savior will naturally lead the main line. Right or wrong, there will be clues sooner or later, we just need to be more prepared, that’s all.”

“Yeah.”

********************

Garen, overcome with boredom, tended to Yuria’s injury. Determined that Yuria was just asleep due to over-exhaustion, he too went back to sleep. He was currently in his state of relaxation as he knew that the threats in this world were not exactly a lot. With his Sword Master-Level powers, he was basically invincible on land, not to mention if he used his Soul Ring to rank up his Saber Art realm. Soul Energy nourished his body all the time.

Yuria and his sister, Kong Xinxue, Nine-Tailed Fox, the transmigrators… These people seemed to be evolving along with the plot all the time, whereas he was the only one at leisure.

Ever since the battle at the beach, Yuria seemed to be somewhat triggered and started to train every day to strengthen himself.

On the other hand, Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue got together every day for discussion.

As for Garen, he just did not bother with any of those things. He would go to the restaurant every day and ordered some small dishes, enjoyed the hot springs, do saunas, and occasionally show up for classes to reminiscence the memorable, high school era.

Life was unrestrained.

As for money? There was no need to worry about it. With his capabilities, it was nothing for him to earn a little cash. There was this one night when the National Security Agency came visiting him and they spoke all night long. After that, Garen received money that an average person could never get in a lifetime. It was more than enough for his casuals spendings.

All he had to do was to lend a hand in urgent times. He became the so-called Chief Instructor of some Special Forces Team, or maybe it was some military coach or some other title.

As for what team exactly, he himself had forgotten already. It was enough for him to lead a better life anyway.

Of course, news of the other party’s identity soon came to Nine-Tailed Fox. It turned out to be Vulture’s men. Seemed like Vulture and homeland security have always come hand in hand.

This, however, was confusing for Garen and the others. Why did Vulture’s men kill a large number of maritime police at the sea then? It made no sense.

But Garen was too lazy to think about all these things.

Anyway, his only mission on-hand was to stay behind for garrison duty and just wait for news from Nine-Tailed Fox and the others.

This kind of boring yet comfortable life lasted for more than two months when there was finally new updates.

********************

Lying in the huge bathtub by the French windows, Garen soaked in the milk bath scattered with rose petals. With a towel over his neck, he relaxed lazily with his eyes half shut.

The city night was extraordinarily fascinating. Helicopters occasionally flew across the sky, the city’s traffic and sweeping lights set off against the night background.

“Is there a new situation?” Garen looked at Kong Xinxue idly. She was sitting not far away watching the television. “Otherwise, how would you be so free to drop by my place?”

Kong Xinxue had the remote control in her hands and rolled her eyes at him. After switching channels a few times, she finally muted the television.

“Look at you, which part of you actually look like a student? How long have you not return home? Father almost believed that you’re missing.”

“It doesn’t matter anymore.” Garen shrugged. “We’re all just passersby of this world, too much nostalgia wouldn’t be good for everyone.”

Speechless, Kong Xinxue stood up and walked over.

“The situation has changed. Yuria received news that the Vulture’s strongest man will be showing up soon.”

“So what?” Garen did not move at all.

“What do you think?” Kong Xinxue retorted, “I came all the way here, anxious to tell you this news, why do you think I’m doing this?”

She combed her hair.

“Root Doctor from the previous time, Jiatai, is ranked sixth in Vulture, there are five stronger ones above him. Earlier on when Yuria knew about this, he decided to leave to find his mother, a formal top bounty hunter. Do you want to tag along?”

“What? You are all preparing to go out to sea?” Garen reluctantly opened an eye and glanced at her.

“At least you know that. We don’t have much manpower up for combat. So, are you up for it?” Kong Xinxue was getting impatient.

Garen did not respond immediately, he just turned and leaned into the tub.

“Why don’t you all just go straight into the main subject? Go after Slayer, get rid of him or maybe initiate a good relationship with the opponent and warm up a bit? Why must we only follow Savior?”

Kong Xinxue frowned slightly. “What are you thinking? Why did you ask such a question? Isn’t Savior the plot’s mainline? Why do we follow if not him? Or perhaps you think you are capable of defeating Slayer? Why not you go off alone and take care of him, that would save us a whole lot of trouble. We’ll just do what we’re doing and what we want to do.”

“No, I’m just living my own life. I don’t want anything to do with this kind of hard work. The Four Great Cornerstones cannot be killed, they’ll resurrect after a year, so what’s the point of killing them in the first place?” Garen said in a serious tone. “What I care is, what are your true motives in all this? Perhaps you guys are able to take advantage of the Four Great Cornerstones and obtain some benefits out of them?”

He added with a yawn.

“I just don’t want to waste my efforts.”

Kong Xinxue did not reply immediately but started to ponder. It looked like she was contemplating whether to tell Garen the truth.

Garen was not in a hurry. After all, searching for the Soul Energy Force Field was his secondary objective when he came to this world. He mainly wanted to fix his own state of mind, his rigid mind was incompatible with the art of relaxation. Even if he did not find any clues that directed him to Soul Energy, it did not matter to him. Instead, his interest toward the Lighthouse further increased.

In the fifty-story high-rise hotel, both of them did not speak for some time. One was pondering while the other was waiting.

“You do know the original plot, don’t you?” Kong Xinxue asked suddenly.

“I know a bit but I’m not exactly familiar.” Garen nodded in response.

Kong Xinxue turned around a few times with her hands behind her. She sorted out her mind carefully before speaking once again.

“In the original plot, the main focus was the story of how Vulture helps Savior, supports him and fight against Slayer. Everything revolves around the grievances between the three generations of Slayer and Yuria. The first generation of Slayer was killed by Yuria alone. That was the first generation. After the second generation of Slayer resurrected, he started to seek revenge but he was killed by Yuria and Vulture together. That was the second generation. As for the third generation, Slayer came to life once again and killed Yurijie. By this time, Vulture had fallen apart and there were numerous internal contradictions so they were unable to help Yuria, leaving Yuria alone in the battle. This time, there will be two endings, one is Yuria will be killed along with everyone who is with him, and the other ending would be him perishing together with Slayer.”

Kong Xinxue explained briefly.

“In the entire plot, the constant focus is always the battle between three generations of Slayer and Yuria. The two other Cornerstones would appear somewhere in the middle, Mind Reader and Illusionist. They will also deal with Slayer in different positions.”

“Well then, which generation are we at now?” Garen asked.

“The first generation, which is also the first time Savior and Slayer came into contact. Vulture is just by the side helping Yuria but did not officially join in the battlefield. In this generation, Yuria basically dealt with Slayer alone. This is also the most peaceful generation,” Kong Xinxue lamented. “That’s why we dare to follow Yuria’s whereabouts everywhere. If it’s the second or third generation, the age of bloody chaos, we wouldn’t have dared to do it so obviously.”

“So what is your main intention?” Garen pestered. “If you all had no benefits from this, you wouldn’t have done everything so out in the air already.”

Chapter 1190: Plot 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Of course it’s all for benefits,” Kong Xinxue nodded. “Let me tell you this, many people may know about this secret, but they just choose not to expose it.”

“What secret?” Garen was getting curious as well. “To be able to attract so many transmigrators’ and even the Nine-Tailed Fox’s attention, that shouldn’t be just some ordinary thing.”

Kong Xinxue was not ashamed at all as she sat in the tub, her back facing Garen.

“Four Great Cornerstones are known as they are all due to one main thing which is the Sacred Sigil.”

“Sacred Sigil?”

“That’s right.” Kong Xinxue nodded. “The reason the Four Great Cornerstones can outstand other people plainly is because the four of them possess extraordinary powers and this is where the Sacred Sigil works its magic.”

“So you guys want to obtain the Sacred Sigil?” Garen asked out of curiosity, “If it’s that easy to claim it, can you guys can get it?”

“Obviously it’s not easy to get it,” Kong Xinxue rolled her eyes at him, “but there are many parallel worlds out there and some of the older generations of some worlds have been researching for a long period of time and they’ve concluded that a certain amount of energy can be drawn out from the Sacred Sigil by undergoing some special transplant, not seizing, but just absorbing a little. This is actually pretty impressive already. Once one gets a hold of this and leaves this world, they are free to use the powers of the Sacred Sigil. Although it won’t be as phenomenal as it originally was, it won’t be subjected to the world’s regulations and restrictions. This is the advantage of receiving powers of a low martial arts world. It’s the same as how you get powers from the Mother Stream System which is applicable for most worlds’ regulations.”

Garen nodded as a sign of understanding.

“Then what’s the main purpose of the Sacred Sigil’s powers?”

“There are four kinds corresponding to the Four Great Cornerstones.” Kong Xinxue simply broke everything into detail. “First on the list would be Slayer’s Sacred Sigil, then Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil, Illusionist’s Sacred Sigil, and last of all, Savior’s Sacred Sigil. A Sacred Sigil would allow us to possess a portion of the Four Great Cornerstones’ powers, but just a weaker version of it. The good thing is that it’s usable in any world out there, the bad thing is that it’s not much of a use in an upper martial arts world.”

“That’s why some people want it, some people are not bothered by it. Just like those of Sea God Grades, why would they care?” Garen seemed to understand.

“That’s right.”

“I guess I understand the basics of it.” Garen touched his chin. “For us transmigrators, the Slayer’s and Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil would be our top picks, followed by the Illusionist’s and Savior’s. The Savior’s Sacred Sigil has very rigid restrictions, that’s why it is not as popular as the others.”

“Yeah.” Kong Xinxue returned a smile. “It’s great that you understand. I want the Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil, Nine-Tailed Fox wants the Slayer’s, I guess everyone wants different things. Due to the fact that this is a weakened version, there’s plenty of copies out there. One Sacred Sigil is sufficient to be given to ten or more people, but the conditions to acquire those are extremely tough, which is why everyone is working so hard.”

“Yeah, everyone’s putting in a lot of effort.” Garen nodded in agreement. “If that’s the case, that thing won’t be much big of a use for me then…What time am I able to go to the Lighthouse Headquarter? Compared to this, I’m more interested in going there.”

“They’re still under lockdown, you will have to wait for this plot to end and for the powers of the Sacred Sigils to slowly die down in order to prevent the activation transmission of rules in the world. I’d say you won’t be able to go over any time soon,” Kong Xinxue explained. “You’d have to at least wait for the first generation to end.”

“How long would that be?”

“Probably a few years time.”

“That’s long…”

Garen was speechless Ever since he found out the existence of the Lighthouse, he had always been eager to check it out. He would not have to just walk his own wild path or swim in Mother Stream anymore, a more convenient way was always better.

“Alright then… I’ll just wait for a couple more years.”

After Kong Xinxue left, Garen started to think about the possible situations that might occur. A few years time was not exactly a long period of time in his opinion, it would pass like a breeze as it was back in the Mech World. There were plenty of ways to pass time too, but it was what Kong Xinxue revealed about the powers of the Sacred Sigils that caught his attention.

If he guessed it right, the Sacred Sigil’s powers could be a variant of Soul Energy. Since the Four Great Cornerstones were able to use such a vast amount of Soul Energy, why was he not allowed to do so?

With that thought, inspiration started seeping into his head. He started researching everything that was related to the usage of Soul Energy.

After staying at a high-class hotel in Slann for a long period of time, the occasional trip back home to see Kong Yuan was something arranged by the government, even reporting to the university in advance. Sometimes, the security department would contact him and assign him to difficult tasks. Though they were not much, Garen would always complete the tasks successfully.

Unconsciously, a year had passed.

Garen had also gained a certain reputation in the international market, living up to a success rate of 80%, which was an impressive score in a high martial powered country like Slann. As for the in-between tasks that were unsuccessful, they were basically troublesome things like searching for wanted people, which Garen simply gave up on.

In the National Security department, the nickname given to him was Sword Master.

While he was enjoying his leisure life, Yuria was already holding meetings with Vulture’s high graded powerhouses. The forth powerhouse had been defeated by Yuria, the third one resigned voluntarily, while the second one tied with Yuria. The situation only subsided one night after a year’s time when the first ranked powerhouse trashed him completely.

Within the year’s time, Yuria traveled around in hopes of finding his mother, Light Path. He brought his sister along as they wandered around the world. Naturally, the experiences he gained had surpassed many adults that were older than him. In the beginning, he would occasionally return to the hotel and ask for Garen’s help regarding problems with his Saber Art. However, later on, he only dropped by for the occasional visits, a form of etiquette as a disciple toward his master. As for Saber Art pointers, there was not much that Garen could teach anymore due to the rules of this world. Techniques of higher levels were not usable and all the techniques available were already taught.

Easier said, Yuria had already finished his apprenticeship.

Yuria was now just slightly weaker than Garen. Other than Garen’s power card of raising his realm grades, if they were to fight against each other, the ratio would be a four to six.

Due to problems with expenses, Yuria would accept some of Garen’s government missions. In fact, those tasks were assigned to Garen but he outsourced them to his disciple and the reward money would be split into half.

If not for Yuria’s unwillingness to join the government, he would not have to make this choice in the first place.

*********************

Thud.

The teacup was placed gently on the glass table.

Yuria slowly exhaled a breath of hot air, the scent of tea calming his nerves. Raising his head, he looked at Garen sitting in front of him.

“Minister, how many unrestricted combat people did you recruit? Why are the people contacted this time around all our old friends?” He frowned and asked.

“There’s no other way, welfare is pretty good,” Garen answered lazily. “Unrestricted combat has now basically separated from school and has set up its own organization. The small fraction of people who stayed voluntarily will occasionally pick up the subcontracting tasks that I have outsourced. The pay is good, the risk is low, so naturally, everyone is willing to do. What’s not good about it?”

“Although you’d take care of problems personally, that isn’t a big problem. However, do you really not care about these things?” Yuria rolled his eyes. “You’re basically using the public funds to raise your own private soldiers.”

“Private soldiers your ass.” Garen could not control his laughter as he scolded Yuria. “Look at that bunch. The moment something happens, the ones who will back out and run away will definitely be them!”

“Alright then… I’m used to it anyway.” Yuria leaned on the sofa, shifting into a more comfortable position. He was dressed in a white windbreaker and long fitted jeans. His beard had not been shaved for a long time, making him look unnaturally mature. He did not look like a sixteen or seventeen-year-old. A year of running around in search of his mother had brought him experience and maturity.

“So tell me, why are you here? I know you wouldn’t look for me unless you wanted something,” Garen held his teacup, sitting lazily in his white pajamas.

“Heh… I knew I couldn’t hide it from you,” Yuria smiled begrudgingly. It was a little disgusting coming from a grown-up looking man doing that expression…

“Hurry up, stop dilly-dallying,” Garen was slightly irritated.

Yuria’s expression became dead serious.

“So here it goes, although I couldn’t find my mother this time around, I sort of have this feeling that she’s avoiding me somehow.”

“Avoiding you? Why?”

“I don’t know.” Yuria’s brows tightened in a know. “That’s what I’m frustrated about, what more…”

“What more what?” Garen took a sip of his tea.

“This time out on my trip, I met a weird guy. He seems to know me and he came over to me all secretive telling me that my target had died and asking me not to waste my efforts and hurry back to converge,” Yuria spoke with a bewildered expression.

“Converge?” Garen was confused as well. “He said your target is already dead? Does he mean…”

“No… Not that meaning,” Yuria shook his head, “he seems to think that I belong to some organization or something. Converge. Who do I converge with? He didn’t say anything about all this. He disappeared right after I turned around. It’s just all very strange.”

“And after that when I was on my way back, I inadvertently received a small note which warned me that I’m in danger. It also had instructions on it asking me to burn it right away and not let anyone else other than me see it,” Yuria just could not figure it out.

“So you burnt it then?”

“Burnt it? I didn’t tell anyone about this, only you right now. I suspect that I’m somehow dragged into something.”

Garen sorted out all the information he just heard. Yuria’s situation was not mentioned at all in the plot, whereas Nine-Tailed Fox and the others were still in other countries trying to pave the way for Yuria. The news was not unusual. The only odd thing was that Slayer and the others who were supposed to appear by now were still nowhere to be seen. According to the plot, they should have appeared long ago, but there was still currently zero news of them.

“Well done, don’t tell anyone about this, your sister included. This matter won’t be much of use other than worry everyone else, everything will be clearer when there are more clues.” Garen explained, “I’ll pull some strings and try to find out whatever I can for you and see what kind of people are trying to get into contact with you or to influence you or whatever…”

Chapter 1191: Combat 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Alright, I’ll be waiting for your news then, Master,” Yuria smiled.

Garen was speechless. The fellow had been getting too sleek in the past year. Compared to the simple-minded teenager he used to be, he was now no different than a normal uncle.

“Well, if there’s nothing else, you should go back now. Don’t stay here for too long.”

“Got it, Master.”

He stared as Yuria left with a giddy smile on his face, Garen then closed the door and returned to his sofa.

“Nine-Tails and the others went to some other continent to investigate the situation with Slayer. I wonder how are they doing now. Yuria over here just met some weirdo, and it’s a weirdo not mentioned in the original plot,” Garen touched his chin. “Why does this feel like a gaming world? The first generation of Slayer, second generation, third generation? It’s a bit interesting.”

“Forget about it, these things are too much trouble to manage. I should just continue living my ordinary life, and take good care of my body and mind…”

He was too lazy to bother about all these messy things. After all, his main purpose in this world was to just enjoy anything interesting. This kind of serious investigation tasks were not suited for him. He would rather stay at home and watch movies or television shows, play some games, or go out and stroll. Those leisure activities were so much better.

He lifted his wrist and checked the time, it was a quarter past eight nighttime.

“I’ll go for a walk around and get some food back for dinner,” Garen remembered that the snacks in his hotel room were almost finished, so he had to go to the supermarket to replenish his stock.

Grabbing his jacket, he headed out.

Walking out of his room, he turned around and closed the door. He then walked along the carpet until he reached the elevator.

The elevator was empty and nobody could be seen.

“Everyone should be resting or getting ready for bed at this hour,” Garen mumbled as he pressed the elevator button.

Ding.

Among the four other elevators, one just happened to stop at this floor. The door slowly opened.

Garen walked in quickly and stood in the middle. There was a stylish office lady in the elevator as well. White blonde hair drooped over her frame like a waterfall, white skin as delicate as porcelain, tall and slender, and she was wearing a black professional skirt with nude stockings matched with a small black bag in her hands.

Seeing that Garen entered, his over-bulky physique made her feel oppressive. His burly figure occupied a large part of the elevator.

The lady reluctantly inched closer to the wall with a helpless expression.

Garen drew out his room card and brushed it on the elevator panel, he then pressed the third-floor button. There was a huge supermarket chain there. To his surprise, his room card seemed to be not working and it was still no good even after he pressed the button multiple times.

“Which floor are you going?” The lady could not stand it anymore, she was flustered by Garen’s arm that kept flinging in front of her.

“Third floor, thank you,” Garen smiled embarrassedly.

“No problem.” The lady took out her own room card and brushed it, then pressed the third-floor button.

After brushing the card, the lady took out her phone and dialed a number. After a short wait, the call was connected. She then began to speak in another language.

Garen could not understand anything as he stood by her side.

Besides the main line of the Four Great Cornerstones of this world, ordinary people in other parts of the world still led their ordinary life. The knowledge of the Four Great Cornerstones was only limited to a small area of people, the rest of the places only consisted of plain ordinary lives. This was the reason he could slack.

Ding…

From the forth-something floor to the ninth floor, the elevator stopped again. The doors opened and a handsome young man dressed in a suit and leather shoes walked in.

When he caught sight of Garen in his white pajamas, he was shocked for a bit, but he returned quickly. To be able to stay at this hotel, one would not be just a typical customer. However, to dare to walk out of one’s room dressed like that, one was surely not just an ordinary person.

He flashed a friendly smile toward Garen.

Garen ignored him entirely. Ever since he joined the security department, so many people wanted to get closer to him that they could probably form a line all the way to the ocean.

Soon enough, he reached the third floor. Garen walked into the empty supermarket. The things sold here were not generally cheap, so naturally, not many people came to shop here.

After quickly picking a few boxes of snacks that he liked, Garen checked out and returned to the elevator with his arms full of snacks. The supermarket staff helped to press the elevator button for him.

He then waited quietly for the elevator.

Ding…

The elevator doors opened.

The lady was still inside. At the sight of Garen once again, she was obviously surprised for a bit. She, too, flashed a friendly smile toward him.

Garen thought that a foolish smile would lose his Sword Master style, so he ignored her. Although she was indeed beautiful, she was still not his cup of tea. Hugging his boxes of snacks, he walked in and once again, occupied most of the space in the elevator.

The lady seemed to be slightly embarrassed as she had her head bent low, both hands clutching onto her handbag.

The elevator soon reached the forty-something floor which was the floor Garen was staying at.

Holding onto his things, Garen walked out and swiftly headed to his own room. Garen straight away divided the snacks into different categories and poured himself a glass of strawberry wine. He added some milk, a few ice cubes, sprinkled some pepper, and lastly, a few slices of sausages to give it a flavor. He then took a sip.

“Wow… Nice!”

He plopped onto the couch and turned on his projection television.

Suddenly, he remembered he seem to have forgotten something. He had something to eat, but he was short of something to drink, a mere wine was clearly not enough. He went to his cabinet and had a look, the milk was almost finished. Garen started to contemplate whether to get more milk.

Once again, he took his room card and headed out. He stopped before the elevator and pressed the button once more.

It did not take long before the elevator doors opened.

The girl with long white blonde hair was still inside. The both of them stared at each other for a moment across the elevator.

Wacko.

Garen carefully sized the girl. Was she addicted to taking the elevator?

The lady looked embarrassed as an awkward smile crept onto her face, her fingers tightened their grip around her handbag strap.

“Excuse me…” She started. “Does Mr. Byron Corey stay here?”

“Byron Corey?” Garen did not seem to understand what was she saying. “Who is that? I don’t know him.” He continued measuring her with his eyes. “Are you sick? Delusional?”

“Hmm?” The lady could not react on time as it seemed that Garen was speaking too fast and she was straining to catch up on his words. “What are… Talking about?”

“I said, are you sick?” Garen repeated his question.

The lady still had a blank expression. “Sorry, my foreign language isn’t very good, what are you asking?”

“I said, you’re sick.” Garen was already almost speechless.

“You said, I’m pretty?” The lady pointed at herself as she blurt out word by word.

“Yes, you’re sick, very sick…” Garen had his arms around himself as he looked more and more helpless by the moment.

“Thank you for your kind words.” The lady showed a shy yet grateful smile. “Actually, my makeup wasn’t done very nicely.”

“I didn’t say that your makeup is nice…” Garen could feel a little pain in his balls.

“Then what do you mean?” Apparently pretty and sick sounded similar in Slann language, hence why the lady was confused once again.

“You’re not even good with language, why are you here all alone? Aren’t you tired?” Garen did not want to waste any more time talking nonsense to her.

“Yes, I’m very tired.” This time around, she finally understood what he meant and nodded her head eagerly.

“Go back to your country if you’re tired. This is Mars, it’s not suitable for humans from Earth to stray around,” Garen simply responded. Just then, the elevator doors opened as it stopped at the third floor, and so he walked out.

The lady still had a dazed look on her face, she did not even understand what was Earth.

Staring at the back of Garen’s figure, she smiled as she repeated the two terms ‘Earth’ and ‘Mars’ multiple times in a hushed tone.

“I think he was probably complimenting me…” She too was unsure herself.

**********************

Garen was resting at the hotel, alone and bored.

On the other hand, Nine-Tailed Fox had sent over the news on some new developments over on her side. They had initially found out the whereabouts of Slayer but they dared not rush into contact, so they continued observing from afar.

As for the strange man Garen had asked the security department to investigate on, there was still no news.

He gave the feedback to Yuria. Garen was actually slightly interested in Slayer, though it had nothing to do with whatsoever Sacred Sigil, but how strong was Slayer who was also known as the pinnacle of the world.

Therefore, with such curiosity, Garen left the hotel and started his journey. After learning about the location of Slayer that was sent out by Nine-Tailed Fox and the others, he quietly left the agreed guarding point alone and went straight in the direction of the Slayer.

********************

As far as the eye could see, a giant cruise ship was slowly headed into the sea’s horizon. Sunlight, seagulls, waves, plus the lapping wave sounds and the frequent dolphins leaping side to side.

Everything painted a beautiful picture altogether.

“Where’s Slayer?” Leaning on the ship’s rail, Garen asked quietly as he stared at the leaping dolphins.

“Should be somewhere here.” An intelligent female officer from the security department who was dressed as a wealthy lady was standing beside Garen, sipping the light green glass of wine in her hand.

“Are Nine-Tailed Fox and the others nearby?”

“Yes.”

“Order your people not to stray too far away from here. If they’re really at the bottom of the sea, they have to be ready to aid me at all times,” Garen instructed.

“Understood, Sir. Are you not going to wait for the assisting manpower?” The wealthy lady asked softly.

“No need.” Garen shook his head.

“Nine-Tailed Fox and the others are still not close enough to Slayer as of now, they’re afraid of being discovered by the other party so they chose an island further away. There is only a half an hour gap of monitoring in between, and this is the time when Slayer will be more alert. This is the time when I go over.”

Garen did not intend to let the others witness his battle against Slayer, turning the fight into a combat show. It just happened that Slayer dived into the water and was currently somewhere near the seafloor. He seemed to be searching for something, so Garen still had some time to attempt to get near him.

“Get the wetsuit ready.”

“Already ready.”

Garen held onto the handrail as he turned around and walked toward a secret door in the cabin.

The door slowly opened and a gorgeous lady dressed in a black suit by the door bowed. She also had two black sabers by her side.

*******************

At the bottom of the sea, everything was pitch black in the trench.

A black figure was swimming around, moving about in the water. Behind it were dozens of groups of people dressed in silver diving suits.

This group of people continued to swim along the trench as their flashlights shone, constantly illuminating the surroundings.

Oh!!

A massive great white shark swam from a distance, but before it got close, a long black spear pike pierced through its eye. A long black chain necklace was attached to the entire spear pike and the chain was held by the black figure.

“Clear.”

The hoarse voice of the black figure rang in the small region of the sea.

All the silver figures quickly swam in all directions, dispersing immediately. They started clearing any other threatening creatures nearby. As for the great white shark, strangely enough, there was not a trace of blood. It just started sinking slowly as if there was something heavy added into its body.

Slowly, the eyes of the black figure lit up like rubies, a glowing bright red.

He slowly raised his head as if he sensed something, and looked up.

Chapter 1192: Combat 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Who do you think will win?”

On another ship, a tall man wearing a white military uniform softly asked. Beside him stood an old lady with white hair. She was holding a walking stick and her expression was very serious.

“I don’t know… Sword Master’s potential was something we have never completely seen. He usually acts arrogantly and there has not been an opponent that he has had trouble with before. However, Slayer is the strongest individual existence that has been around since ancient times. I’m predicting that Slayer would win by a bit,” the old granny answered.

“Sword Master is the number one Kendo genius in my country, Slann. There probably will not be anyone able to surpass him within the past and the next ten centuries. Especially since he could reach such a level at his age.” The man in the white military uniform shook his head. “I feel that Sword Master is more likely to win. This time around, all the higher-ups from Vulture had also come. Regarding Sword Masters casual decision to initiate a duel, it seemed to have caught the attention of a lot of people.”

“Both of our number ones and number twos have already personally taken action. Although we have no contact, the experts from the other two countries will also surely monitor this duel in secret,” the old granny calmly stated. “If Sword Master wins, our country Slann would become the strongest existence within the Three Great Nations. This is a matter of national security, so of course, they will be paying attention.”

There were also a group of people in white military uniforms standing behind the two, filled by men and women of all ages. All of them looked very serious. These people were the elites sent in by the National Security Bureau. It was the best team they could prepare with such short notice, all in case Sword Master gets defeated. They would be able to provide aid and bring him away as fast as possible.

“Then who do you want to win?” The man in the military uniform asked once more.

This time, the old granny did not answer immediately, she just narrowed her eyes.

******

At another location of the sea, a few black submarines were slowly moving towards Slayer’s location, almost as if a school of black sharks.

“The number one genius of Slann, Sword Master Garen and Slayer’s duel. This is going to be interesting. However, no matter how strong they are, they will never compare to Lord Battle Flag from our Black Federation,” a male in a black military uniform laced with gold said cheerfully.

“Lord Military Flag is also surely watching this duel in secret,” the female officer next to him replied.

“That’s natural. Lord Military Flag is the one behind this entire plan. Other than Lord Battle Flag, all of the tactical level powers are all under his control as he has the highest commanding authority right now.” The officer laughed coldly. “We’ll leave everything to Lord Battle Flag when both parties are both critically injured. Heh.”

“The only thing we don’t know now is where the Red Nation people are. Those cowardly and fake bastards are useless other than for annoying others with talks of their god. If only they could be destroyed along with those two,” the female officer coldly said.

******

Garen slowly changed into a white charming diving suit. There was a huge crescent moon drawn on his back, looking as arrogant as ever. This was Slann’s strongest and most high-tech micro-type defensive gear. There were not more than four of these suits available in the entire nation, and one of them was currently used for Garen’s battle against Slayer.

After changing, Garen wielded two black sabers and headed to the side of the ship. Two female special agents handed him an oxygen tank and a gas mask.

“We wish you success.”

“Of course,” Garen smiled. Putting on his mask, he leaped into the sea.

Splash!

Leaving a white splash on the sea’s surface, he disappeared out of sight.

Seawater continuously flowed pass Garen’s ear, air bubbles slowly rising up. A patch of dark blue was all he could see.

As time went on, he dived deeper and deeper. He slowly turned on the weight loader on his body, increasing his weight.

Looking down below, he saw a black figure standing on the sandy floor at the bottom of the ocean a distance away.

That person’s eyes were emitting an ominous red light, looking like two drops of fresh blood.

The two were dozens of meters apart but they could clearly see each.

“Are you Slayer?” Garen directly asked him.

“What are you trying to say?” Slayer’s voice was very unique. It was very coarse, almost like an old man with a hoarse voice. “You’re blocking my advance, looks like another one who came to challenge me to their death.”

The tone of his voice displayed his absolute confidence. This was the absolute confidence of someone who had murdered a lot of self-proclaimed experts.

Garen did not say anything. He was honestly quite curious about this person who was one of the Four Great Cornerstones. His visit this time around was to test the waters and verify how strong Slayer truly was.

Woosh!

Suddenly, a black line shot towards his waist from the side.

Dink!

Garen’s saber hilt blocked the black line, causing it to ricochet.

“You’re an impatient one,” Garen lightly laughed, once again looking at the Slayer’s position. He was gone.

Rapidly turning to his right, a pair of glowing red eyes was crashing towards him.

Bam!!

The two collided with each other. Almost as if two balls of glue intertwining together, they started rolling off, shooting towards the distance.

The black gun and dual sabers intensely vibrated from the collision, hitting each other dozens of times in that small area within that instant. The black gun’s speed was obviously faster than the dual sabers. This gave Garen a shock.

“What fast speed! Even my speed is already near the human’s limit, my physical attributes have already reached the terrifying level of a five-point average, comparable to that of a beast. To think his power and speed could even match and exceed mine!”

“Four Directional Winds!”

With a clank, four rays of silver light started flashing and flying out in all directions from Garen’s body.

Slayer shook his hand and the black gun suddenly formed dozens of gun clones. It’s immense strength and speed caused whirlpools to appear in the water. These whirlpools attacked Garen like a snake, almost as if more opponents had appeared and Garen needed to simultaneously attack them.

Ching ching ching ching!

With four clashes, the Four Directional Winds had successfully blocked off the black gun whirlpool snake.

“Crouching Tiger Light!”

Slayer coldly shouted, his entire body started furiously spinning, whipping around large amounts of seawater. Under the tremendous amount of seawater pressure, it started to emit a whistling sound from the water flow.

Roar!!

That felt almost like a tiger’s roar. The water flow gathered together forming a huge transparent tiger, crashing down towards Garen.

“Thunder Shock!”

The black gun did not stop for even a moment, once again shooting out a triangle.

With a buzz, the seawater in the area started violently vibrating, its temperature rapidly rising. He seemed to use some sort of power to make all the seawater in a ten-meter radius rapidly boil. Ignoring his other attack flying towards Garen from all directions, he created a second wave of attacks.

“Scorpio’s Gun!!”

With his last attack, the black gun in Slayer’s hand looked like an enraged black dragon, ferociously lunging towards Garen. Along with the bright red light glowing in Slayer’s eyes, the black gun’s barrel shot out like a burst of lightning, it’s power increasing more than three times the original.

Within that short second, Slayer managed to unleash three strong abilities, creating one overwhelmingly terrifying attack.

Garen finally understood what was a slayer, and also why he was given the nickname Slayer.

At this moment, he was at the center of all of these finishing moves. He felt that he was not battling a single person, but rather an entire army! Within the time he could unleash one move, his opponent managed to unleash three. He could even feel that within each of Slayer’s move it had more than a couple of different types of abilities being activated at the same time.

Among the incoming undercurrent attacks, some were fake and some were real, some were strong and some were weak. They had different intensities and even different orientations. Due to the variation in this attack, any normal person would find it completely impossible to react in time.

Every one of these undercurrents had various types of changes and follow-ups hidden within them.

“This is a completely different level…” He looked a bit helpless. “Looks like I can’t afford to hold back…”

An idea suddenly flashed in his mind. Garen instantly wielded his dual sabers tightly in a reverse grip, holding them out in front of his chest.

Forcefully, he slashed outwards with the sabers.

Splitting Sea!

Whoosh!!

The sabers flashed, the entire seawater was somehow split into two. Garen was stood in the middle with his two sides being two seawater walls that were more than ten meters high. He stood at the center, holding on to his sabers as he started running, looking like a God of the sea, arrogant. This formed a white line that shot towards Slayer below.

The seawater was instantly slashed into a vacuum, destroying all the earlier attacks. The black gun was moving up from below, whilst Garen was moving down from above.

The two seemed to have given up on their fancy tricks and decided to have a head-on clash.

Boom!

The vacuum under the seawater was only maintained for a short instance before immediately collapsing.

Twonk!!!

A huge sound wave rippled from in between the black gun and the dual sabers, causing the sand floor at the bottom of the sea that the two were standing on to instantly crumble away. A clear ring of the ripple with the two as a center point started spreading out.

This caused the coral, mud and rocks to completely be shocked into pieces. Even the crabs and prawns in the area directly died from the shock.

Slayer coldy sighed, releasing the gun barrel from his grip. With a whip of the chain at the end, he threw it at Garen like an actual whip. His gun technique immediately transforming into a whipping technique.

However, at this time, a red bloodstain had appeared on his chest, blood dissipating out from his chest into the seawater.

Garen rapidly stepped back, dodging the whip and started to create distance between them as he looked at Slayer.

“Sorry, it seems like my power is slightly stronger.” He wielded his dual sabers in a reverse grip behind his back.

“Is that so?” Slayer touched the wound on his chest. Understandably, although his abilities and moves were complicated, varied and abnormally strong, his physical fitness was still a level lower than his opponent. Although the difference was not huge, it was still something that he could not believe. His strength was obviously weaker than his opponent, that’s why he sustained this light injury during the battle.

However, even if Garen was strong, Garen’s speed was still no match for him.

“Interesting.” The red lights in Slayers eyes faded away. “Originally I only planned to play around a bit…”

He reached his hand out and threw his gun forward.

Click.

The gun somehow broke into dozens of pieces and started floating around him.

“My muscles can simultaneously muster up energy for fifty-three moves,” Slayer slowly explained. “In other words, I can activate a move similar to the attack just now a total of fifty-three times within an instant.”

He slowly grabbed two of the gun pieces. With a wave of his hand, the water started rippling from the dozens of guns moving together, almost as if there were dozens of attackers, each holding a gun. This looked extremely weird.

“What gave you enough confidence to come and challenge me?”

“…” Garen’s face turned pale.

Fifty-three times simultaneously… If what his opponent said was true, then…

Chapter 1193: Surprise Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Before he even realized it, Garen suddenly stepped back. A black line flashed through where he was originally standing.

It was a surprise attack that came in the form of a silenced gunshot.

Garen’s narrowed his eyes even more.

“Again!”

He sharply leaped forward.

“Wind Ahead.”

With a whooshing sound, a bright light shot out from the saber forming a white pillar crashing into the opponent. This saber was actually two sabers combined as one. Hence, its strength was twice as strong as the one in front of him.

Slayer had also started to take this a bit more seriously.

The dozens of guns floating around him all started to vibrate, gathering together to form one gigantic black metal shield.

Bam!

With a loud thud, the gun shield and the dual sabers crashed against each other.

Garen twisted his body, rapidly moving away like a swimming fish.

As a result, the two Undercurrent Attacks that Slayer used at the same instantly missed their target, leaving him frowning in his position as he looked at Garen’s silhouette leaving the place.

“What is this supposed to be? Some test?”

He had already caught wind of Garen’s challenge earlier on, so he had been waiting for him here. However, since his opponent had already retreated before they reached a resolution, this was obviously just a test and Garen had no intention to fight till the end.

Both parties knew that they both still had their strongest cards concealed up their sleeves. Thus, if the fight would have continued on, there would be no way of predetermining a clear winner.

“Sir?” A sliver diver swam over. “Do we pursue him?”

“No need, there are too many pieces of trash surveilling the area,” Slayer raised his hand. “We didn’t find what we were looking for, so let’s just retreat for now.”

“Understood.”

After his subordinates left the scene, the red light in Slayer’s eyes started to light up once more. He turned around and glared at the black submarines slowly closing in underwater, his face revealed a slight mocking expression.

******

Garen climbed up onto the ship, helped up by two special service personnel onto the deck. Water naturally dripping off the surface of his completely drenched diving suit.

“Your Excellency, you’re hurt!” One of the special service personnel said, covering her mouth in shock. She saw that Garen had a huge bloodstain on his back.

“I’m fine.” Garen pulled off his headgear, swiftly shaking off the water in his hair. “Start making the preparations to go back, we are leaving as soon as possible. This small wound isn’t a big deal.”

“Al… Alright.” The female personnel saw that Garen’s wound had already started to visibly heal. She was so shocked that her eyeballs were about to pop out. After stutteringly answering Garen, she swiftly ran off.

Garen started thinking back to the battle he had with Slayer just now.

“How interesting.” A smile appeared at the corners of his mouth.

Originally, he planned to just take it easy as he thought that there would not be anything that could threaten him in this world. However, he never would have imagined that there would be someone like the unknown and mysterious Sea God and that Slayer’s potential would exceed his expectations by so much.

“Should I just kill Slayer?” Garen thought to himself as he rubbed his chin. He had basically already grasped the foundation of his opponent’s potential. Furthermore, he had yet to display his true powers as well. He could still use his Soul Energy Acceleration to forcibly increase his potential by another level. Once he used his full power, he could reach the levels of unnatural powers, having his potential countless times stronger than it was currently. It was definitely enough to annihilate Slayer in an instant.

“However, it seems like that guy still has some sort of trump card. The threshold of unnatural powers in this world was too high so it would still not make much of a difference. How troublesome.”

Back in the Mech World, Garen was at the level where he could annihilate an entire planet with an arm tied behind his back. He was a true Demon King Level and if not for the world’s overly complicated rules, he might have already destroyed this planet out of impatience. After all, for a Demon King Level Soul Ring, just the Soul Energy itself would be strong enough to condense into a physical form. His potential growth rate could even be considered the most overpowered amongst the most overpowered. In addition to that, as his Soul Power increases, the speed of growth would also increase, and so would the intensity.

Although he was still being suppressed by this world’s rules, Garen’s average physical fitness had still reached the terrifying degree of an average five points.

The Mother Stream System’s most terrifying part was demonstrated here.

They had extremely high adaptability no matter which world they were in. As shown in this situation, it could almost flawlessly fit into the new universe’s rules and find the strength at the strongest level. Then, using that scale as a basis, it uses soul rings to forcibly increase levels, achieving even more.

That was the strongest part about the Mother Stream System.

Garen finally fully understood what it meant.

After changing his clothes, he went into one of the restaurants in the cabins to rest. In the cabin, food and beverages had already been prepared for him. The entire cruise ship started turning back because of special ‘malfunctions’. Originally, this cruise ship was specifically allocated to Garen.

“You went to challenge Slayer?” A voice rang from the restaurant’s entrance area.

Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua walked into the restaurant, glaring daggers straight at Garen.

“Didn’t I tell you to keep watch back at the base and protect everyone? Do you know how much danger and risk your absence could have caused everyone!?” Nine-Tailed Fox walked up to Garen, angrily slamming the table.

“Nothing happened anyways, right?” Garen lazily replied.

“What if Slayer decided not to accept your challenge and went directly to our comrades back at the base? Who would take responsibility if something happened?!” Nine-Tailed Fox looked extremely angry. “Ah Xue and the gang were all still back at the base. If something happened to them, can you even take the responsibility for it!?”

“No worries, it’s fine. Didn’t I already allocate people to protect them before I left?” Garen spoke carefreely. “Slayer’s target isn’t us, his attention won’t be focussed on us at all.”

He casually picked up a piece of cake, putting it into his mouth.

“You still dare to continue eating!?”

With a slap, Nine-Tailed Fox smacked the piece of cake Garen was holding onto the floor.

Her chest intensely puffing in and out, making it seem like it was not just the average anger.

“No organization! No discipline! Can’t even take care of such a trivial task! Why are we still keeping someone like you!? What are you even good for other than wasting our resources!?”

“Hey… Calm down.” Li Hua pulled lightly on her sleeve, but Nine-Tailed Fox jerked her arm away immediately. “Stay out of this!”

Garen looked over at the cake on the floor. He seemed unperturbed by it as he picked up another piece.

“I’m wasting your resources?”

He felt that Nine-Tailed Fox was venting out his frustrations as if he had encountered some stressful situation. This was just a channel for him to vent.

“The cruise ship you are currently sitting in, the food you are currently eating, the utensils you are currently using, are all these not a waste of our resources!?” Nine-Tailed Fox coldly laughed.

“This looks more like the National Security Agency’s power though,” Garen slowly replied.

“Why do you think they value you so much? If it wasn’t for us helping you behind the scenes, why would they bother with a side character like you who is still in their teens? At the end of the day, most of the resources you used belong to everyone!”

“Enough, enough, stop arguing!” Li Hua could no longer help herself, she had to hold her back.

“You guys helping me behind the scenes?” Garen laughed. “Looks like you really don’t understand the actual situation here…” He picked up an apple and moved it to his nose to get a whiff.

“Do you want to… Have a bout?”

The restaurant’s air suddenly turned icy cold, as if it regressed from the warmth of spring back to the cold of winter.

An icy cold killing intent emitted out of Garen’s body, permeating to every corner of the restaurant.

Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua could not help but shiver due to the cold. They suddenly remembered this was the man that just retreated in one piece after challenging Slayer.

He was now sitting here, no injury in sight. He was even able to give off such an intense killing intent.

A chill was sent down Nine-Tailed Fox’s spine. The fervor and rage from what happened earlier were instantly cooled down, almost as if someone had poured a bucket of ice water over her head.

She took a deep breath, holding up her arm to have a good look. Her skin was completely covered in dense goosebumps. This amount of goosebumps was something that would only appear when she was facing an extremely dangerous threat.

Streams of cold air gushed into her brain, reminding her that the man seated in front of her was an immense threat to her.

She looked over at Li Hua, this comrade of hers, who had a similarly terrifying strength, currently had her pupils contracted. Although she still remained in the same stance, her entire body had tensed up, as if she was ready to make her move any moment.

At this moment, Nine-Tailed Fox suddenly remembered. Ever since they first met, Garen had never ever revealed his actual trump card.

“Have you calmed down a bit?” Garen raised his wine glass and had a sip of red wine, lightly tossing the apple over.

“…” Nine-Tailed Fox had no idea what tone to answer with as all her intense emotions earlier had been instantly cooled down by this sudden surge of cold air.

“Let’s just talk it out.” Li Hua was advising at the side. “We’re all comrades here.” She motioned for the other staff to leave the area, leaving the three of them alone in the restaurant.

Dragging Nine-Tailed Fox over and seating her down, she sat right across Garen.

“Ah Xue went missing.”

“…”

Garen’s immediate reaction to the news was shock, but he instantly calmed down.

“I was still talking to her on the phone yesterday…”

“She just went missing yesterday night,” Li Hua interrupted him.

“Sorry, that was why Wenzhen was so agitated earlier.” Li Hua closed her eyes and recounted her memories. “Wenzhen and I spent the entire night looking for her. In the midst of our search, we heard that you challenged Slayer. That was why she lost her temper just now. I hope you can understand.”

Garen did not reply her. Instead, he pulled out his phone and called Kong Xinxue directly.

The phone rang over and over. After four times, eight times, and even over ten times, no one picked up the call.

Seeing that no one was picking up, Garen’s face suddenly turned pale.

Li Hua pulled out her own Lighthouse communication device and initiated a formless signal interceptor shield, gently placing the Lighthouse communication device on the table.

“Maybe you did not know this. Although the souls of us Transmigraters have the special trait for unlimited transmigrations, after you transmigrate too many times, it will start to have a bleaching effect.”

“Bleaching?” This was the first time Garen heard of the term. “What does that mean?” His hands did not stop, he was still making calls, this time to Kong Yuan.

“Although our souls cannot die, due to being forcibly distorted by the interference of space-time and various other forms of radiation energy, we will start to lose our memories, and eventually, our own souls. At the very end, when we have lost everything, we will become an empty soul, starting over from a blank slate… The more times you transmigrate, the more intense the effects of this phenomenon,” Li Hua lowly explained.

“However, Ah Xue did not just transmigrate three or four times like she said. She had transmigrated more than eight times…”

“Eight times is the limit.” Nine-Tailed Fox opened his mouth, speaking softly at the side. “She was with me since the very start. She cannot die another time! She already had half of her memories from the past worlds bleached away, if she dies again… She might not even remember who am I anymore.”

Chapter 1194: Surprise Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Eight times…” Garen took a deep breath. To think that an average looking person like Kong Xinxue would have transmigrated more than eight times before.

The coldness lingering in the restaurant slowly started to fade away. This was considered an oversight on his part, he did not expect that there would be someone other than Slayer who had the strength and ability to target Kong Xinxue.

“The most important thing now is to find Ah Xue,” Li Hua said urgently.

At this point, Garen put down his phone. Kong Yuan did not pick up his phone as well.

This gave him an uneasy feeling in his heart.

“We have searched all the places we could, before finally coming to you at sea,” Li Hua sighed. “I hope you understand why Wenzhen lost control of her emotions earlier.”

“I was careless this time,” Garen calmly admitted his oversight. After talking with the Transmigraters and understanding their situation, he understood that no matter his Natural Attribute Points or the path he chose in the Mother Stream System, it was almost completely unique. The amount of Mother Stream Practitioners were too low, there was almost no one who was known for it. On the other hand, the Natural Attribute Points was even more overpowered, it could help an average person breeze their weakest period in the beginning at their fastest rate.

This was the reason Nine-Tailed Fox and the others had already been stagnating at their peak for the longest time, whilst Garen could improve to this ridiculous level due to his higher Soul Limit and continuous nourishment of the Soul Ring.

With an average Attribute Point of more than five, he would be able to knock down a Mammoth with ease, he was equivalent to a Humanoid T-Rex. For him, handling normal materials was like handing flour, crumbling to dust with just the slightest of pressure.

Seated down, Garen’s entire body also looked exponentially stronger as compared to a year ago. His body was easily twice as large as Nine-Tailed Fox. In his white suit that he changed into earlier, it gave of an excessively strong and massive stature.

“Is there any information on where Ah Xue was last seen?”

“Of course there is. I have already hired the best pursuit specialist to investigate and record the situation at the scene,” Nine-Tailed Fox had also completely calmed down. Although her tone was still cold, it was no longer like when she lost control earlier.

“Send me the information,” Garen said with an unquestionable tone.

“Slayer is just outside. I’ll go ask him myself.”

Nine-Tailed Fox was slightly shocked.

“I have fought the Slayer before, the difference between our strength is too high, I’m definitely no match for him. Even if we combine our strengths…”

“It’s fine,” Garen smiled, a weird air of confidence leaked from him. Instantly, Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua who seemed like she had something to say were completely silenced.

******

Slann Country Border, Yhann Forest Area.

Within the luscious greenery of the large mangrove forest lied a winding and rugged road.

Vroom!!

Yuria was riding on a black heavyweight motorcycle, his body leaning forward as he sped down the road. He was in a skintight leather suit and a pair of brown sunglasses, completely focussed on the road.

His sister Yurijie was seated behind him, her arms holding on to his waist tightly.

As the motorcycle zoomed past the large mangrove forest, the sound of its engine echoed in the distance. Their speed whipped up the wilted leaves on the road, blowing them up into the sky.

The gloomy sky was covered in clouds, making the entire skyscape a whitish-gray patch. Occasionally, sounds of roaring thunder could be heard.

The motorcycle sped straight towards a sharp turn. The road ahead somehow had a huge log in the middle of it, completely blocking their path.

The motorcycle started to slow down, stopping right before they hit the log.

Yuria signaled for his sister to wait at the side. Without saying a word, he alertly surveyed their surroundings, pulling out the long saber from the scabbard attached to the side of his waist.

Yurijie silently nodded at him, similarly pulling out her saber from her back. The two stood back-to-back as they slowly inched towards the two sides of the forest respectively.

Bang!!

Suddenly, there was a loud explosion right below Yuria’s feet.

An intense flare shot up to the sky, breaking through the ground. A large ball of scarlet red flames and smoke burst out, knocking Yuria away, lying straight into a thick tree branch nearby.

“High explosives!!” Yuria felt a sharp pain surging throughout his body, his vision completely blurred up.

The saber in his hand had also been broken in half from the impact of the explosion.

“They really seem to think highly of me, don’t they… This power… It’s enough to kill an elephant with just the impact…” Even if his Saber Arts were unparalleled, against these types of surprise attacks, he would still have incurred heavy damages despite the Savior’s vitality enhancements.

Yuria tried his hardest to scan the area with his blurred vision. He dropped down from the branch and slowly tried to regain his stability. Under the dark lighting, he vaguely saw a large silhouette slowly moving towards him.

Thump… Thump… Thump…

It was the sound of heavy footsteps.

“Humans… How could they have such heavy footsteps?” Yuria was lying flat on his belly, desperately attempting to push himself up. However, he could not stand up for some reason. He tried mustering up all his might but somehow felt his entire body being completely powerless. The power of the Savior he used to have absolute control over had completely disappeared.

“Bro…” He could vaguely hear someone call out to him.

“Xiaojie…” He reached out at the direction of the voice, seemingly grabbing on to something but his grip immediately loosened.

After a moment, the large silhouette finally walked up to Yuria. Looking at it up close, he was shocked to see that it was a giant robot standing at more than two meters in height.

He had a triangular head and his body looking as sturdy as a tank. The robot lifted up one of its legs, before furiously stomping down on Yuria’s back.

Bam.

A sudden intense pain.

Yuria’s vision turned red as he completely passed out.

******

Pitter Patter…

The rain slowly splattered onto the ground. The icy cold water dripped down along Yuria’s cheeks.

It was already night time. A tiny figure walked up to him and squatted down. She slowly turned Yuria’s body over before lightly slapping his face.

“Hey, wake up!”

Yuria remained motionless, his blood being washed off by the raindrops on his face. The mixture of blood and rain slowly flowed down his still unconscious body onto the ground, dying the grass below him a pale red.

The tiny figure did not have an umbrella, her body had already been completely drenched by the heavy rain. Looking at the situation, she rapidly applied pressure on to Yuria’s chest, placing her ear on it to check for his heartbeat. He was still alive.

This person then stood up and looked around, but there was no one in sight who could lend a helping hand. Seeing no other option, she once again squatted down. With some difficulty, she carried Yuria’s body on her shoulders, slowly moving out of the forest onto the road ahead.

******

“What? Yuria is also missing?!”

Garen stood in the restaurant, frustratedly talking on the phone with one of the special agents from the National Security Bureau giving him a report.

“When did this happen?”

“Just a few moments ago. Our contact with the Yuria siblings suddenly got cut off. At the same time, all the communication devices on his body had also been disconnected. Our satellite monitors found the vehicle they were riding abandoned in the middle of the road. The area had traces of an explosion.” This female special agent was someone the National Security Bureau specifically tasked to give these reports and updates to Garen. Her speech was short and concise, not wasting any time when conveying the messages.

“Yuria’s movements was something that only the National Security Bureau and us would know about. Do we have a spy in our midst!?” Li Hua stood up and said in a low voice.

“This is bad,” Garen nodded, his expression starting to pale, “Yuria is a key figure in our plan. This type of incident wasn’t accounted for in our original plan. Furthermore, Ah Xue is also missing.”

“Could it be the work of the same people?” Nine-Tailed Fox stood up and said. Her current emotions had completely calmed down.

“Vulture would never attempt this stunt on their own. Maybe it’s one of the other two countries’ forces,” Garen guessed, “Red Nation and Black Federation. It should be one of them?”

“The possibility of it being the Black Federation is much higher,” Nine-Tailed Fox replied. “They are an ambitious bunch, always trying to start wars and challenges. Yuria is one of the Four Cornerstones, this is something that most of the higher-ups all over the world acknowledged. Their intentions and goals are very obvious, but why would Ah Xue also be targeted?”

“Let’s continue this when we get back.”

Garen walked out of the restaurant and arrived at the deck. Both hands holding on to the railings at the sides of the ship. He felt the waves of the blue sea violently crashing about causing the cruise ship to rock. He could also see a few ships moving in the distance.

Chapter 1195: Mystery 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bam!

Garen threw his fist at the speedboat coming up next to him, knocking off the people on it. Jumping onto the new speedboat, he sped directly towards another group of speedboats.

Weaving in between two enemy speedboats, Garen drew his blades.

With a swift slash, four white-shirted enemies fell into the sea whilst grabbing on to their necks.

“Too weak!”

Garen rapidly sheathed his knife. Suddenly, Garen’s eyes opened wide, he moved his scabbard to block something.

Twank!

A bullet the size of his index finger ricocheted off, creating a small dent on his scabbard.

“Armor-piercing rounds?!” Garen was not shocked, but rather, he was delighted. Looking back at the enemy who fired at him from afar, it was one of the three robots he saw earlier. “Now that’s more like it. There’s no meaning if all of you are so weak!”

With a maneuver of the speedboat, he headed directly towards his target.

The dozens of gun barrels behind the robot shot all at once, causing a loud boom similar to a huge clap of thunder. Spitting out a large flames, it emitted a deafening roar, which caused the seawater to start ripple uncontrollably.

Large amounts of armor-piercing rounds were shot towards Garen. The intense amount of recoil had caused even the robot and the speedboat it was on to be pushed back.

The bullet speed was extremely fast, especially since the gun barrels were all custom-made. At the same time, it also had a high explosive and penetrative power. It was something that a small handgun could never replicate.

Nine-Tailed Fox and the others were looking at this scene in the distance, their heart rate immediately peaked. This level of attack was absurd. It would still be fine if it was average bullets, but there were also armor-piercing rounds and explosive rounds mixed amongst the normal rounds, even Nine-Tailed Fox would not have the ability to survive that attack. The only option was to find cover. However, Garen was on a speedboat in the middle of the sea. If he went to find cover, he would lose his current position, putting him at a disadvantageous situation and at risk of being surrounded.

“Save him!” Almost simultaneously, Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua thought out loud. Garen was neither a Savior nor one of the Four Great Cornerstones. He had no unnatural power or special ability. Even if his Sword Arts and Saber Arts were top class, he would still be helpless against this type of absolute firepower. This was not even a power that a human could ever hope to wield.

Garen just stood on the speedboat. In an instant, he felt that everything around him started to slow down. The bullets flying straight towards him, the gunshots from afar, the screaming, the waves splashing, the firefight and shouting on the cruise ship, and even the fearful screeching of a lot of visitors on the average tourist boats, all of them suddenly played on in slow motion.

The firepower this time was at least two times more intense that his confrontation with Yuria. When he first fought Yuria, it was only against one machine gun, but now, he was up against countless explosive rounds, armor-piercing rounds, and custom-made rounds. Furthermore, the firing speed had obviously been enhanced, so the power of the rounds are definitely more than twice as strong. It looks like his opponent had already done some research on him, specifically using a weapon of this level to attack.

If the difficulty level when he was fighting Yuria was 1, then the situation Garen was currently facing would no doubt be classified with a difficulty level of 10.

They seem to be trying to defeat him as if he was a Main Battle Tank…

“How troublesome…” An idea suddenly flashed into Garen’s mind. He no longer had any time to hesitate about it.

Finally, at this moment, he used his Soul Power to forcibly increase his level. This was the trump card that he did not even use when he faced Slayer earlier.

Right at the instant before the explosive round hit Garen, his entire body seemed to glow with a pale white light.

Shing!

The dual sabers were crossed in front of him, a type of flame-like Soul Power Aura started burning around Garen’s body. If there was an existence that could see Soul Power spectating this battle, they would surely notice that his body currently seemed to be engulfed in a layer of pale white flames. This floating white flames looked like countless white ribbons floating in the air.

“Wind Reversal.”

Before he even finished, the speedboat under Garen suddenly broke into multiple pieces, while Garen instantly shot up into the air, his trajectory aiming towards the robot not far away.

His speed was extremely fast, to the point where even the bullets could not keep up with him.

Merging his two sabers as one, Garen sliced down from above like a high-speed circular saw.

Kaboom!!!

The robot exploded.

At the instant the saber sliced through the robot’s armor, the entire robot exploded into a ball of flames, bursting out in all directions. Large amounts of heat and light had completely engulfed Garen.

The fireball had a diameter of almost six meters, its intensity even causing the surface of the ocean to be pushed down by more than a meter.

The flames completely stunned Nine-Tailed Fox and the others, but the other attackers did not show any signs of hesitation. They continued their high-intensity attacks. Due to the distraction, Li Hua had injured her shoulder. On the other side, Nine-Tailed Fox was also ambushed by the two remaining robots. Luckily her speed was slightly faster, so she managed to get behind some cover. In addition to that, it seemed like the robot that attacked Garen was the strongest of the three, the explosive rounds fired by these two seemed lackluster compared to the other one. This gave her a sigh of relief, but at the same time, she also started to worry about Garen’s safety even more.

As the flames slowly dissipated, , the remains of the destroyed speedboat were still burning on the ocean’s surface, emitting a crackling sound.

A soot black figure suddenly pooped his head out from underwater. It was Garen.

His entire body had been burnt completely black and his clothes were in tatters. The two sabers in his hands were only left with the two hilts. He looked as if he had been rolling in a pile of charcoal.

“How sly!” Garen wiped his face, rubbing off the black parts, revealing his original appearance. Looking at his awful appearance, he could not help but feel slightly embarrassed.

His opponent was too ruthless! Who would have thought that it would use this type of move? If not for his current physical fitness averaging more than five points, that self-destruction would almost definitely be the end of him.

His opponent was definitely someone who knew him very well, otherwise, they could not have seen through his favorite closed-combat style to this extent. They didn’t even give him an opportunity for close combat.

“This proves that the enemy definitely knows that close combat is ineffective against me. Even when using an alloyed robot with an extremely hard exterior, they were completely sure that closed-combat would have absolutely no effect on me. This opponent seems to understand my combat power quite clearly…”

With a splash, Garen leaped out of the water, landing on the remains of the speedboat near him. Using all his might, he propelled himself into the air like a rocket.

Swoosh!

What remained of his sabers suddenly flashed white.

One of the men on another speedboat was flung straight into the sea. The other man voluntarily jumped into the sea, diving down for his life, fearing that he could not escape in time.

“This monster!!” One of the attackers yelled out in fear.

All of the attackers rapidly started retreating, leaving behind dozens of corpses without a second word. Within a brief moment, all of them had retreated at least ten meters away from Garen, desperately praying that he was not pursuing them from behind. They just kept on moving and running for their lives.

******

“Even High Explosives couldn’t harm him…”

Inside a submarine under the sea.

In the darkness, a figure said lowly whilst facing at the surveillance screen. He looked at Garen who was standing on top of a speedboat without so much as a scratch on him.

“Any counter-strategies?” Another person in the darkness asked softly.

“This guy seems to be like the Four Great Cornerstones, maybe a new Cornerstone?” The man facing the screen asked suspiciously. “At the beginning, Slayer was the same. High Explosives basically had no effect on him.”

“Impossible. Cornerstones would have specific Sacred Sigils, but he doesn’t have any,” the person in the darkness replied.

“So what’s the plan?”

“Let’s go with number three,” the person in the darkness answered, “No matter how strong his individual potential, there will eventually come a time where he’s powerless.”

“That’s true.”

******

“Are you fine?” Nine-Tailed Fox, Li Hua and Garen gathered together back at the cruise ship. At that moment, the cruise ship surprisingly did not have any major damages, it only had a few scratches and burns here and there. The surviving members of the special agents were rapidly putting out the fires along with the crew members. The battle was over. There were even some passengers who dared to peek out to check on the situation.

“It’s fine. I didn’t get hit that much, it’s only a scratch,” Garen shook his head as a gesture signaling that he was fine, at the same time, his gaze moved towards a point afar.

This caused Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua to also shift their gaze in the same direction.

“What are you looking at?” Just as Li Hua finished asking her question, she was immediately silenced.

Honk…

At this moment.

A small warship appeared in the distance. It was in the shape of a fish, completely white, with a silver-white crab logo on its sides.

On the side of the warship, a white robot with a metal exterior was stationed. Its three-meter tall body lifted up a person with a single hand in a chokehold. It was a beautiful girl with a nice figure and long hair.

The girl was being choked at her neck, her body struggling mid-air. She was desperately hitting the robot’s arms with her fists, but to no avail.

“Ah Xue…”

Nine-Tailed Fox’s voice suddenly turned icy cold.

Garen and Li Hua had also recognized who the struggling girl was. It was definitely Ah Xue. Although they had already prepared for Kong Xinxue to be captured as part of their original plan, the problem was that the one who captured her was not Slayer and his men, like the plan intended, but rather another completely unknown force.

What were their goals? Why did they know their situation so well? All of these factors remained unknown to them. At this point, all three of them were quite sure that there was definitely a spy in their midst.

At this time, the escaped attackers on speedboats were rapidly getting onto the small warship, climbing in from behind the ship.

“Do you want to save her?”

A husky male’s voice rang out loudly from afar.

“Then come and meet me… Sword Master, you must come alone. Or else…”

Rip!

The robot just ripped of the white one-piece blouse Kong Xinxue was wearing, revealing her stark nude body that was going commando.

Her snow-white body looked almost as if it was glowing in the distance. Garen could even here the passengers behind him exclaiming and gulping.

“Heh… This is getting interesting,” he carelessly tossed his two broken sabers away, they were no longer of any use anymore. “You guys head back.”

Without even looking back, he ordered, “I will deal with him by myself.”

“They obviously know us very well. Be careful,” Nine-Tailed Fox lowly warned.

“Do you have confidence?” Li Hua asked softly.

“No clue,” Garen chuckled. With a light leap, he dived into the water causing a splash, almost like a pelican diving into the sea. Then he started swimming towards the warship, his movements as natural as a fish. His speed was almost comparable to the speedboats earlier, leaving a white trail behind him as he zoomed towards the warship.

Chapter 1196: Mystery 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

They stood there looking at Garen’s silhouette.

“It was the Black Federation after all!” Li Hua furiously said. “Their target is Slann. If they manage to kill off either Slayer or Garen, it would be considered a strategic victory for them! Bastards!!”

With a loud bam, she angrily hit the railings out of frustration

“Let’s head back,” Nine-Tailed Fox calmly said as if she was completely unworried about Garen.

“What!? Are we supposed to just leave Garen here and not care about his well-being?!” Li Hua could not believe what she had just heard.

“Just listen to me,” without an explanation, Nine-Tailed Fox turned around and walked into the interior of the cruise ship, leaving behind a shocked Li Hua.

******

Yuria slowly opened her eyes.

He noticed that he was currently lying in a log cabin made of mangrove wood. His body was resting on a wooden bed at the center of the cabin. He was even covered with a thick white blanket that was emitting a nice fragrance.

Looking at the window at the side, there were a few rays of bright sunlight shining in from the outside. They seemed to be sunrays that passed through the gaps of the trees. They were small and scattered, moving occasionally.

The cabin seemed to even have a heater as it was quite warm. On the table at his side, there was an electric kettle that was boiling some water, sounding like it was almost done.

“You’re awake?”

A charming voice came from the door.

Yuria had a splitting headache, his entire body was off-balance. When attempting to push his body up, he noticed that he could not even muster up that little bit of strength.

Cough…

He wanted to say something but discovered that he had no voice and could only hear the coarse sound of him exhaling air from his throat. Air was definitely flowing out of his throat, but there was not even a hint of audible vibrations or sound.

“Your body is under the effect of severe heavy metal poisoning,” the voice moved from the door to the front of the bed. Placing down a glass of water, a beautiful and youthful girl with a black ponytail appeared in front of Yuria.

“When I found you, your body was severely dehydrated to the point where your skin had started to dry up and wrinkle. You looked like a little old man. If it wasn’t for the medication I used on you, you would’ve probably died back there,” said the girl. She was not wearing anything fancy, the only accessory she wore was a white hair clip that gave her hair a side parting. She looked gentle and charming, giving off the vibe of a daughter from a humble family.

“Hah… Hehah…” Yuria tried to speak, but to his dismay, he found out that not only could he not move, he could not even speak. The only thing he could do was to occasionally shake his head slowly in disappointment.

“Looks like your injuries this time are quite serious…”

“Your spine had been broken into five pieces, it would take at least ten or more days for you to recover,” the girl dragged a chair over next to the bed, softly explaining. She seemed to be able to speak Slann’s language but occasionally dropped in a couple of terms from the Red Nation. Looks like she wasn’t local.

“In addition to all that, your spirit has been heavily damaged as well. Taking that and your physical injuries into account, you need to rest well. You’ll need at least one month to recover.”

Pulling off the blanket, she started closely examining the injuries on Yuria’s body.

Yuria noticed that the clothes he was wearing had been changed into a pair of brand new white pajamas. It was special pajamas with grey stripes, resembling the clothes worn by patients in hospitals.

What surprised him even more, was that this young girl was masterfully undoing the buttons on his pajamas. Her icy cold hands started applying pressure on his chest as if she was checking something.

“I know you have a lot of questions,” the girl softly said. “I know you aren’t a normal person. I also know there are a lot of people looking for you, searching for you, but what I have to tell you is that, out of all the people looking of you, some of them are trying to harm you.”

She reached out her arm and pulled down Yuria’s pants.

“The poison this time should be the work of those people on the inside. Otherwise, you wouldn’t lose your strength at the key moment.”

“Hehe… Hahahahaha!””Hey hey, what are you doing!? Where is your hand reaching!!??”

Yuria glared at the girl’s hand, refusing to even blink. He desperately wanted to stop her, but he was obviously completely helpless. At this point, his focus had completely shifted off what she was saying. He was more focused on protecting his virginity status that he had kept for more than ten years…

Woosh.

Yuria suddenly felt a cool breeze. His pants had been completely pulled off, Feeling his lower half completely in the nude, not even wearing any underwear, the complicated feelings he had were at volcanic levels, bursting out uncontrollably as he squealed out.

He started to feel a sense of sourness, sadness, and helplessness, all mixed in with a hint of excitement.

“It’s not like I haven’t seen this before. Why are you so shy?” The girl openly said as she started checking the injuries of his lower body. His thigh had a fracture and some internal bleeding. There were also a couple of places that obviously had chunks of his flesh missing, but everything had been patched up and bandaged nicely by her.

Luckily, his manhood seemed to have incurred no damages.

“I had already closely examined every inch of your body countless times when you were passed out for the past few days. What’s there to be shy about?” The girl calmly said.

After she finished her check-up, she pulled Yuria’s pants.

“Alright, looks like you’re recovering quite nicely.”

“Haheha… Heha…” Yuria opened his mouth trying to say something.

“I guess you’re trying to ask who I am,” the girl laughed. “Don’t worry, I’m not going to harm you. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have saved you back then,” she paused briefly. “As for my name, there’s no meaning in revealing it, so I’ll just leave it at that.”

After she finished speaking, she turned around and left the log cabin. After closing the door, her footsteps slowly faded away as she walked through what seemed like a thick layer of dry leaves.

“Hahah…What the heck!” Yuria could not suppress the memory of the scene that just happened. He was uncontrollably replaying the scene of the girl pulling off his pants and touching him in different parts of his lower body.

Then, rather embarrassingly, he became hard…

No, but rather, he was never flaccid from the start…

“Hahe…” Yuria suddenly thought of Xiaojie. “Xiaojie, I hope you’re fine…”

At the time, various questions popped up in his head. Who poisoned him? Why did they poison him? How did he fall for the explosive trap? Seems like there was definitely a planted sensor, otherwise the enemy would not have known about his movements so accurately. Furthermore, where did Xiaojie go? This young girl who saved him seemed to have a lot of knowledge about what was going on behind the scenes, what is her actual identity?

A series of different questions and thoughts started jumbling up inside his mind, giving him a migraine. His originally weak body suddenly felt a surge in fatigue as a natural defense mechanism. After a while, he fell asleep again.

******

Splash!

On a deserted island in the Slann Sea.

There were a few seals on the beach lazily resting under the sun. Suddenly, they were startled by a loud splash from the water. They looked towards the direction of the splash where a black head suddenly emerged from the water, followed by an entire human body as it slowly walked up to the shore. Standing up straight, the figure walked onto the beach, leaving behind wet footprints on the golden sand.

Garen looked up at the hot sun above him, then at the seals that were once again lazily enjoying the sun. These greyish-black furred fellows were obviously enjoying their time under the sun.

“What the heck?” Garen mumbled. Why would a seal that could originally be found in the colder sea regions be in this sort of tropical region enjoying the sun? Were they not afraid of being burned to death by the heat?

Looking at these seals who treated him like a harmless creature, Garen decided to ignore them. He walked straight up the beach, surveying his surroundings.

This was not a big island. There was a luscious forest that comprised of coconut trees and various large-leafed trees. In the middle of it all was an extremely simple-looking golden beach.

Garen saw that the warship had stopped at this island when he was a distance away, following it all the way to this island. However, now that he looked at it, this was most likely not a deserted island. Due to how the seals reacted, he knew that they were already used to the presence of humans as they had completely lost their natural alertness against humans.

“How interesting…” He glanced over at into the depths of the island.

Shaking off the water on his body, the water immediately turned into a white mist, clearly visible under the sunlight.

******

“All units on guard! All units on guard!! The enemy has entered the border of the base! All battle units ready yourselves at your stations! Alert level, Red!”

Inside an underground base in the island, a husky male voice rang out,

The entire huge base functioned like a huge beehive. Countless white-shirted combatants were running out from different departments. They were armed with a large number of guns and equipment and a lot of them even had cyborg bodies.

At the center of the base, within a red three-meter tall artificial crystal tube, Kong Xinxue had her eyes closed shut, floating at the center of the tube. Her white blouse was completely undamaged.

The naked girl in the hands of the huge three-meter tall robot, though visibly similar to Kong Xinxue in their appearance had some minor differences in their detailed features. If one were to look closely, they would easily notice that the two were not the same people.

“Let’s move… We must finish off the strongest Sword Master of Slann!! We cannot let Slann develop the second!!” The robot’s icy cold voice continuously echoed throughout the huge hall.

Clank!!

Two large and sharp crescent blades popped out from the robots two arms.

“I felt a force… A very strong force…” The naked girl closed her eyes, her face turned towards a direction outside of the base.

“Yes… I could feel it too…” The robot turned around, now facing the same direction as her.

On the beach, Garen’s entire body was surging with Soul Energy, almost as if his entire body was engulfed in countless white flames.

The strong Soul Energy Force started burning even more intensely, slowly forming the illusion of a gigantic abstract peacock behind him.

At this point, there was no longer a reason to hold back. This was because he had already felt it, another existence with Soul Energy Force…

Countless autocannons slowly rose up from in between the forests of the island. Large amounts of combatants in white military uniforms also slowly appeared out of the forest.

There were also chariots, helicopters and infantry scooters.

Garen tilted his head, slyly grinning.

He raised up his right palm.

“How unfortunate… I don’t have my sabers…”

Whoosh!

He disappeared into thin air in an instant.

Kaboom!

Countless cannons started firing simultaneously. Large amounts of explosive rounds, armor-piercing rounds, and radiation rounds hit the area Garen was standing on just now, causing the beach to explode, whipping the sand and dust into the air. Flames, acid, and metal shreds were flying about in the air.

Amongst all the cannon’s fire, a shadow flew straight into the crowd in the forest. Large amounts of people were knocked off their feet like a bunch of wheat being cut by a sickle. The autocannons started to break and the chariots had a clear fist mark. Some of the equipment started to fall apart from the hits, some even straight up exploded

No one could stop Garen’s advance, this could not even be considered a battle, it was a massacre!

Chapter 1197: White Crab Army 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen kept flashing and jumping without even a moment’s pause, such that the guns could not pin down his location at all. Upon activating his Soul Ring and increasing his level, his speed had gotten even faster than before. Still, his true formidability lay in the way he moved, almost as though he could predict the enemy’s nex attacks.

They clearly thought they had him completely covered, but he would still manage to break his way through when they least expect it, and miraculously find an escape path where they thought there was none. And his powerful physical fitness allowed him to completely ignore any long-range aftershocks generated from the explosions.

That was why, just a few minutes after the beginning of the battle, Garen was strolling leisurely through the battle squads, completely unaffected.

His Combat Strength was incomparable to how he had been one year ago.

“Is he still human?!!” A soldier driving a tank in the distance had broken into a cold sweat.

“He’s literally a monster,” said another soldier coldly. “Just fight him as though he’s an inhuman monster. Don’t get distracted, ready the cannons!”

“Yes, sir!”

Boom!

The insides of the tank instantly caved in, as a clear fist-print sunk into the tank from outside.

Brrr!!!

An intense tremor immediately traveled through the whole tank. The two soldiers did not even have time to scream before their bodies crumpled to the ground, spasming as they foamed at the mouth. They were clearly not going to last long.

Outside the tank, Garen leaped backward, his palm tapping the heads of two half-machinized soldiers lightly. After he killed them with one hit, he landed more than ten meters away and stood steady.

By then, the dust had more or less settled over all the battlefields around the island. Fire and smoke, corpses, and battered remains were scattered everywhere, and the few helicopters that remained airborne decided to just leave.

Garen ignored them. Unlike in the Mech World, he did not have long-range attack options here, so he could not do anything to those helicopters. Of course, he could also use these soldiers’ guns, but it did not really matter. After all, even if he caught up with them, destroying these choppers would not be easy. They were all equipped with heavy armor, so not only would normal guns have no effect, he would even need some specially-made weapons for this.

Garen did not intend to go to all that trouble.

Stepping on a piece of the tank’s broken metal remains, he looked around him. Only a dozen or so soldiers were left from the previously hundred-man-strong battle squad, and these were rapidly retreating. Of the ones left behind, some were lying on the ground, and others were already on fire, catching the flames ignited as a result of the explosions. They sizzled as they burned, emanating the fragrant aroma of cooking flesh as well as the odor of something charring.

“They’re all small fry.” Garen felt slightly bored. With his current powers, bullying minnows like these was completely meaningless.

He kind of wanted to go to Lighthouse as soon as possible now. According to Nine-Tails Fox and the others, the basic rules in this universe and other nearby universes accessible by Lighthouse were the same, and many of the laws were quite similar, such as the Physical Gene Law. However, these restricted the extent of supernatural powers, also known as unnatural powers. That was why many Transmigrators could bring a part of their powers into other worlds, unlike the worlds he had reincarnated into before this.

Garen could clearly remember how he suffered, always starting from scratch, constantly adapting to the vastly different universe laws, going through so much trouble and hard work before he could reach an extremely high realm.

“Sigh… Why didn’t I ever think of exploring the universes nearby?” he complained to himself for a bit, and then rapidly took one step back.

Clang!

A pitch-black bullet hole had instantly appeared in the spot he had just been standing on.

“Oh, a super long-range shooter?” Garen recovered with some interest. “There are probably three kilometers between us, how impressive.”

The bullet had evidently come from the other edge of the island, and the shooter was clearly an exceptional marksman.

Beep… Beep…

Suddenly, there was an anxious police siren coming from the sky.

Garen’s expression changed, he had suddenly remembered something. He began to move at even faster speeds, dashing straight ahead.

Boom boom boom!! …!

In that instant, a series of gunshots chased his tracks closely. Every spot he had just flitted path was instantly obliterated by the artillery fire, until all that remained were deep craters.

“Bombard with long-range wide-area artillery fire,” said a deep man’s voice from the sky above the island.

Boom!!!

Countless shots instantly descended upon him from up in the air and swept through the entire area within several hundred meters of Garen.

Instantly, the entire island shook intensely, as though the very ground of the island was about to fall apart. Dust, flames, tree branches, as well as shrapnel that could either be metal scraps or debris from the bombs, all of it flew everywhere.

Half of the entire island shook violently, and these tremors lasted for several minutes before the bombardment finally died down.

“Concentrated air bombs,” said that man’s voice again.

Bam!

A transparent air current bomb exploded ruthlessly, blowing up even more earth from the battlefield that had already been reduced to a crater in the ground. All the air there was forced down and pressurized, turning into waves of wind that spread in all directions.

Immediately after that, more air bombs were dropped one after the other.

These air bombs were extremely powerful. They could instantly condense the air and form extremely forceful shockwaves, which made them extremely deadly when paired with their wide area of effect. Forget humans, even tanks could be disfigured by the shockwaves should they get hit.

Inside the base.

“Even the Sword Master would not be able to survive a 无差别地毯式大面积轰炸,” said the robot coldly. “Not as long as he’s human, with a body of flesh and blood.”

“What’s wrong with a body of flesh and blood?” said the naked woman beside him angrily. “We’re not like you metal racks, if you can’t even enjoy the greatest pleasures of the human life, what’s the point of living? How boring.”

“It’s all over.” The robot ignored the woman.

******************

Since the restrictions on supernatural powers were too harsh in this world and universe, there were no effective ways to counter artillery fire.

That remained true for Garen as well. If he could use his supernatural powers, he would be able to demolish such a low-tech squadron in one go. Unfortunately, he could not use them.

And since he could not, he had no choice but to take the enemy’s indiscriminate gunfire head-on.

Right now, he was hiding in a deep cave, holding what seemed to be a black metal plate from the remnants of a tank. The black metal plate was as thick as half his palm, which made it more like a metal brick, but he still managed to twist it by force, turning it into a giant metal club more than a meter long. The giant club was wider than his own body and looked more like a shield than a weapon.

He was standing in a crater that was more than a meter away from the surface of the ground. As he had taken a direct hit from the gunfire, his face was looking slightly pale.

The gunfire outside finally seemed to have stopped.

Only then did Garen release the breath of impure air that he had been holding.

“Looks like I can’t handle concentrated fire head-on just yet…” He had taken one hit directly, and his whole body had been stuffed into the deep crater behind him, instantly sustaining internal injuries.

The gunfire in this universe seemed to be even more powerful than those on Earth or from the Secret Technique World, or rather, the gunpowder here was more potent. He had misjudged them.

On the bright side, however, he had used the momentum from that direct hit to evade all the other shots aimed at him.

“It’s finally stopped… Next time I can’t try to go head-on against mechanized squadrons anymore, this isn’t a universe where I can use supernatural powers.” Garen listened carefully for the noises outside. Once he was absolutely sure that they had stopped, he reduced his body temperature and heartbeat, slowly crawling out of the crater.

Whoosh!

As soon as he left the crater, he turned into a shadow that flitted straight for the other end of the island.

The enemy evidently could not react in time, nobody could have imagined how Garen survived that unavoidable large-area bombing. They had no time to react at all before they watched that wisp of a shadow instantly disappear toward the direction of the base on their surveillance cameras.

They had no time to start up their large-area fire, those weapons also required locking on and a cooling period, so they could not be instantly fired.

Garen leaped and jumped among the forest of coconut trees, dashing forward like a bolt of lightning. The surveillance cameras and automatic guns around him could not keep up with his speed at all, and before the cameras could even swivel around to see him, he had already vanished.

The trees retreated rapidly before Garen’s eyes, and he heard the clacking of autocannons turning on both sides.

Bang bang bang bang!!

The autocannons began to fire indiscriminately, since they clearly could not catch hold of his tracks, they began to simply fire everywhere. All they needed was for one hit to land, or to make Garen wary of the fire, so that they could reduce his speed and locate him once again.

Whoosh!

The edge of the black metal plate where it had broken off was unnaturally sharp. Garen held it in one hand and sliced mercilessly, immediately cutting down three of the coconut trees to his right. At the same time, he had also destroyed one of the automatic cannons positioned between the trees.

He turned his hand around and used the metal plate to block his left, immediately intercepting several cannon shots. The bullets sank into his metal plate, the tremor forcing a slight shudder out of Garen.

“What impactful force! Looks the enemy’s desperate!”

He understood and increased his speed further.

The forest sped past beside him, and soon enough, the few helicopters that had escaped before appeared in front of his eyes once more.

Bang bang bang bang bang!!!

The two autocannons underneath the heavy-duty helicopters began to wail, countless bullets sweeping toward Garen. They formed several clear chains of bullets.

But the trajectory of their aim was far too obvious, Garen just had to deduce it slightly and then he could continue forward amidst the chainfire with ease, completely unaffected.

The helicopter’s autocannons could not aim anywhere near fast enough to follow his movement paths.

“Rattlesnake!”

Someone roared from the ground. They seemed to be yelling at the helicopters.

Even Garen could hear that roar.

Boom boom…

All of a sudden, several lines of fire shot out from underneath the choppers, they were homing missiles!

But they were too close to him, their aim too obvious, so all Garen had to do was somersault, using the momentum to leap up, to avoid getting caught in the gunfire.

Bang bang bang!!

The forest began to burn. Garen circled around it, and after he evaded the homing missile, he darted straight into a small cottage made of silver-white metal, beneath the helicopters.

Clang!

Garen kicked the metal door and sent it flying, crashing hard inward and plastering itself onto the wall inside the room.

Inside, it seemed to be a reception room used for rest, and obviously, there was also an extremely thick black metal door on the floor. Beside the door, there was a high-tech electronic scanner, probably meant to scan the identity of any guests.

Other than that, there were also two cyborgs in the room, their whole bodies trembling as they pointed their guns at Garen. They cursed at him loudly, and he had no idea what they were saying. Still, he could see that they were completely petrified.

“I can tell that you’re very scared.” Garen grinned. This room had clearly been fortified with the best defenses, and regular autocannons would not be able to break through. Just now, he had put all his strength into that kick, otherwise he would not have been able to send the door flying.

Chapter 1198: White Crab Army 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Die!” One of the half-machinized goons finally gave in and started firing.

Boom boom boom boom!!!

The light-duty submachine gun made very little noise, but still could not hit even Garen’s shadow.

Compared to their response times and action speed, Garen moved as though he teleported. With such short distances, he just needed to leap forward, and before they could even blink, he had already jumped across several meters of space. He held in his hand the thick metal plate, more than a meter long, and casually bent over, slicing the two men’s waists.

Their guns were still firing, but the two men slid to the ground in two halves each, their mouth still screaming for a full two seconds before the noise died down.

The bullets continued to rebound all around the room, but Garen just waved the exceptionally thick metal plate casually, and all the bullets embedded themselves into the plate effortlessly.

He looked down and observed the underground facility.

“Why do these guys always like to build their bases underground?” Garen rubbed his chin. “Should I go down or not?”

He did not have his powerful supernatural powers right now, so if he went down and some of the people inside ignited a grenade or something powerful like that, trying to pull him down with them, within that sealed room, its power would be… Tsk-tsk…

As he was right now, there was no doubt about it, he would definitely die.

The hot weapons in this world were clearly much stronger here, and the restrictions on supernatural powers were too considerable. And after he forced himself up a level, the increased supernatural powers mostly manifested in his speed and reactions. After he strengthened himself, his Saber Art could be executed at twice the speed of before, at the least. That was the true power of it.

In Saber Art, when he was waving his blade, he would naturally follow the air current that gave him the most speed, slicing down the path of the gravitational field, such that everything was almost completely perfect.

But none of these power-ups could help him face non-discriminatory fire head-on. The only way to handle attacks like those were to hide or take them face-on.

“This is slightly hard…” Garen did not want to put himself in harm’s way.

Ever since he found out that this universe was connected to the other Lighthouse universes, all he wanted to do was simply kill time in this universe, holding in there until his physical fitness reached its most terrifying peak limits, and then he could destroy any opponent he wanted easily.

There was no need at all to fight the enemy to the death right now.

But clearly, there was a chance that the enemy held Kong Xinxue hostage. To Garen, that was a problem.

However, he did not have long to agonize over it, because the other party showed up just like that.

Brr…

Amidst the low hum of the earthquake, some drastic changes appear to have occurred outside.

Garen quickly retreated out of the metal house and saw a gigantic platinum-colored metal platform, more than several hundred meters long, rise slowly from the beach at the front of the island ahead of him.

There was a huge cylindrical crystal bottle on the platform, with a pale yellow liquid inside. An unconscious woman floated inside; it was the missing Kong Xinxue.

Two figures stood in front of Kong Xinxue, one tall and one short. The former was the tall robot that had appeared before, with a triangular head and the symbol of a white crab on its chest. Two scythe-like scimitars jutted out of its arms, making it look like a small-sized elephant. It had considerable tonnage as well, which clearly meant that it was the power-type.

The other shorter figure was the stark naked woman who had impersonated Kong Xinxue. She held a long, sharp spear in her hand, the kind of riding spears people only used on horseback in the past. It made a stark contrast against her demure figure, merely 160 centimeters tall.

“Force Fielder…” The robot spoke first. “You are emitting similar forces… Looks like we are the same.”

“?”

Garen had no idea what the robot was saying.

“Wanna fight? If not, just hand her over, I’m in a rush,” he said nonchalantly. Other than large-area bomb attacks like before, nothing else worked on him. Even the bombings from earlier did not cause as much damage to him as one would expect, all he sustained were some light injuries.

“Hand over your Sacred Sigil, and I can let you leave here in one piece,” said the robot in a deep voice, waving the scimitars in its hands.

“Do I look like an idiot to you?” Garen was speechless. “Please don’t ask such r*tarded questions, it feels like you’re insulting my intelligence.” And a Sacred Sigil? He never had one of those, so he could not hand it over even if he wanted to.

“Or else, I kill her.” The robot tilted its body to one side, aiming one of its scimitars at Kong Xinxue, who was behind it. “She’s your older sister, yes? Are you going to disregard your relative’s life?”

It had not occurred to Garen that they would do that, or rather, he had practically forgotten that he still inhabited Kong Xiaofei’s identity. Now Kong Yuan had gone missing, and Kong Xinxue had fallen into enemy hands as well. Indeed, if it were him, a face-to-face threat would be the best course of action.

“Go ahead, kill her,” Garen rubbed his chin and replied after some thought. Threats were the last thing he was afraid of, practically nobody had been able to threaten him throughout his journey, since he started from the Secret Technique World until now.

The robot and the woman had not expected Garen to reply so decisively and were clearly taken by surprise as they paused there for a moment.

Whoosh!

At that moment, Garen moved instantly. He tossed the black metal plate he held in his hand ruthlessly, and it sliced through the air, spinning at high speeds and crashing toward the two with a terrifying momentum. Even Kong Xinxue behind them was caught in the crossfire.

“Is he crazy!?” The same thought flashed through the robot’s and the woman’s minds. It seemed as though Garen planned to kill Kong Xinxue as well, he showed no signs of holding back.

And all of this happened too quickly. The woman still managed to leap away by the tiniest margins, but the robot was by nature heavier and clumsier, so it could not dodge at all and had to resort to holding up its blades to block.

Bam!!!

The black metal plate, spinning like a shuriken, crashed mercilessly into the robot’s twin blades, emitting a loud and piercing sound upon impact.

The vibrations of the sound made the woman next to it go numb, and before she could react, she saw something flash before her eyes. There was an intense pain around her neck, and then she felt nothing more.

The very last image she saw was Garen instantly pulling his hand out of her neck.

Since she was frozen still for an instant, Garen managed to kill her off before she could even activate her true powers, and she sank into the darkness unwillingly. This may have been something that she and the robot never expected.

On the other side, the robot was hit by the black metal plate at high speeds. It pulled its arms apart, and fiercely tore the metal plate in half. This was a demonstration of its considerable strength. It was almost equal to Garen’s.

“How dare you kill Carice, how dare you kill my daughter!! I’ll bury you with her!!” roared the robot furiously, swinging its blades as it pounced at Garen.

Large gusts of high-temperature steam gushed out of his ^1 shoulders and permeated the air, carrying with it a clear and pungent odor. It obviously contained some special poison.

Garen held his breath, at his current level of physical fitness, he could fight continuously for ten minutes without breathing. He had nothing to fear against poisonous gas attacks like this one.

The two of them dashed straight at each other, without trying any fancy moves.

Hah!!!

Garen bent his waist and gathered his qi, then he smashed his fist straight at the robot!

The robot also slashed at him with both blades at the same time. Putting all his effort into it.

“Only an idiot would go head-to-head with you!” Suddenly, the corners of Garen’s lips curved, and he disappeared with a whoosh, reappearing directly behind the robot. He crashed his elbow into the middle of the robot’s back.

Bam!

There was a dull sound. The robot fell straight to his knees, but there was only a slight dent in his back.

That exasperated Garen slightly. This metal was rather overpowered, to think it could withstand his attack with more than five points in his Strength stat. Back in the Secret Technique World, two or three Strength points were already extremely terrifying, allowing him to treat regular steel plate or iron armor like they were nothing, tearing through them with ease. In addition, he also had his Body Hardening Technique, such that even bullets could not penetrate his eyelids. It was only natural that he would be nearly invincible like that.

And now, although he did not have his powerful Hardening Technique, his Saber Art was still his strongest and sharpest weapon.

“Wind Reversal.”

Garen held his hand up like a blade, and as the robot turned around, he chopped his neck hard.

Hiss!

A slight pain spread from his palm, giving Garen a shock and making him pull back his hand into a hasty retreat.

It just so happened that two of them had swapped positions, and he landed beside Kong Xinxue, looking at the robot, who had shot more than ten meters out, from a distance.

Garen raised his hand and looked at the edge of his palm, where there was a small and slow trickle of blood. His expression instantly turned solemn.

“What is this?” He thought back to that moment, it seemed as though there was something invisible and sharp protruding out of the back of the robot’s neck. His own strength had made him collide mercilessly with the sharp edge, and that was why even his powerful defenses could be broken and blood drawn.

It was like how people could easily tear a piece of paper, but when the edge of a paper was abnormally sharp, a brush along that edge would result in a papercut. It was the same principle.

The smaller the surface area affected was, the stronger the pressure exerted on it would be. Garen’s instantaneous explosive power was already unimaginably fearsome, and it had all been concentrated on that tiny, thin little sharp edge. It would be a miracle if he had not gotten hurt.

Of course, that item on the robot’s neck also seemed to fall to pieces. That was the result of both of them exerting their power.

“It’s the latest gadget, the Invisible Metal Blade…” To Garen’s surprise, the robot actually responded. “Alright, time to send you off.”

“?” Garen was taken aback. “What’s that mean?”

The robot laughed coldly.

“The medicine should be taking effect right about now,” he said proudly. “Your wound will slowly begin to rot and split even further, while your muscle tissues and blood cells are rapidly infected and infested. The parasitic bacteria will worm into your body’s internal organs and tissues, causing you unbearable pain…”

“Medicine?” Garen looked at the wound on his palm. “You mean this? It’s closing up already.”

Seeing the edge of his palm where not even a scar remained, the robot’s voice ended with a duck-like squawk.

“No way!”

He stared at Garen’s hand in disbelief.

“This is the newest cutting-edge high-powered corrosive poison! How could it be!? How could it be!?” He repeated ‘how could it be’ twice, showing just how shocked he was right now.

Garen could not be bothered with him and sank a backhanded fist into the bottle that held Kong Xinxue.

With a splash, the entire bottle shattered, and Garen caught Kong Xinxue’s body in his arms.

Garen could already tell that this robot was merely a researcher who had never really fought with his own hands, placing all his hopes in his poison. Unfortunately, his poison was child’s play to Garen, whose fearsome physical fitness was at an average of more than five points.

Carrying Kong Xinxue by the waist with one arm, Garen walked up to the robot.

“Spill it, where’s Kong Yuan?”

Chapter 1199: Behind the Scenes 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Kong Yuan? What are you talking about?” The robot took two steps back. Garen had guessed right, he was just a simple researcher, and as such he did not have much fighting power at all. Or rather, he had obtained a part of the Slayer’s fake Sacred Sigil, a counterfeit, and yet he did not have the courage to use what little power he possessed.

It was just like with a weak average person, no matter how weak they were, they would still have some power. If they just trained a little and had the guts for it, they would easily be able to kill the person they used to be. But this person in front of Garen now evidently did not even have the courage for it, he relied on his thick armor for defense, hoping first to render himself invincible. Then, he used his poison to fight the enemy.

Faced with a minnow like this, Garen did not even feel like killing him.

“You guys weren’t the ones who caught Kong Yuan?” said Garen impatiently.

The robot kept retreating, his expression unnaturally frantic.

“I have no idea what you’re talking about! What Kong Yuan, I don’t know anything at all!”

“You piece of trash!” Garen had completely lost his patience, it seemed like the robot had no clue.

He held up his hand like a blade and dashed forward ruthlessly.

With a slight hiss, the hand blade pierced straight into the robot’s chest, as though it was a real sword. It vibrated intensely at a high speed, and he swung it downward.

Instantly, a clear white line appeared directly in the middle of the robot’s body.

Garen carried Kong Xinxue with one arm, leaping aside and quickly retreating to about a dozen meters away. Accompanied by a rumbling sound, there was a wail and tremor behind him.

Boom!!

The robot exploded.

The flames burned for quite some time, but practically no one appeared around him anymore. Garen could now be certain that the enemies here had probably issued a hasty retreat, and as he watched the flames rise higher and higher, he gave up on his initial plans to search for any spoils of war.

“The problem now is where do I find a ship to leave with…” Garen looked around him, but could not find any sailing equipment at all. “The people should have departing ships, right? Or else a plane would work too.”

He lifted the unconscious Kong Xinxue and began to wander aimlessly around the island.

Soon enough, a white helicopter rose slowly from the center of the island. The pilot was a black man, and Garen had threatened him into flying the helicopter away from here and into the distance. In no time at all, the helicopter had disappeared across the horizon, leaving the large blaze to grow stronger and stronger on the island. The thick smoke roiled, rising into the sky as a black-grey pillar.

No one noticed that, on one end of the island, a crystal-clear white gem was sparkling in the gradually dying flames, at the center of the place where the robot had exploded. The gem was hexagonal in shape, as though it had been carved before, and it was completely transparent. It also emanated a Soul Energy Aura that regular people could not discern.

If Garen were here, he would be able to recognize it instantly. This was a lost Soul Energy Crystal, a component part of the Soul Ring that he placed so much importance on. It was also a part of the Soul Seed.

A Soul Crystal could only be condensed with a variety of precious experiences and inspiration, as well as power. Although it was not as high quality as a Soul Seed, a few Soul Crystals were already enough to condense and distill a Soul Seed.

If Garen had obtained it and converted it into Soul Energy for him to absorb, he might have been able to condense a new Soul Seed, turning his Soul Ring into a Four-Soul-Seeded Soul Ring. It would also greatly reduce the time needed for him to reach the next grade of the Demon Lord Class, as well as increase his Soul Limit. Once he entered the Five-Soul-Seeded Soul Ring Phase, he just needed another breakthrough to reach the Seven Colors Phase, which meant he would need to condense seven Soul Rings of different colors — red, orange, yellow, green, blue, indigo, violet — once more. Finally, he would reach the True Soul Level.

After all, there were levels within the Demon Lord Class as well.

Another option would be to use it as simply pure Soul Energy, so he could strengthen his own physical fitness. It would speed up his journey of growth further.

Unfortunately, he never put any stock in such a small fry, and since he had Kong Xinxue with him, he did not have any spare time to check, so he left just like that.

Leaving a Soul Crystal lying right there, sparkling away.

The Soul Crystal lay on the black metal that had been charred and was still smoking, when suddenly it was picked up gently by a large hand and lifted up.

“Slayer’s Soul Crystal… A Forged Soul Sigil,” said a deep masculine voice. It was a man in black, completely wrapped up in a black cloak. His face was obscured, and all one could hear was his deep voice.

He kept the Soul Crystal away carefully, hiding it inside his cloak. Then he looked into the distance, in the direction Garen had left toward.

“I just need to collect two more, then I can condense the Sacred Sigil Seed…”

He murmured, turning around to look at the sky. There was a helicopter there, slowly flying toward him at a low altitude, and someone tossed a ladder down from it.

*********************

The helicopter flew slowly, surrounded on all sounds by the endless ocean.

Garen sat aboard the aircraft, continuously dialing numbers on his phone. Unfortunately, this place was dead-smack in the middle of nowhere, and his was not a satellite phone either, so he could not get any reception whatsoever.

“Do you have communications?” He looked at the pilot impatiently.

“Yes! Of course!” replied the black pilot hastily, fearing for his life should Garen fly off the handle. He had been terrified throughout the whole journey, after all, Garen had demonstrated that he could fly this chopper with just one hand almost as soon as he came onboard. It seemed that the only reason the pilot survived until now was that this person appeared to be somewhat lazy.

“Dial a number for me,” said Garen.

The black pilot immediately turned around and glanced at the phone screen. Then he quickly dialed the number exactly.

Unfortunately, the call still did not go through.

Garen was at a loss now, it was extremely scary to lose communications on a flight. He would not mind so much if it was just him alone, but now he had someone with him. If he tried to swim his way back like before, that would truly be troublesome.

“Do you have an emergency channel?” he asked the pilot with his final ray of hope.

“N-no…” The pilot was even more panicked now. “But I’m bringing up the naval map now, there should be some decently-sized supply islands nearby, we always go there to replenish our everyday supplies!”

“Then let’s head there!” Garen decided.

Beside him, Kong Xinxue also began to stir right about then.

Mmgh…

“Where is this?” She massaged her head, opening her eyes slowly.

“Over the sea.” Garen turned around to glance at her.

“I remember… being kidnapped, I think,” Kong Xinxue said hesitantly. “How long was I out?” Her words began to flow better.

“How would I know how long you were out? All I know is that it was quite a while,” said Garen, annoyed. “You’re the reason I came vacationing all the way out here in the ocean.”

“Well, it was your fault for neglecting your guard duty and leaving your post, otherwise I wouldn’t have been kidnapped, would I?”

“Yeah, yeah, it was my fault. I shouldn’t have left my position like that.” He did promise to watch everyone’s backs, and Garen was not an irresponsible guy, so he decided not to argue.

This was indeed his fault.

“What should we do now?” Kong Xinxue frowned, looking at the black man flying the aircraft in front of them.

“We need to find a way to contact the outside world, and then wait for help to arrive,” replied Garen, cutting to the chase. “It would be best if we could reach Nine-Tailed and the others. Still, the most important thing now is to first figure out exactly which faction attacked us.”

His gaze fell on the pilot in front of him.

“I’ll talk! I’ll talk! According to international law, you can’t torture prisoners of war!” yelled the black pilot hastily.

“First off, tell me, who are you guys!?” asked Garen directly.

“White Crab, I’m just a regular aircraft pilot under the White Crab Army!” replied the black man immediately. He did not dare to pause for breath, lest his slow response ended his life. He had just watched Garen kill off more than a hundred elites without batting an eyelid, and most of those elites were terrifying killers who had been half-machinized and modified, usually they were the ones who killed indiscriminately.

But Garen had destroyed and obliterated each of them as though he was merely slicing through watermelons. The survivors had mostly gone into hiding, the killing had scared them away.

“White Crab?”

“That’s right!” The black man nodded his head like a chick pecking at feed. “The White Crab Army is an independent mercenary troop, we don’t know what faction we actually belong to, but most of our missions are passed down from the Commander-in-Chief above us, our small island base is only one of the twenty-or-so such islands under the Commander-in-Chief’s control. Our codename is the Biochemical Army. There are a lot more armies besides us.”

“Who’s the White Crab Army’s Commander-in-Chief?” asked Kong Xinxue coldly. This question was crucial, this White Crab Army could very well be related to the traitor among their midst, or else the enemy would not be able to follow their tracks so easily, capturing Kong Xinxue as soon as Garen left.

“What about Kong Yuan? He’s fine, right?” Garen asked Kong Xinxue in a low voice.

“About time you remembered!” Kong Xinxue rolled her eyes at him. “He’s fine, he’s just under temporary protection for now. He has no idea what happened, so we told him that he was aiding the investigations of a murder case, and he’s at the police station now.”

“That’s good.” Garen nodded. Then he began to listen to the black man’s explanation.

“I’m just a regular soldier, how would I know the Commander-in-Chief!?” the black man yelled. “I’m just a low-ranking soldier, a low-ranking one!!” he kept repeating.

“Fine, fine, I know you’re just a low-ranking soldier.” Garen was exasperated. “Tell me everything you know.”

“Got it! Got it!!” The black man heaved a long sigh of relief.

********************

On the cruise

Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua stared down the heavy-duty robot opposite them, as though readying for war.

On the surface, this robot looked just like a normal person, the only difference being it had a high-speed spinning metal sphere connected to its arm, and every inch of the sphere was covered in sharp thorns.

The robot was about 180 centimeters tall and appeared to be slightly thin, looking more like a man in armor rather than a robot.

But there was an evident gap in its neck, formed by a cluster of metal strips. From the outside, anyone could see that there was no flesh or blood in its neck, only metal strips and wires.

The waves were growing stronger, and there were corpses scattered all over the cruise ship. The cause of death was clearly the caving in of their chest cavities, as though something heavy had crashed ruthlessly into their chests, shattering it and killing them through their internal injuries.

There were crew members among the dead, and some special service personnel, but most of them were passengers.

That robot had suddenly dashed out from among the passengers, staying hidden and motionless when Garen, Nine-Tailed and the rest were fighting hard outside, only to suddenly attack and ambush Nine-Tailed Fox as soon as Garen left.

Although Nine-Tailed Fox noticed something amiss in time and managed to dodge, she still stabbed in the waist by that extremely quick poisonous needle. There was a great force behind that steel needle, so even putting aside the poison on it, merely the impact of it was enough to penetrate the muscles in her waist.

By now, the blood was slowly dripping down the right side of her waist.

Chapter 1200: Behind the Scenes 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Nine-Tailed Fox tried to withstand the intense pain, forcing herself to stay on her feet and face the robot. Beside her, Li Hua held up her gun, but her complexion was pale.

Her shooting skills were extremely formidable, but in comparison, the gun’s firepower was sorely lacking, and would not be able to penetrate the robot’s outer shell at all. Under these circumstances, she did not pose a threat. Right now, Nine-Tailed Fox was the only one holding up their side of the battle.

“White Crab again.” Nine-Tailed Fox glared at the white crab logo on the robot’s chest with a hint of anger. “Just who the heck are you guys!!? Why did you ambush us!”

The robot slowly stopped the spinning of the steel ball on its arm and cackled with a strange laughter.

“Against you? I’m just following orders, as to why we’re going against you, I don’t know either.

“With your wound as well as the intense corrosive poison, no matter how strong your physical fitness is, you will definitely fall unconscious and go into shock within ten minutes. I just have to wait to achieve an easy victory, why, I won’t need to waste any energy at all.” It spoke, word by word, demonstrating its obvious intellect.

“You’re shameless!!” Li Hua could not help but curse at it loudly.

“Shameless?” The robot laughed again. “Even if I didn’t ambush you, you still wouldn’t be able to leave this ship. My Speed is 1.4 times that of yours, Nine-Tailed Fox, and my Strength is 2.3 times of yours. Plus, I’m covered with the most recently developed corrosive poison, touch me and you’re instantly incapacitated. Do you two really think you can win? What a joke!”

“You’re not a robot!?” Nine-Tailed Fox was slightly surprised.

“Of course not!” replied the robot with a laugh. “I’m just remote controlling this robot’s body. Unfortunately for you two…” Before he could continue, his voice was abruptly cut off. He seemed to be listening to some other information.

“Hm? That idiot Begal is dead!?” he said, his voice shocked and confused, but it sounded more like he was talking to himself. “Looks like it’s about time I finished you guys off.”

The metal sphere in his arm started to turn again, spinning into an illusory wheel that wailed as it cut through the air.

“I’ve investigated your trump cards a long time ago, now die!”

He stomped down hard with one foot, and a part of the deck caved in with a rumbling noise as the entire robot shot toward the two women like a bolt of lightning.

“Retreat!” Nine-Tailed Fox whipped out her ribbon, her body spinning rapidly so that the countless white ribbons circled around her, forming a soft defensive wall. But at the same time, this further aggravated the wound on her waist, her blood slowly splattering everywhere. It dyed almost every part of the silk ribbons. The white mixed with red possessed its own bright beauty.

At the same time, Li Hua was swept by Nine-Tailed Fox’s ribbon and sent flying high up over the clouds, until she finally landed in the ocean beyond the deck.

To her surprise, there was someone steering a Speedboat and waiting at the spot on the sea where she was about to fall. It was a muscular man who opened his arms and caught Li Hua with all his might.

Bam!!

The two of them crashed into each other on the Speedboat, and the large man’s arm made a cracking sound. Still, his expression did not change at all, he just immediately turned around and started up the Speedboat, heading into the distance hastily.

“What about Nine-Tailed!?” said Li Hua urgently. It was not easy, but she finally managed to get on her feet and steady her footing on the Speedboat.

“Someone else will fetch the Boss!” replied the large man quickly. “Relax, right now we’re the ones holding her back!”

“Alright!” Li Hua calmed her heart.

Just then, there was a huge explosion from the cruise.

Boom!!

The deafening explosion spread to the Speedboat Li Hua was wondering, and the tremors made both their scalps go numb, their ears buzzing. Their vision was a blur, and they could barely see anything at all.

Amidst the flames, a slender figure leaped into the air and landed on another Speedboat not far away on the surface of the sea. That Speedboat just happened to be speeding toward the side of the cruise, and managed to catch Nine-Tailed.

“Go!” Nine-Tailed yelled loudly, her body all covered in blood.

The two Speedboats did not hesitate in the slightest, rushing toward the horizon at the same time.

On the deck, the steel sphere robot dashed out of the flames and saw the two Speedboats that had already gotten some distance away. He snorted coldly.

Suddenly he looked up at the direction the Speedboats had left in, and saw a giant white army ship headed toward him at a high speed.

“Vulture No.1, huh? Consider yourselves lucky!” He leaped straight into the ocean and soon disappeared into its depths.

Even though it was an ambush, but in truth both Nine-Tailed and the robot knew that even if it was not an ambush, even if they had gone face-to-face, Nine-Tailed would still be no match for the robot. After all, that would be pitting the human body against a cutting-edge peak-level product made entirely of technology. There was no competition at all.

And Nine-Tailed Fox’s true abilities were actually more along the lines of Vulture’s No.4 or No.5.

*******************

Bam!!

Countless bullets and guided missiles left long trails of white smoke behind as they shot toward Garen.

They were currently on another island, but the same scene was repeating here as well.

After the black driver landed here, Garen was once again surrounded. And this time, the enemy was even better prepared. Their firepower was a lot stronger than before, and this time, they even used electromagnetic bombs and poisonous gas grenades without hesitation. They had clearly prepared in advance for this.

Garen had the black man take Kong Xinxue away from here, while he stayed behind on his own to face down the White Crab Army members on this island.

He held in his hand a long military saber that he had picked up somewhere, and the soil under Garen’s feet exploded, again and again, the immense rebound force allowing him to quickly dodge the vast amounts of gunfire that kept raining down on him.

Whoosh!

There was a flash of blood. Even if the soldiers holding submachine guns were armed to teeth, Garen still flitted past them easily, penetrating their necks and killing them instantly.

Garen’s figure did not stop for even a moment. Compared to the previous conflict, this fight had stronger firepower, but he also had more experience now. As a result, he could deal with the attacks more freely, facing the continuous and widespread fire from more than two hundred enemy soldiers.

He ignored the bullets completely, swinging his military saber as he moved at high speeds. Most bullets could not even reach him, he could easily block stray bullets with one hand, and ricocheting bullets could not even break his skin.

As for explosive and missiles, he might take one blow occasionally, but aside from that there was no problem at all.

Amidst the forest of coconut trees, Garen wielded his military saber and flitted past like a ghost. Wherever he passed, the soldiers there would simply crumple to the ground.

“Retreat, retreat, retreat!!!”

Someone yelled, and the soldiers at the back instantly abandoned their comrades at the vanguard, retreating without hesitation.

A fighter jet dived down, emitting a sharp wail as it unleashed its guided missiles.

Boom boom boom…!!

Consecutive explosions and fires burst to life not far away from Garen, but it was as though he had predicted the missiles’ trajectories in advance each time, allowing him to dodge aside.

Suddenly, a guided missile came flying at him and actually made a turn in mid-air. Garen was originally sure that he had evaded it, and was taken slightly by surprise.

“Heat-seeking missiles?”

He kicked up a large patch of stones and soil, forming a black flying dart that preemptively hit the heat-seeking missile with extreme precision.

Barroom!!

This missile was exceptionally powerful.

An intense wave of heat and flames exploded in mid-air, the resulting tremor making all the nearby explosions feel small in comparison.

Garen raised his hand to block the incoming high temperature and heat wave, then he quickly changed his location. Hurriedly, he dashed forward.

These were the perks of being a small and fast target, plus his physical fitness was strong enough. Only direct hits would have any effect at all on him, so the legend of one man destroying one small-sized army was repeated again on this world as well.

Whoosh-whoosh!

There were two clear sounds, and a bunker that Garen flitted past instantly misfired. Garen had stabbed his saber straight through the embrasure, instantly and decisively killing the person inside.

He had immense strength and the shock techniques to match, so with an enclosed space like that, everyone inside was simply shocked to death, no exceptions.

More than ten bunkers and several tanks, Garen annihilated them all with his ghost-like attacks.

Finally, he picked up a submachine gun and opened fire loudly at the armored helicopters circling the airspace above him.

The bullets hit the bottom of the chopper, clanging as they went, and somehow hit some crucial spot, causing the entire helicopter to sway and circle. Soon enough, each of the helicopters crash-landed onto the ground.

There was yet another string of unending explosions, causing this relatively larger island to shake continuously.

If someone could look down on them from the sky, they would be able to see that on this B-shaped island, the white earth was all covered in flames, human remains, burning trees, corpses, and fresh blood.

And one person stood alone in the middle of all this.

That person was Garen.

His clothes had been destroyed a long time ago, and he was currently wearing a full suit of the White Army uniform that he had pulled off someone somewhere. The only difference was he had torn off the logo of the White Crab at the chest area.

Holding his military saber upside down, Garen glanced at the rapidly-retreating naval ship and felt extremely bored.

“That wasn’t a challenge at all, how uninteresting.”

“Then allow me to be your opponent!”

Garen turned around and saw a young blonde woman dressed in white skin-tight clothes. She had all the curves in all the right places, and the zip at her collar was pulled down, revealing her deep cleavage. The only pity was that her face was covered with a silver-white metal mask.

And just like the robot from before, this woman also emanated a faint hint of Soul Energy Aura.

“A higher-up from the White Crab Army?” Garen raised an eyebrow.

Clang!!

The woman appeared behind him as though he had teleported there, and stabbed a dagger mercilessly at his waist. Garen stopped her.

“You’re not very polite, are you?” Garen chuckled once, turning the military blade back around and stabbing it toward his right. At the same time, his other hand formed a blade, swinging in a circle before coming down on the woman’s shoulder.

Even if he rounded off his Strength stat right now, he could still easily hurt the enemy’s bones and grievously injure her.

That was the benefit of being strong enough, you just had to hit them once and things will be settled once and for all.

Contrary to Garen’s expectations, however, the woman was extremely fast. She leaped backward and did several nimble backflips, heading toward the distance.

“Tailwind.” Garen’s saber gave a small jolt, and he also vanished from the spot. When he next appeared, it was directly under the place where the woman had done her mid-air somersaults.

Their eyes met, one pair above and one below.

A hint of a smile appeared on the corners of Garen’s mouth. His blade sliced upward without hesitation!!

Psst…!

The woman was still flipping in mid-air, and it never occurred to her that Garen would be so much faster than her. Frantically, she activated her ability. Her body became instantly faster, and a faint wind began to encircle her.

The air current caused by the wind picking up seemed to block off any interference from Garen’s blade, and at the same time, the woman’s body turned. She was forcing herself to twist and turn in mid-air, and just barely managed to evade Garen’s attack.

“Are you challenging me at move transformations?” Garen instantly laughed, and the woman’s pupils dilated abruptly.

She actually saw the military saber coming straight at her head once more. Despair shone in her eyes, and she closed them abruptly.

Psst!!

Barroom!!!!

Yet another terrifying explosion.

Garen looked at the intense explosions about a dozen meters away, his heart still pounding. Thank goodness he retreated backward as soon as he stabbed her, because it seemed as though the people from the White Crab Army had a thing for self-destruction. He abandoned the military saber and took off in a run.

Thankfully he managed to evade it too, or else he would surely be injured again if he took that blow at such a short distance.

Even now, he had yet to completely heal from the light injury he sustained before, so he must not get injured again.

Chapter 1201: Capture 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The flames turned into what looked like countless pieces of confetti, floating about everywhere.

Garen avoided the embers and looked at the huge blaze that just would not die down, frowning deeply.

The Soul Energy Aura was just in there, but he could not go in and deal with it. These flames burned at several thousand degrees, at least, and as he was right now, it was not quite possible for him to walk into the fire head-on to look for something.

“How troublesome.”

He turned around and glanced at the distant sky, the helicopter Kong Xinxue rode on was flying toward him slowly. Clearly, it was here to pick him up.

“Well, the Soul Energy is so miniscule, so I bet nothing much will remain.” Garen turned around and left quickly.

Soon, the helicopter left this little island once more.

Sitting in the helicopter, Garen lowered his head, looking at the island beneath him.

“How many more such islands are there?” he asked the black person.

“I only know how to navigate to one more,” replied the black pilot in a panic. He was terrified of ticking Garen off, after all, he had watched Garen massacre so many members of the White Crab Army with his own eyes. Right now, he both admired and feared Garen to the extreme, and was treating him just like he would the Commander.

“Take me there,” said Garen nonchalantly, narrowing his eyes. “I might as well get it all done at once. You’ve refueled the tank?”

“Yes, sir!”

“Then let’s go!”

Beside him, Kong Xinxue looked at Garen as though he was a monster.

“You– Since when have you become so overpowered…” She could not hide the shock in her heart at all, this guy went head-to-head against so many elites and killed them all! In her perspective, Nine-Tailed Fox was the strongest, but even she could not do that…

Garen smiled but did not say anything. He just sat in his seat, closing his eyes and resting his mind. The military saber leaned on the side of his seat, and he placed his hands on his knees, falling into a deep sleep.

Kong Xinxue sat right beside him, but she felt an ice-cold aura, the kind that warned all living creatures to stay away. It was as though she could sense a slight chill coming from Garen. She thought she knew this guy very well, but right now the image of him in her eyes was beginning to seem more unfocused and mysterious.

“What kind of a person was he in the past! How could he have possibly reached such heights in such a short time!?” In spite of herself, she was slowly growing curious about Garen.

**********************

Smack.

The large blaze was slowly dying down, and a piece of charcoal exploded in it, splitting in half. Immediately, a black leather boot trampled down hard on it, shattering it.

The man in the black windbreaker slowly walked up to the place where the woman Garen had killed was.

He bent down and slowly reached around the ground, finally retrieving a transparent crystal-like hexagonal gem from the ashes.

“Soul Crystal… number two.”

He murmured in a deep and low voice. Keeping the Soul Crystal into his coat.

“How lucky, I just need to gather three of these, then I’d be able to condense a Soul Seed, and if I absorb it then… Even the Slayer wouldn’t be able to stop me!! Hmph hmph hmph…” He began to chuckle coldly and deeply.

“I just have to be a bit more careful, and no one will know that I was the one who took away the Forged Sacred Sigil… All the blame will be pinned on Garen. Not bad.”

The figure retreated slowly, taking the Soul Crystal with him, and got onto a submarine at the beach. Soon enough, he had vanished into the depths of the ocean.

*******************

Garen strode forth slowly, picking up speed as he went, going faster and faster.

All of a sudden, he did a forward flip. Psst psst psst!!

There were three consecutive hisses, and three robots on the island beneath him, each three meters tall, simply fell sideways, rendered completely useless. A large burst of sparks rose from each of them.

Boom boom boom!!

Three explosions.

Garen landed and continue to walk forward, military saber in hand.

There were corpses and remains all around him, shards and debris from tanks or even fighter jets littering the landscape. Flames, black smoke, and all sorts of vitrified craters had turned this new island into an utter and complete mess.

“White Crab Army. Don’t you have any stronger opponents for me to face?!” Dissatisfied, Garen yanked up the last remaining bald man. The latter was the leader here and also the person in charge of the entire island. He was dressed in a white suit, and his bald head was almost shiny, so all in all, he would have usually looked like quite the strongman. Now that Garen was holding him up by the collar, however, he just looked weak and small, like a newborn chick.

“D-Don’t kill me!!” the baldy pleaded, his face covered with tears and snot. The terror in his eyes spread uncontrollably to the rest of his face, leaving a strange and distorted impression on any onlookers.

“You’re too weak…” Garen tossed him aside. When it came to people like this, he could not even be bothered to kill them.

Barroom!!!

To his surprise, however, the baldy only managed to fly several meters away before he abruptly exploded.

Horrifying green flames, accompanied with some spots of white light, exploded from that spot, instantly covering everything within a dozen meters of the center.

Garen’s reaction was instant, and he immediately retreated, but it was still too late. The impact hit him head-on.

Pff!

He could not help but spit out a mouthful of blood and was sent flying backward.

“Damn, what is this!!” It never occurred to him that these self-destruct explosions were not controlled by the agents themselves, and in fact appeared to have nothing at all to do with their own intentions. They just exploded randomly, completely out of the blue.

He was hit head-on by this blast and was thrown back, flipping head over heels until he finally landed on the ground more than ten meters away. He rubbed the blood from the corner of his mouth angrily. After sustaining several injuries like that, even his powerful Vitality could not save him from vomiting blood.

“Why is it that the weaker guys have the stronger bombs!?”

Getting up from the ground, Garen looked around him. There was not a single thing left alive on the entire island, everything else had either escaped or died.

“Consider this a lesson for you all.”

He turned around and left, walking toward the helicopter in the distance that was slowly landing from its low flight altitude.

Although Kong Xinxue did not have any particularly strong powers, she was still perfectly capable of threatening a black pilot by pointing a gun at him.

Not long after he left, the figure in the black windbreaker appeared beside the flames once more.

This time, the person had a fire extinguisher in his hand, and he sprayed it at the flames fiercely.

The fire died down immediately, and the black figure walked into it, his leather boots sizzling on the black ashes, emanating the foul odor of burning leather.

He bent over, using a piece of metal to rummage around the soil for a while before he once again found a crystal-clear hexagonal gem from amidst the ashes.

“The third one…”

He took a cell phone out of his pocket, and lightly dialed a number.

“What are your orders, Your Excellency?” A crisp and cold voice spoke from within the phone.

“There are five more bases on the White Crab Arny’s side, settle them all at once,” said the windbreaker-man softly.

“Understood, everything is prepared and ready, awaiting your orders.”

“Yeah, settle everything within half an hour.”

“As you wish.”

The call was disconnected, and the windbreaker-man chuckled softly.

“This is quite a decent haul…”

He turned around and walked toward the beach.

*******************

In a certain submarine at the bottom of the ocean.

“This is the ninth base to be destroyed.” Two black silhouettes stood side by side in front of a white screen, as they looked upon the sorry state of the battle-ravaged island.

“Garen annihilated three armies all by himself. This is unbelievable. He’s just one man!” said another man in a low voice. “Also, we couldn’t find the crystals, so Garen must have taken them. The attackers on the other islands must be his collaborators, working together with him in this operation. If I’m not mistaken, I think they’re collecting all of the crystals and handing them over to Garen.”

“We must get them back, the Soul Crystals are the foundation to our deal with Slayer. Since Garen has the guts to take the Soul Crystals from us, that must mean he is fully prepared to declare open war against us.”

“This time, are you going or should I?” asked the other person.

“I’ll go. As the Head Commander, you have too many things on your plate, and I might as well go out for a warm-up. I haven’t moved these bones for a long time, wonder how much of my old power is left.”

“As long as the people from Vulture don’t interfere, everything will go smoothly on my side. After you finish off Garen, came back immediately and rendezvous with me.”

“Got it.”

“Let’s show him that there are some things he should never have touched…”

******************

Aboard the helicopter, Garen sat in his seat, quietly waiting for Kong Xinxue to react.

“How’s it going?”

“I found it.” Kong Xinxue widened her eyes. “Don’t doubt my abilities, even if I’m not as strong as you guys, this field is my specialty!” she said in frustration.

“Approximate location.”

“It’s in the sea right beneath you!”

Garen picked up his military saber, opened the cabin door, and just jumped down.

Splash!

He sank straight into the sea beneath them.

In the ocean, everything was a dim, dark blue, but he could very clearly see the pitch-black roe-shaped submarine appearing right in front of him.

The fish roe submarine was somehow transparent, and a person, wrapped from head to toe in a windbreaker, raised his head suddenly.

He was holding in his hand what looked like an oval-shaped crystal-clear gem, and then he popped it into his mouth. Seeing Garen rush at him, he instantly sped up. A hint of a smile played on his lips.

“You’re too late, you.” He projected this message to Garen from a distance.

Garen had long since sensed that something was amiss, it was not just about how the Soul Energy behind him kept disappearing, but it was more about how someone seemed to have helped by loosening the security measures of the White Crab Army. It appeared as though word of him destroying the bases never reached the other areas, and he managed to take the White Crab Army by surprise three times in a row. There was obviously someone helping him to keep the information secret, only an idiot would think otherwise.

This was not like ancient times, where they required flaming torches to relay messages. Now, they just needed a number to pass their call and information to a very distant place. There was only one reason something like this could happen in such a technologically-advanced era– someone must be secretly helping him suppress the information. Garen was no greenhorn either, and his several hundred years of experience came in handy. If he could not even smell such an obvious rat, he would have wasted so many years’ worth of effort.

“Too late?” Garen’s lips curved, and suddenly the saber in his hand gave a jolt. It began to burn all over with white flames, as his powerful Soul Energy Forces were triggered and burst forth from his body.

The Soul Energy penetrated the submarine, and landed hard onto that gem.

With a buzz, the gem actually paused for a while, suspended beside the windbreaker-man’s lips, as though it was controlled by some invisible power for an instant there.

“Forewind.” Garen swung his military saber gently.

The blade burned with white flames and cut a strange path through the air before it landed mercilessly.

Clang!

The submarine was instantly slashed in half, and the seawater began to surge in frenziedly. The submarine gave a heavy jolt, and its movements slowed down considerably.

Chapter 1202: Capture 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black figure of the windbreaker inside instantly panicked a little.

He obviously had a diving suit on him all the time. Shedding the black windbreaker on the outside, he directly opened the other cabin door and swam away. At the same time, a large amount of airflow sprayed out behind him, significantly increasing his speed. It seemed to be some kind of acceleration equipment.

Garen pulled out his saber and swam straight toward that person. This person had been following behind him and waiting idly to reap the benefit, treating him as a fool and taking him as an uninformed person who knew nothing.

The speed of the two was not a lot different. Although that person was using an accelerator, he still could not shake off Garen. He was instantly alarmed; when he looked back, he was immediately in shock.

Garen was clearly just making a few simple strokes, but his body was as flexible and as natural as a fish, and his speed was even faster than himself.

“I am not from the White Crab Army!” He hurriedly opened his mouth and shouted. “I have been assisting you along the way. Haven’t you noticed?”

Garen grinned and continued giving chase.

“I am here to help you get rid of the White Crab Army! The enemy’s enemy is a friend! Why are you chasing me!?” The windbreaker person was feeling nervous at once.

Whoosh!

The saber light flashed, and the clothes behind his butt were missing a patch, scaring the fellow into quickly increasing the output of the propeller behind him in order to widen the distance again.

“I’m your friend! Friend! Bloody hell, can’t you understand!?” The windbreaker-man was frustrated.

Whish!

The boot on his leg was directly missing the sole, and the right leg was almost cut off.

Garen chuckled and continued catching up with his saber. This scared the hell out of the windbreaker-man. He promptly accelerated again, but the acceleration could only increase the speed for a short time, and there was no way of maintaining it. After all, the accelerator also had its durability and capacity factor. A short-term acceleration was equivalent to a short-term overclocking, and so it would not last.

“I haven’t harmed you at all!” The windbreaker person, whose heart was initially filled with glee from having taken advantage, was now having a brain dysfunction and shouting non-stop. “Isn’t it just a few pieces of your Soul Crystal? I’ll give them back to you!” He quickly threw out the Soul Seed that had just merged together in his hand.

Garen grabbed it, his face revealing a strange expression.

“What is this?”

“The Soul Seed! Didn’t you come looking for me for this?!” The windbreaker-man was exasperated.   ( )

“For this?” Garen immediately showed a baffled face. “No? I didn’t even know you have this stuff.”

“Then why are you chasing me?!” The windbreaker person was about to have a breakdown.

Garen quickly put away the Soul Seed, “You look powerful, and you definitely can have a good fight with me!” Stashing away the Soul Seed, Garen exposed his teeth and smiled again. “I didn’t expect to reap a new benefit just like that. Not bad, not bad!”

“Don’t play tricks!”

Before the windbreaker person’s voice had come out, he could feel a chill at the back of his ass.

Whoosh!

A saber light swept past, and the surface of the diving suit on his butt was precisely sliced off as though a scalpel was used, revealing the white buttocks.

“I’ll kill you!” The windbreaker person finally broke down and turned around to charge at Garen. He did not conceal himself anymore, instead revealing a girl’s voice. With an incomparable anger and humiliation, she rushed at Garen.

As a girl whose pants were actually lopped off at the butt, showing her embarrassing part in front of a man, this was simply a great humiliation!

“Um!” Garen was originally only trying to tease this fellow. He did not expect him to be a female, and it sounded like she was not of age yet. His heart panicked.

Boom.

The girl rushed to the front of Garen, and she madly slammed her fist into Garen’s face with full force. And then, her neck was caught by a big hand.

Removing the outer clothes, her body was extraordinarily petite. Because her arms were not long enough, she could only fling them about in front of Garen’s eyes.

“Let me go!”

Garen grabbed this fellow’s neck and swam upward.

The girl was only now revealing her true appearance amid the struggle. She had a long, bright purple hair until the waist and hip, but her body was no different from a child’s. Her chest was flat, though she did have long legs. However, the aura of a girl was completely absent.

Nonetheless, what made Garen felt familiar was that her body also exuded a similar aura as his.

That was the Soul Energy.

“Mother Stream System?”

He casually asked.

“Ah! You too!?” The girl suddenly was instantly stunned.

Pooh!

The two emerged from the sea, and the girl pulled the mask off her head, revealing a beautiful face. She looked like she was about the age of eighteen. She began to breathe in mouthfuls of fresh air.

Garen’s vital capacity was exceptional to an anomalous state. In the few minutes from going underwater to the present, there was no need for a change of air.

The helicopter dropped down the ladder, and Garen carried the girl in one hand while grabbing the ladder with another hand, quickly climbing up. He returned to the helicopter.

“You freak!” The purple-haired girl was thrown onto the spacious floor of the helicopter by Garen. The space of a military helicopter was relatively large. After all, it was a heavy-typed, and it could generally carry more than a dozen soldiers at one time.

“Taking off a girl’s pants! If it’s not for the kind of perverted and filthy thoughts, the general perverts would not even do this kind of shameless act! I’m going to go to the headquarters to sue you! Just you wait!” The girl shouted. However, at this moment, she could only lay on the ground and did not dare to get up as the pants on her butt had been cut by Garen. Once she got up, anyone could see her white tender buttocks clearly.

“Who is she?” Kong Xinxue was speechless that Garen caught such a little girl as he went down.

“I don’t know.” Garen shrugged. His body felt very uncomfortable as he was soaking wet. He quivered his body, and a vast amount of water vapor immediately dissipated into a mist and began to rise.

Kong Xinxue and the little girl watched with their eyes affixed.

“Fr… Freak! With such a great law restriction…you can actually achieve this level of control!” The little girl was obviously a person who was savvy in the art, and she clearly knew how difficult this kind of technique was. Seeing this scene at the moment, her face blanched a little.

Garen’s clothes quickly dried up, and he sat back in his seat, casually propping his saber against the seat.

“Alright. We’ll talk once we get back.”

There were black pilots on the plane, so it was inconvenient to talk. However, this little girl was definitely one of the Transmigrators of Lighthouse. This was beyond doubt. She was also from the Mother Stream System and even knew about Soul Seed, which was the name known only in Mother Stream. It seemed that there could be some valuable information to be dug out.

Garen’s eyes on the little girl suddenly became somewhat satisfying.

The little girl was scared by his blatant gaze.

“Bloody hell… Could this fellow be already at the Demon Lord Level!? He can even do kind of freaky act in this kind of world. If it were at other systems, it might still be comprehensible. If he was also from the Mother Stream System…” She did not dare to think about it anymore. “It can’t be that unfortunate…” She began to be nervous and anxious.

Even in the entire Lighthouse, there were less than a handful of those who were at the level of Demon Lords, not to mention in the most difficult Mother Stream System.

She was frightened at one side, while Garen began reaching one of his hand into his bosom and pressed onto the Soul Seed to start absorbing it.

A large amount of Soul Energy began surging incessantly into the Soul Ring. A lot of the basic killing experiences and sentiments were mixed in it. The protagonist was Slayer.

This was obviously some of the Soul Energy Crystals that Slayer had voluntarily split out to for the purpose of trading with others. He just did not expect those heads to merely have the experience and sentiment. Without a matching courage, everything was useless.

Since the beginning, Garen at the Secret Technique World understood that if the heart was timid, one could be crushed even by the opponents of the same level.

Timidity would give rise to indecisiveness, and indecisiveness would produce hesitancy. Hesitancy would cause one to be unable to take action with resolve and to react decisively. When one step was slowed down, every step that followed would be delayed. The entire strength in the body could not be played out at the moment when it was pushed to the peak and could only be interrupted by the opponent when the strength had not been accumulated to the vertex. Therefore, it would be considered quite good if one was able to bring into play sixty percent of one’s capability.

When the strength and speed were not as good as the opponent’s, there would only be one result – defeat.

On the battlefield, that would be death!

So, even if those people obtained the Soul Crystal, it was just a waste. It was simply impossible for them to exert its effects.

That was probably why Slayer did not mind giving out the Soul Crystal.

“Well, what’s your name?” Garen looked at the little girl lying on the floor.

“Night Water,” The girl’s heart skipped a beat and hurriedly replied.

****************

“You’re awake?” Yuria had just woken up when he heard the girl’s voice ringing in his ear.

“The injuries are much better. Just need a few more days to be healed. What an enviable body.” The girl gently pulled up Yuria’s pants.

“…”

Yuria was already feeling numb. Being body-checked by a girl every day, anyone would feel numb.

“Who are you actually? How ’bout my sis? Where is she now?” He could not help but ask.

He was still lying on the bed in the log cabin, while the girl would take care of him once a day. The rest of the time, she would complete chores such as chopping wood for cooking and starting a fire. The girl would always say nothing. Apart from the times when she took care of him, she would always be silent. No matter what Yuria asked, she would not reply, as if she was deaf and mute.

“Didn’t you want to find your mother?” The girl answered softly. “She should be at the Forest Capital.”

“The Forest Capital?” Yuria repeated.

“Yes, I only know that,” The girl stopped talking.

Yuria felt that his body had recovered a lot, and he seemed to be able to move.

He slowly tried to raise his hand, and his right arm was instantly lifted up.

“I can move!” He was overjoyed.

“Congratulations.” The girl nodded and showed a smile.

“I should thank you instead for saving me.” Yuria was in a good mood. “But can you tell me your true identity? Why do you know so many things?”

The girl shook her head.

“Sorry, I can’t tell you.”

She brought a bowl of oatmeal with some oil and salt in it, which smelled aromatic.

“There are many people looking for you on the outside. Once your injuries are healed, you won’t have to worry about the spy. This is your contact number.” The girl returned the phone to Yuria.

When their fingers touched each other, Yuria shivered slightly. His feeling toward this mysterious girl was very complicated. His entire body had been seen by the other party. As this kind of care had lasted for so long, it caused him to involuntarily have some different feelings.

“Don’t think too much.” The girl smiled slightly. “You will meet a lot of girls who are better in the future, I’m…not worthy of you.” There was no other expression on her face other than her smile, but her eyes revealed a trace of hopelessness and deathly stillness.

Yuria opened his mouth, wanting to say something, but when he saw this deathly stillness, he was suddenly stunned, unable to say anything more.

Chapter 1203: Trail 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Speak up. What’re you after?” Garen sat in the chair with his arms crossed and looked at the little girl, Night Water, in front of him. This fellow disguised as a person clothed in black to follow him around quietly and had a relatively nice submarine. It seemed that the intelligence of her side was also unimpeded and obviously, she was not in action alone. There certainly would be other companions.

“After? Nothing? Just following behind you to pick up some crumbs? Why put it in such a sinister way?” Night Water blinked and smiled back. She did not answer Garen directly.

The two had left the sea at this time and had returned to the Lily of the Valley at which Garen was originally located. This was the Slann’s site, which was protected by the Vulture and the Ministry of National Security. It was absolutely safe.

This was now Garen’s base camp.

“Alright, stop spouting nonsense. Just cut to the chase. My patience is limited,” Garen casually said, “I suppose, you’re following me for the Forged Sacred Sigil?” He took out the condensed Soul Seed, which had shrunk by nearly half. Most of the Soul Energy had been absorbed into the Soul Ring by him. ( )

In the Soul Ring, the three Soul Seeds were at this time rotating around a new kind of virtual and transparent Soul Seed. This new virtual and transparent Soul Seed was in the early stages of formation, evidently deriving from the Soul Energy of the new Soul Seed in Garen’s hand. However, it was noticeably much weaker than the other three Soul Seeds.

The Soul Seeds were also divided into strong and weak. Among Garen’s three major Soul Seeds were the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique (Blue), the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book (Black-Gold), and the Hellfrost Peacock Queen Soul Seed (White).

Among the three major Soul Seeds, Hellfrost Peacock Queen Soul Seed was the most powerful, and its radiance almost dyed the two other Soul Seeds into the same white.

On the other hand, the power of this newly emerged Soul Seed was not even one-thousandth of the other two Soul Seeds; it could be called the weakest in history.

“I was indeed after the Soul Seed,” now that there were only the two of them here, Night Water spoke frankly, “this Soul Seed came from Slayer and has a strong value of actual combat experience. The sentiments inside can save me from many unnecessary twists and turns. It is also medium-grade in the division of Soul Seeds. So, the way I acted was also considered reasonable?”

“Medium-grade?” Garen did not expect such a Soul Seed, which was so many times weaker than his three major Souls Seeds, to be actually worth noting in the eyes of the other party.

“Of course! Although the Soul Energy in Slayer’s Soul Seed is not much, it is very suitable for the basic development in various worlds, and it is almost unlimited. The strength developed in this world is hardly restricted extensively by other worlds. It’s just that because the laws restrict the bottleneck, the growth in this world is much slower.” Night Water had a stand-to-reason expression on.

“Well, I’ve said what I got to say. You should be letting me go?” She decided to simply be forthright. “I just happened to saw you fighting with the White Crab Army by chance. It was then did I go over to take advantage of the situation.”

“You…” Garen pondered for a while. “…have a way of returning to the Lighthouse?”

“How do you even know that?” Night Water was suddenly shocked, and she stared at Garen with a preposterous look.

“There really is?” Garen instantly laughed.

“You tricked me!” Night Water was speechless. “It’s actually nothing. I do have the way of returning to the Lighthouse now, but it had cost me a great price to obtain that information. I will not give it to you freely!”

Garen had now learned that the Lighthouse’s Transmigrators actually had a subtle difference compared to him.

They were equivalent to the flowers grown in a greenhouse. Due to having the Lighthouse’s guidance, coupled with the world’s environment which was less cruel than they were, they had not been developing fast.

However, he himself was different. Whether it was a coincidence or the direction and path that he chose, Garen had come all this way through conquests. There was no fluke.

“Tell me. I will let you go,” Garen said idly.

“You wish!” Night Water replied unwillingly, “You can just kill me! I will not tell you even if I have to die!” She had acquired the method after almost dissipating all her fortune and borrowing money everywhere from her friends. How could she give it to Garen freely?

“Have you forgotten what our Mother Stream System is really good at?” Garen smiled sinisterly.

Night Water was taken aback, and her body immediately shuddered.

“Don’t… Don’t you think of scaring me!”

The Mother Stream System specialized in the soul. There were diverse means of targeting the soul. There were some among them which were likely to be related to memory searching.

“As soon as I bring you out of this world, I will not be restricted by the laws then. At that time, hehe…” Garen sneered.

“….”

Night Water stared at the evil smile on Garen’s face with great trepidation.

“I’ll tell!”

She decisively gave up withholding and persisting.

“The Space-Time Hole can only have one person going in and out at a time! There were only three of us in total who came in! It also requires very precise calculations, time and opportunities.”

Garen began to carefully inquire about the so-called Space-Time Hole. Indeed, just as he expected, Night Water did find an unknown Space-Time Hole that could escape this extremely-restrictive world, but the price to pay was that every time, one had to clean off the power of this world that had not yet been formed in one’s body. This meant that one had to leave with nothing. Apart from the Soul Energy, she could not take anything with her, which was why they were trying their best to find this world’s Soul Energy, which was the force field of the Sacred Sigil.

By a stroke of luck, she discovered the battle between Garen and the White Crab Army and felt that she could take advantage of it, so she rushed over.

Unfortunately, she did not succeed but was captured by Garen instead.

“So what is it with the White Crab Army?” Garen intended to quickly understand this world. Since he could acquire the Soul Seed from Slayer, it would mean that there should be more things that he could gain from him. He turned his thoughts around and began asking about the White Crab Army.

“The White Crab Army? They are Illusionist’s army! Don’t you know?” Night Water was surprised.

“Illusionist’s army?” Garen was slightly stunned. “Not Slayer’s?!”

“Of course not. They are only collaborating with Slayer. The real mastermind is Illusionist!” Night Water immediately explained, “You didn’t even realize it?” She felt a little unbelievable.

“How do you determine that they are Illusionist’s army?” Garen frowned. How did an Illusionist suddenly emerge?

“I’ll tell you the truth. You have to let me go!” Night Water began making a deal.

“Fine,” Garen decisively agreed.

Night Water did not react right away, as if she did not expect Garen to promise so fast. However, she quickly recovered from the shock.

“I don’t know the identity of Illusionist, but I have personally heard the conversation between Slayer and the White Crab Army. I have the best cyber-espionage expert on my team. There is absolutely no mistake. In the battle between you and the White Crab Army this time, it was also us who helped you to block the White Crab Army’s communication!”

Seeing that Garen nodded, she continued.

“The White Crab Army seems to be an independent mercenary organization. It is huge, and it has a lot of mechanized technology. They have been doing some unintelligible actions, and it does not appear to be purely for profit. In any case, it is a very weird organization. The Commander-in-Chief seems to be a very mysterious and very powerful person.”

“Very powerful? As powerful as me?” Garen was piqued.

“I don’t know. Maybe stronger than you!” Night Water answered with a serious face.

Garen rubbed his chin.

“So how did the Soul Seed come about? Can Slayer simply create a Soul Seed? Isn’t that too unrealistic?”

“He is able to split the Soul Crystal, which is only a part of the mere experiential sentiments and Soul Energy. After I have condensed and refined it, coupled with my own sentiments, I am able to condense a good medium-grade Soul Seed. This can lessen a lot of the troublesome steps of accumulation,” Night Water explained, “of course, the people from other professional systems prefer to refer this kind of Soul Seeds as the Forged Sacred Sigil. They can solidify it on their bodies, naturally gaining the Slayer’s experiential sentiments and strengthening their combat. It’s just different uses and a different name.”

“When can you take me to the Lighthouse? You know that now that the Plot is starting, we can’t go back through the regular passage for the time being,” Garen enquired.

“Any time.” Night Water nodded assertively. “It’s just that, compared to the regular passage, my way is much more dangerous.”

Garen fell silent and pondered a bit. This world had a lot of restrictions, especially for the unnatural powers. Whereas, the Lighthouse was used as a transit point connecting many similar worlds. His strength had not recovered to its peak, if he were to head there right now, it would not be worth it. After all, the strength gained in this world could be used in most of the worlds, so it was better to stay here for a little while. It would not be too late to leave only after getting more of the Forged Sacred Sigils and increasing his Soul Limit.

After knowing that Slayer could create Soul Seeds, Garen was not eager to leave anymore. One Soul Seed could increase his Soul Limit, which was an average of ten points of fitness. If he could get more Soul Seeds and Soul Energy from Slayer, it would be a great advantage for him at the present.

At least for a certain period of time, he would not need to switch bodies anymore, as the laws of these worlds did not differ much from one another. Being able to acquire a Soul Seed without switching bodies was naturally a good thing.

He was not a masochist. Every time he transmigrated, he had to re-cultivate. If he could avoid that, then that would be the best.

“You will temporarily follow me on my actions in the future.” Garen also intended to quickly investigate the matter over Yuria’s side. He felt that there was something fishy about the whole matter, and the internal spy must be caught. Otherwise, his side would fall to absolute passivity. At this time, since Night Water had just said that she had a complete intelligence ability, it would be really stupid to not utilize such a great aid.

“But!” Night Water was going to protest, but she was directly ignored by Garen.

“I did promise to let you go, but I haven’t found the Space-Time Hole yet, haven’t I? Before that, the deal between you and I does not count, so…” Garen revealed a menacing smile.

Night Water was so frightened that she instantly shuddered.

The present Garen was almost standing at the top of this world. He was one of the strongest players alongside Slayer and the others.

*****************

“Are you alright?” Yuria took the phone and heard the inquiries from the phone.

“I’m fine. Help me to inform the minister. He must be worried. I’m alright, and I’m going to go to the Forest Capital to look for my mother,” Yuria quickly answered.

“I don’t mean to tell you off. This time you have really scared everyone. You are the Savior, one of the Four Great Cornerstones. If something happens accidentally, none of us can get away with it,” The man on the phone said snappily. He was also from the same Combat Department with Yuria back then, which was why there was much more propinquity in his tone. “How ’bout Xiaojie? How is she?”

Upon hearing the mentioning of Xiaojie, Yuria’s face suddenly darkened. He recalled the image of that tall robot, and there instantly was a trace of gloom in his heart.

“Xiaojie, she…was caught…”

“What!?” There was a sudden exclamation from the phone. And then, chaotic noises were continually heard as though all hell had broken loose; there were a lot of people asking about the situation. The people were talking all at once, and the voices were indistinct.

“Don’t ask. I myself don’t know what is going on.” Yuria’s face did not look good.

Chapter 1204: Trail 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I will have Bat head over there immediately. Egret will also hurry over to help you! Without initiating the unnatural powers, even you are not their opponent. In addition, Egret is very skilled in the area of digging out and gathering information, which would certainly be a great use to you.”

“Thank you.” Yuria felt much better. These people were the branch ministers under Garen. They were scattered all over the country and occupied a post in each place. During critical times, they could servttttte as powerful special agents to assist in the necessary tasks. Of course, only the minister and the deputy minister had the rights to mobilize them. The person at the other end of the phone was the deputy minister of the Unrestricted Combat Department and was also an old acquaintance who volunteered to resign from the Vulture to help out here… Root Doctor Jiatai. This fellow’s rear service was like no other, while his combat ability was second to that. What he was most powerful at was not in combat but medical practice. There were a multitude of cases of reattaching cut-off limbs, bringing people back to life from the brink of death and whatnots that had been performed by him.

“What’s there to thank? You little brat, what really happened that even cause Xiaojie to be lost!? The satellite records showed that you guys did not encounter any problem at all. It was just like you had a car accident. Someone must be blocking the signal.”

Yuria felt warm and that he was not alone in the fight. He instantly felt much more at ease.

“A robot, which was extremely powerful. I was ambushed and suffered serious injuries from the explosion. It seemed that I was poisoned as well. I suspect that there is a spy on the inside who intentionally poisoned me. I could not use my special ability at all at that time.”

“A spy… poison?!” Jiatai’s tone sank. “Are you sure you were poisoned?”

“Definitely. The person who saved me said so and treated me in accordance with that. It should be so,” Yuria nodded in certainty and spoke in a low volume as he laid on the bed.

The other side of the phone was silent.

“Alright. We had initially concluded that there was a spy. Otherwise, it would not be this easy to grasp your course of action and set an ambush of explosives in advance. Now, we are a hundred percent certain. Did you eat anything before you depart?” Jiatai asked attentively.

“No. All that I ate were the food and snacks you could randomly buy on the way. It was impossible to poison the food because it wasn’t only me who ate them! There were other people in the supermarket as well, and Xiaojie ate them as well.” Yuria replied in a low voice.

“I will report this to the Head Minister. You be careful, and the one who saved you…”

“She’s reluctant to reveal her identity.” Yuria recalled that mysterious girl, and there was a slight surge of emotions in his heart.

“Be careful,” Jiatai did not say anything more but just that, “your position has been determined. It’s best to wait in the same place as our people will be arriving soon.”

“Understood. If nothing unexpected happens, I will.” Yuria nodded.

The two then disconnected the call.

“The call has ended?” A voice suddenly sounded from the back of Yuria. He was terrifically startled.

The voice was very close to him, almost as if it was less than a meter behind him.

Yuria abruptly looked back and saw that mysterious girl standing behind him at the other end of the bed, smiling at him. With his sense of alertness, he actually did not notice anything.

His heart was slightly wary. Yuria suppressed the shock in his heart and nodded slightly.

“Yeah, I’ve got in touch with my friends, and they will come and pick me up soon.”

“That’s good.” The girl nodded. “I have to go too. Take care of yourself.”

“You’re leaving too? Don’t you want to meet my friends?” Yuria was surprised.

“No…” The girl shook her head. “I also have something to attend to.”

“Is that so?” Yuria felt that the deathly stillness on the girl was even more intense. He thought for a moment and asked again, “Can you tell me your name?”

“Sorry.” The girl shook her head slightly.

“Alright…” Yuria did not know what to say for a while.

“When are you leaving?” The girl asked.

“I’ll leave once my friends arrive. It is estimated that they will arrive tomorrow,” Yuria replied in a low voice.

The two fell into silence again.

Suddenly, Yuria smelled a faint trace of fragrance, which seemed to be some kind of a special aroma. It was very light but very refreshing. He faintly felt that his blood was flowing quicker.

“What aroma is that?” His mind was slightly wary. The Qi and blood in his body began to slowly accelerate, and his eyes began to involuntarily concentrate on the towering breast and the petite body of the girl in front of him.

Suddenly, he felt that the girl before his eyes seemed to be more seductive and sexier than he had seen before. Her white dress was slightly translucent, revealing the white underwear beneath it.

The slender legs and flat lower abdomen continued to attract Yuria’s attention.

His breathing started to become heavier, and his entire skin began reddening slightly, but he did not notice it at all. Instead, all his attention was focused on the girl.

“Leave me with the best memory…” The girl gently knelt on the bed and slowly embraced Yuria. Her tender eyes began to close.

The two slowly fell onto the bed, and pieces of clothing were torn open…

**************************

Sitting in the hotel room, Jiatai was wearing a white coat as he stood in front of Garen’s desk. Using one hand to support himself by the table, he had on a serious face.

It was nighttime. Behind the chair that Garen was sitting on, one could clearly see the dark night sky and the huge light beams that were sweeping pass occasionally through the floor-to-ceiling windows. If one were to look down from the floor-to-ceiling windows, one could see countless yellow-white lights and traffic flowing slowly like liquid mercury. A large number of light beams were sweeping everywhere, and huge billboards and various lights were shining inconspicuously. The entire bustling night view of the Lily of the Valley could be seen.

“…The entire situation is as such. I have asked Egret and Bat to head over there. They should be able to be of help.” Jiatai frowned.

“About the spy… What do you think?” Garen asked as he sat on his seat with one leg crossed over the other, seemingly indifferent.

“I suspect that the spy is very likely to have been by Yuria’s side all along. Otherwise, the spy would not have been so concealed and could timely grasp his whereabouts.” Since the transfer from the Vulture to becoming one of Garen’s men, Jiatai had shed off the previous decadence and had quickly mastered the power of the entire new department. At the same time, he had also recruited some of his good friends and some unfamiliar powerhouses from the Vulture and other places. Coupled with the recruitment of a few powerhouses due to Garen’s fame, this had formed the current Unrestricted Combat Department which was under Garen’s command. It was called the Unrestricted Department in short. On the surface, Garen was a minister in one of the Vulture’s branch. But, as a matter of fact, he had actually been placed in the Vulture rankings. Since the battle with Slayer, his position had directly entered the top three and was now ranked third. In fact, he was already the strongest No. 1 in combat strength. Although the first two were outstanding, their roles were mostly reflected in their background and other abilities.

Therefore, Garen’s current title of Sword Master was equivalent to an independent hallmark. He was also the golden fighter in ranked first in the Vulture.

“Bat can still make do. Regarding Egret, I have personally taught him throughout this year, and his ranking has risen to No. 15. His left eye is the latest multi-function detector, and so he should be able to detect who administered the poison and prevent the next possible poisoning threat from the other party. You did well.” Garen agreed.

“That’s for sure.” Jiatai laughed. “I have also equipped him with an internal linear laser, which can be also used for precise surgery at critical moments.”

“During my trip this time, I met an organization called the White Crab Army.” Garen changed the subject. “I suspect that Yurijie’s kidnapping, Kong Xinxue’s problem, and the spy could be masterminded by this organization. Did the Chief find any clue?”

“I will go and ask. The Chief is still at the Holy Capital. You’re also aware of the funding problem this year. The Chief had already argued with the Prime Minister and the ministers for who knows how many times.” Jiatai made a helpless expression.

Such a large organization as the Vulture would naturally require a very large amount of money, and the Chief was responsible for tackling these troublesome matters.

“That is really frustrating. What about No. 2?” Garen asked casually.

“Second Sister went for an exchange visit to the Red Nation. You also know that her identity on the surface is the Minister of Education. This visit is a trip dictated by the higher-ups, and so it can’t be avoided.” Jiatai was feeling even more impatient. “So now you’re the sole principal of the entire Vulture for the time being.”

“Then, I am really honored.” Garen was speechless. Although one might say so, this year around it was still No. 1 who was giving the order through teleconference.

He retold his encounter once again and did not mention the things related to the Soul Seed, instead only focused on the White Crab Army’s over-powerful technology.

“White Crab Army. I have come in contact with this organization before, but it is only an upper-middle-class mercenary. They actually have such a strong technological modification ability… It is indeed suspicious.” Jiatai frowned.

“Could they be Slayer’s force?”

“It is possible, but how does Slayer come to replenish this army with such a large amount of money?” Jiatai slightly opposed.

“We’ll wait and see. Since Yuria could meet the White Crab Army’s robot for the first time, he will be able to meet it for the second time. The other party is definitely paying attention to him. I even have a feeling that they value Yuria the Savior even more than us!” Jiatai frowned.

“Maybe…” Garen nodded.

Very soon, the phone on Garen’s table rang again. He looked at the caller ID. It was Nine-Tailed Fox.

After motioning at Jiatai, Garen waited until he went out before picking up the call.

“Hello?”

“Garen, are there any news? About the White Crab Army and Yurijie’s matter, how does the Vulture plan on handling them? What is the stand of the Unrestricted Department?” Nine-Tailed Fox poured out her questions in one go.

Garen was now in a high position, and so Nine-Tailed Fox and the others were far less than him, be it strength or intelligence. This kind of rate of circumstances changing was neither expected by him nor Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest.

“I can’t answer these questions for the time being, because everything is undecided. However, the one thing I can promise you is that I will inform you as soon as there is news,” Garen calmly answered.

“Li Hua has some matter on her side and needs to make a trip to the Black Federation. She will probably need to your help for protection,” Nine-Tailed Fox paused for a bit and continued.

“No problem. I will send someone over and arrange everything. Have her directly contact Kingfisher will do. I will inform in advance,” Garen promised. He did not ask what the matter was. Everyone had their own private affairs, and so there was no need to ask questions and get to the bottom of it.

“This time, we encountered White Crab Army’s ambush shortly after you left. I was seriously injured and am now recuperating, whereas Li Hua and others were alright and only sustained some light injuries. How’s Ah Xue?”

“She’s been rescued. Should be back soon. She had nothing on her, be it a mobile phone and whatnot. I can only wait for her to come back before knowing more. At that time, you can ask her yourself. The Royal Princess Cruise. She’s coming back by ship and will be arriving at the Lily of the Valley tomorrow morning.”

“I understand.” Nine-Tailed Fox was silent for a while. “Regarding the matter the last time, I’m sorry. I was too emotional…”

“It’s nothing.”

Hanging up the phone, Garen was lost in thoughts.

Chapter 1205: Suspicion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few days later…

Garen rinsed off the sweat on his body. He had just come back from the gym and was covered in sweat. Standing in the bathroom, he recalled the matters over these few days. There was a hint of uncertainty in his heart.

Night Water was still under his supervision at the headquarters of the Unrestricted Department. The Unrestricted Department was also known as the Saber Art Department, and there was a small number of men who were once his subordinates from his previous school’s department. Although their strengths were not exceptional, keeping guard of Night Water should not be a problem.

That person’s Soul Energy and strength had been temporarily obliterated by his Quake technique.

Coming out of the bathroom.

He flipped through the few documents that were placed on the table. All that had happened in the last few days were recorded in them.

Yuria had already met with the people he sent over and went to the Forest Capital together to look for his mother, Light Path. At the same time, it was also because he had learned that there was her sister, Yurijie’s trail over there.

‘Kong Xiaofei —— Strength 6.2, Agility 6.2, Vitality 6.1, Intelligence 6.5, Potential 0%. Soul Limit 55.’

‘Potential Quality – Void Pursuer’

‘Soul Ring — The Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique (Blue), the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book (Black-Gold), the Hellfrost Peacock Mother Queen Soul Seed (White), Unknown (transparent)’

‘Unknown Saber Art +1 – Unnamed realm. Effect: all Saber Art moves +1 speed, strength, precision. Produces unknown changes.’

The new Soul Seed had basically been integrated into the Soul Ring, and it had also affected the Soul Limit, successfully improving the ultimate physical fitness by five points.

“It’s no wonder Slayer’s physical fitness is as strong as mine. It is probably because the Soul Limit is extremely terrific. Added with the constant nourishment of Soul Energy, the advancement could be this quick. So, how many are there who are like him? Do all of the Four Great Cornerstones have such a strong physical fitness?”

Garen could not tell. He casually flipped through the documents on the table. Among them were the interrogation reports of Night Water by the Transmigrators, which had been decrypted and could only be understood by him.

The document he picked up clearly recorded the details of the situation of the upper-level in this world.

‘Sacred Sigil Kings – Slayer, Sea God, Sword Master.’

The three were listed in the top three in the document. Among the Four Great Cornerstones, only Slayer could make it to the top three in the combat ability in the entire world.

According to the calculation of the data, the document mentioned that in this world, even the Four Great Cornerstones had to live for a long time to nourish the Soul Energy in order for their physical fitness to reach a very high level. By estimation, Slayer’s physical fitness should have reached the General-level of the Mother Stream System. It was the middle stage of the five levels of Guardian, Division, General, Army, and Demon Lord.

However, taking into consideration that he possessed the Soul Ring, it would equip him with an extremely terrifying development potential. The overall rating was S.

For Sea God, due to his enormous strength and body as well as the cultivation of the Sea-Mirage Breathing Technique, his body’s hardness and strength had reached an incredible level. However, the Soul Energy and the level of the Soul were not high, so one part was strong and another weak. The overall rating was also S-level.

Meanwhile, the Sword Master, who emerged as a powerful genius in less than a year, was of the Mother Stream System. The initial appraisal was that the physical fitness had reached the General-level, and in the battle with Slayer, his strength was even stronger than the other. The overall rating was S-level.

In the document, these three were said to be the top three strongest individuals in combat ability in this world, and an advice was given whereby if a person encountered anyone of them, one should choose to flee the first moment. They belonged to the level of unmatchable.

The second was the Black Federation’s Military Flag, Battle Flag, and the Vulture’s No. 1, No. 2 and so on. Their overall ranking was A-level.

“That’s interesting.” Garen had long accustomed to being in a high position. Regardless of whichever world he had transmigrated to and experienced, he was familiar with this kind of state of being in a high position.

“If I were to judge according to this data document, the ones who can be a threat to me would be Slayer and Sea God. Then, could Sea God be the backer of the White Crab Army?” He rubbed his chin and contemplated.

Putting down the document, he flipped through another one.

This was a detailed survey of the world’s high-level combat power. He himself was included in it. The techniques and Saber Art he had used before were recorded in it with extreme details. Even some subtle little habits he himself did not notice were also recorded in it.

Sea God’s and Slayer’s unique skills were recorded in it as well.

Garen looked through with appreciation. He did not read about Sea God first, focusing instead on Slayer. There was actually a record of him defeating a three-thousand-person mechanized army by himself. It was tremendously savage.

Three thousand people! Even if they were to stand side by side and not resist being slain, one would have to kill until both his arms were feeble. Slayer actually succeeded and was therefore named by each nation’s government as Slayer, becoming the anti-human’s wanted criminal.

The intelligence showed.

The last time Slayer was beleaguered by the three nations, he was injured and had gone missing. There was no news at all until now.

Garen’s mood, which had been relaxed for so long, was again revived with the discovery of the Soul Energy and Soul Seed. Since there were Soul Seeds to be absorbed, this meant that he also had the possibility of progressing even in this world of low-level combat, and so he could not be careless.

Settling down.

He pulled the drawer open. There was a white panel inside with a hundred names densely arranged on it. Some names were glowing, white while some were dark.

However, most of them were bright. In front were tiny ranking numbers.

Garen’s gaze fell straight on the top thirty ranking and was quickly fixed on a name.

He reached out and pressed the name.

“Double-Tailed Scorpion reports to you!” The voice of a woman suddenly traveled out from the name.

“For those who are ranked No. 80 and above, you’re free to choose any five to form a small team to investigate the whereabouts of Illusionist and Mind Reader. Remember to be secretive and try not to be discovered by the other agents from the other two nations. If it is inevitable, try to delay from being discovered as long as possible.”

Garen instructed.

As a Vulture’s higher-up, he had the right to mobilize any person ranked below No. 20 in the Vulture at any time, while there was a certain limit for those above No. 20. For those ranked within No. 10, there would be a need to request from the No. 1 Chief. However, now that No. 1 and No. 2 were not around, naturally he was the one in command.

“Understood. What are the execution time and the final goal?” The woman said decisively.

“One year. You’re required to locate at least the approximate area. Of course, you can choose not to accept this task,” Garen said in a low voice.

There was no immediate reply but a moment of silence. After that, there came the voice again.

“The task reward is?”

“Aren’t you always thinking of retiring? I will make a request to No. 1 and do my best to get you the approval. Of course, this depends on your performance in the task. In addition, another ten million liquidity as the task reward. Is it enough?”

“It is! I accept the task,” Double-Tailed Scorpion replied assertively. In fact, although her identity appeared to be a housewife, she was in effect a beautiful spy with exceptionally strong concealing and disguising ability who had once caused many major incidents one after another in the international arena. Although, no one realized that they were her doings. Her martial power was tremendously powerful. Her right arm, which had been mechanically modified, was nicknamed Kylin Arm. Coupled with the habit of smearing a self-made secret poison on the right arm, she was publicly recognized as the Double-Tailed Scorpion terrorist killer.

Regarding the ability of disguising and assassination, Garen could not beat her no matter how hard he strived to and how strong he was upfront. After all, each person was a master in their own specialized field.

“I’ll be counting on you then,” Garen officially said. His voice was low and filled with a sense of purpose.

Double-Tailed Scorpion instantly had a surge of emotions, and there was a kind of sentiment to serve the country and die for the country without any hesitation.

“I will do my best!”

The communication broke off.

Garen quietly closed the drawer. Yuria the Savior was the key to the Plot and could not be touched. If Slayer’s martial power went off the chart, even if he personally went into battle, it would still be a fifty-fifty chance. Furthermore, Slayer obviously did not exert his full effort that day, so the outcome would still be unknown.

However, the other two Great Cornerstones, who had always been low-key and mysterious, should also have Soul Rings. They could not blame him.

Garen had basically deduced that since Slayer could split the Soul Crystal and Soul Seed this generously, his Soul Energy was clearly far beyond the Soul Crystal. Even if he could not get the Soul Ring, at least it could be a huge replenishment for his Soul Energy, and perhaps he could even enter a higher level of Soul Seed-stage.

“Time to concentrate on more serious things…after playing for so long.” The ease on Garen’s face gradually disappeared, replacing it was a touch of calmness and soberness.

He thought for a moment and directly sent a general geographical scope to Double-Tailed Scorpion. That was the only place which was mentioned in the original Plot where Mind Reader lived. Some of the information regarding Mind Reader’s name, appearances, and features, and so on, were passed to Double-Tailed Scorpion.

*******************

In the midst of the sound of a purling brook, a black stream flowed slowly along the watercourse surrounded by trees and extended toward the distant jungle.

The river was not black, but the mud at the bottom of the river made the river appear to be black when one looked down from the top. The black surface also rippled with the reflection of the surrounding trees. There were a few large trees with their roots deep into the river, surrounded by some sashaying water plants.

The sunset cast its rays down upon the grayish yellow soil by the river.

Crunch.

A small cluster of green grass by the riverside was stamped upon by black leather boots. Yuria squatted down, scooped the river water with both hands and took a mouthful.

“Refreshing!” He shouted.

Two people came from behind. They were wearing tight-fitting white leather clothes, which was very conspicuous in the woods. Moreover, it was a pair of a man and a woman, not over the age of thirty.

“The water here is not polluted. It is absolutely pure mountain spring water, but drink less. Be mindful of stomachaches.” The man wore a white metal sleeve on one ear and had one eye covered with a black eye mask. He was a cyclops.

“I was supposed to go on a holiday to the Basara Island. If it wasn’t for an emergency mobilization order, no one would be willing to come over to assist a rookie like you.” The woman also squatted down and washed her hands with the water.

“Then I really should thank you all,” Yuria said with a glee and was not angry. The current him was no longer the youngster back then. The rich experiences he had garnered led him to understand what kind of attitude was needed under what circumstances and with whom.

Regarding the white man and woman, the male was Egret, while the female was Bat. Both had similarly strengthened the eye, but each had a different division of labor.

“After a day’s journey, how far is it to the destination of Forest Capital?” Egret asked.

Bat looked at the watch.

“About six thousand and four hundred kilometers. Even if our speed reaches the limit, it will still take at least three days to arrive.”

“Why don’t we go by plane?” asked Yuria.

“It’s useless. The route of the plane could be found out too easily, and it will simply expose your whereabouts. The first priority now is to protect you and ensure your safety. This is the task we received. Finding Yurijie is second to that.”

Chapter 1206: Suspicion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Xiaojie…” Yuria was feeling down, yet strangely, he did not seem to be worried. Instead, he had a somewhat eccentric look. After the inexplicable intercourse with that girl, the other party disappeared the next day. No clues were left behind; no name, identity, background and address. Nothing.

However, Yuria kept feeling an abstruse sense of familiarity that caused him to have an indescribable feeling.

“What’s wrong?” Bat’s voice interrupted his thoughts.

“No… Nothing.” Yuria’s mind came back. Recalling the madness of that night, he was still feeling somewhat intoxicated.

The three continued on their way.

Riding their respective heavy-duty motorcycles, the days passed quickly in their stop-and-go journey.

( )  The Forest Capital finally appeared before them.

The vehicles on the roadside were increasing in numbers, passing by them. As they journeyed on, the traffic was getting heavier, the road was getting more spacious, and the trees on both sides were getting taller and taller, changing from originally-curved, mid-short trees to tall and huge ones.

Standing in the woods, one could only see trees that were as straight as a bamboo planted into the ground.

The name of the Forest Capital was pleasant to the ear, but it was actually an ordinary small town built in a sea of trees. It was a famous tourist destination in Slann, so there were a lot of tourists.

The three left their motorcycles with a car dealer, paid some money, and began strolling on the street of the Forest Capital.

The street was spacious and bright, paved with white slates. The black, old small houses on both sides were shops that were open. There were also rows of simple stalls outside of the shops selling all kinds of messy specialties.

Bat took the lead and walked straight to the Vulture’s intelligence contact point here, whereas Egret followed from behind. His primary mission was to protect Yuria.

Yuria was looking around absentmindedly and seeking who-knows-what.

Boom.

Suddenly, a man clothed in black collided with his shoulder.

“I’m sorry.” Yuria’s mind quickly came back into focus and saw the other party holding the shoulder and frowning.

“Got no eyes to see where you’re going?!” The man vented under his breath. However, when he saw Egret approaching from the side, his expression suddenly changed, and he quickly left.

Yuria still wanted to apologize, yet he found that the other party had gone far off and mingled into the crowd. He smiled wryly and shook his head.

He reached into the pocket of his trousers, and his face changed slightly all of a sudden. He looked down, and his face returned to normal. It so happened that Egret had turned his head around and was staring at the man in black, so he did not notice his oddness.

“What’s wrong? Being dreamy on the street.”

“Nothing…” Yuria shook his head with a smile.

“That’s good then.” Egret turned around and walked in front to open the way. The crowd was getting more packed.

Taking advantage of the moment where Egret’s back was facing him and not paying attention to him.

Yuria lowered his head and took out a small slip of paper from his trouser pocket and unfolded it. There was a small line of words on it.

‘Be careful of the people around you. ‘

He quickly stuffed the slip of paper into his trouser pocket and looked around, not finding the trail of the man from just now. This matter came to an end, but it caused Yuria to keep a watchful eye.

In the evening, after the people from Vulture had arranged their accommodation, the three each went to bed while they waited for the intelligence personnel here to respond with the news about Yurijie and his mother, Light Path.

The intelligence personnel here would only deliver the news to the points at a fixed time.

Soon, the intelligence personnel had specific information.

Someone found some clues near the Forest Capital.

The three rushed over.

*********************

In the jungle, the grayish-black ground was covered with a white cloth. There seemed to be a human corpse lying underneath it. There was a stench in the surrounding area. No one knew how long the body had died.

The fresh air from the morning was completely contaminated by the smell of the corpse.

The trio of Yuria, Bat, and Egret knelt beside the corpse, opened up the white cloth, and carefully examined the condition of the body. The surrounding was cordoned off with warning lines. More than a dozen policemen gathered around the periphery to wait for the result.

“It’s a male, between the age of thirty and forty-five, bald, dressed in black, without any identification on his body. The muscle fiber tissue indicates that he always trains, and it is not a simple strength training exercise, but more like mixed combat…” Bat explained in a small voice. She was an expert in this area.

Egret listened carefully, but Yuria’s pupils constricted the moment he saw the face of this corpse. The corpse was the man in black who had given him the note when he first arrived here.

He recalled this scene which had also happened back then. It was also someone stuffing him a note, asking him not to waste his effort and to quickly return and assemble.

Return and assemble? Assemble what? Why asked him not to waste his effort?

And now, this person told him that there was someone suspicious around him. ‘Be careful of the people around you’. This sentence could have two meanings. One could refer to the people who were around him, and the other would be the people who were close to him.

He did not know which one the other party was referring to. Thinking of this, he unconsciously tightened his grip on the saber in his hand.

And now, the other party had died just like that.

Yuria remembered very clearly that this person was definitely the man in black who had stuffed him the note.

“There’s a discovery!” Bat suddenly made a slight exclamation of surprise. She used a tweezer to retrieve a small electronic chip underneath the skin of the man in black’s arm. It was black and seemed to be made of some kind of alloy.

“Check it out and analyze the structure. This kind of standard chip is one of the common formats.” Bat handed it over to Egret, who was an expert in this area.

Egret quickly took out a special watch-like instrument, wiped the chip clean, and inserted it in. Very soon, the information was known.

“This is a position-tracking chip!” He exclaimed in surprise.

“What position?”

Bang!

Suddenly, the police officers in the vicinity were swallowed up by a violent explosion of flames. Small missiles were fired from the distance, and the police car and police officers were swept off the ground due to the explosion as they were caught off guard.

Red and golden-yellow fire ignited the nearby meadows and bushes, and the blaze suddenly spread out, emitting billows of white smoke.

The trio was jerked by the impact of the explosion, and they crouched down to avoid the shock waves.

Some of the police officers who reacted slower were directly blown into the air by the shockwave and thrown out far away. Dead or alive, no one knew.

Boom boom boom boom!

In the continuous explosions, not a single missile was fired at the position of the trio, but the surrounding positions were all blown up. Obviously, this was done deliberately by the attacker.

Some of the police officers died while some were unconscious. The entire site was completely cleared out.

In the blaze, a figure up to three meters tall was treading heavily step by step toward the trio, totally not afraid of the surrounding flames at all.

“It’s you again!” Yuria’s face turned savage the moment he could see the figure clearly. “Where’s Xiaojie!? What did you do to Xiaojie!?”

He bellowed.

The figure came out of the fire and gradually became clear.

It was a black robot with a height of three meters. Its head was triangular, and its chest was engraved with a strange pattern of a white crab. The whole body was like a stone pillar supporting a house, thick and strong. The entire skin was covered with a dull kind of pattern, and at first glance, one knew that it was extremely heavy and tough.

It had a round firing port on each of its arms. At this moment, they were still slowly releasing white smoke. The edges were slightly red, and the temperature was terribly high. Obviously, the missiles earlier on were fired by it.

“If you want to see your sister, then come with me… Savior.” The robot had a deep and thick voice.

“Don’t listen to him!” Egret shouted loudly. One of his hand suddenly stretched out and turned into an exceptionally sharp double-edged triangular knife with a brilliant red fire. “This fellow is from the White Crab Army. They have just attacked your friends, Nine-Tailed and others!”

“Heh.” The robot’s actions immediately became faster. Its arm aimed downward as it opened fire and shot out a missile. It was only when it almost reached Egret did he hurriedly react.

Boom!

Egret awkwardly rolled to one side and barely dodged the attack. His legs stomped the ground, and he blasted off, charging straight at the robot from another angle.

Meanwhile, Bat rolled aside and opened her mouth to make a silent angry roar at the robot.

A burst of invisible interference sound waves instantly caused the robot to sway a little.

The two were the powerhouses ranked high up in the Vulture. Naturally, they would not be defeated that easily.

Yuria quickly separated from the two’s position and avoided the flames. Pulling out his long saber, he sneaked to the back of the robot. Regardless of whether the robot was telling the truth or not, defeat the other party first before saying anything else.

The robot sneered.

“Even if you are the strongest players in the Vulture, or even if the Sword Master is present, it won’t matter to me at all. Not to mention the crap that are you guys, who are not even in the top ten!”

Boom!

A clear shockwave erupted from its body and spread out violently into the surrounding, immediately dissolving Bat’s sound wave and hampering Egret’s sprint. In contrast, Yuria was slightly stronger as his Savior’s special ability was engaged. His entire skin turned red, and his speed and explosive force were a level greater.

“Forewind!”

Whoosh!

A silver light shone, and the distance between the robot and Yuria was promptly shortened.

**********************

Red Nation

The Protestant Headquarters in the province of Aix, on the street of a village on the outskirts.

Black cars slowly entered this remote small village.

These black cars gradually stopped in front of a little wooden, brown-red house. A white street lamp was erected in front of the house, giving out a faint white light in the night. Coupled with the white floor lamps inlaid between the slates on the nearby ground, they constituted the only light source in the vicinity.

A woman got down from the black car at the front.

“It’s here.” She had a high ponytail, and the silver hair was swaying slightly to the left with the wind. She was tall and had a wheat-colored complexion. Wearing a green tube top and denim shorts, she gave off a kind of vigorous, graceful and explosive sensation.

“As the Four Great Cornerstones, he actually attempts to live the life of an ordinary person. How foolish.” Another androgynous man with a heavy makeup exited the car, making an orchid finger gesture (TN: a Chinese term referring to a hand gesture where the middle-finger touches the thumb. It is considered a feminine sign; https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/蘭花指) and fixing his gaze on the wooden house in front.

“The rest of the people, get off,” The woman spoke in a low voice.

All the car doors were opened at once, and waves of well-trained personnel dressed in black uniforms began evacuating the onlookers nearby. They quickly pulled the security department’s warning line across and completely cordoned off the few hundred meters area around into a restricted area.

“Here is Red Nation. Resolve it within ten minutes.” The woman strode to the wooden house and kicked aside the fence outside the wooden house.

If the intelligence was correct, Mind Reader should not be fully awakened at this time, which would make the capture absolutely easy.

Chapter 1207: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The room door was kicked open violently with a bang.

There was a drowsy man inside the room dressed in pajamas. He was carrying a hammer for reasons unknown while a little boy, who could not be older than seven or eight years old, hid behind him.

“Who are you?!” When the man saw the staff members dressed in neat, standardized black uniforms charging in, a frightened look appeared on his face suddenly.

“Take him away.” The woman waved her hand before several ferocious-looking burly fellows seized the man and the boy.

Bang!

A gunshot noise rang out suddenly before the two men who rushed over earlier fell to the ground at the sound of it. The man swayed slightly when they collided against him while an obvious sign of mortal danger flashed across his head instantly.

“There’s a sniper! Hide!” Fear instilled the woman’s mind immediately. She yelled and pulled out a gun before somersaulting away as two more bullet holes instantly appeared on the initial spot where she stood. They penetrated the wooden planks on the floor deeply.

Bang bang bang! A series of frenzied gunshot noises echoed in succession from the outside, as the Vulture members in black uniforms counterattacked quickly.

“My Lord had actually anticipated this!” Double-Tailed Scorpion’s face turned cold before a bullet made a hissing noise and hit the Mind Reader’s right thigh.

Blood splattered instantly.

“Stop immediately! Otherwise, I’ll kill him!!” Double-tailed Scorpion roared suddenly.

Suddenly, the gunshot noises and the blood-curdling screams of the people in black uniforms outside ceased rapidly. It was obvious that the other party was extremely anxious as well because she was afraid that she would also kill Mind Reader during this deadly situation. Although any one of the Four Great Cornerstones could revive themselves within a year, it would be extremely difficult to even dream of grasping their whereabouts so easily again.

Double-Tailed Scorpion straightened her body slowly and looked at the man and boy who were both trembling from head to toe. Her expression turned colder as she leaned closely against the wall, moving slowly while walking towards the doorway and glancing outside slightly.

More than ten people were brought over this time, standing on the empty space outside.

“Damn!”

She could not help but curse.

She had brought over twenty members with her this time, but more than half of them had been slaughtered immediately.

“Come with me!” She walked beside Mind Reader speedily before reaching her hand out to clutch his neck suddenly.

Shh!

A shroud of cold air surged out of her vest suddenly. Double-Tailed Scorpion had no time to think before her body crouched downwards violently. She released her grip on Mind Reader before turning her hand over and shooting.

Bang!

A woman’s low groan echoed behind her instantly. Double-Tailed Scorpion rolled away to dodge the cold current before turning back and noticing that a short, glittering silver dagger had accurately penetrated the spot that she was just standing on.

“Go!” The woman’s cold voice rang out before Mind Reader carried his son away. His speed increased rapidly as he charged out of the room instantly.

Bang!

The sniper rifle sounded again.

Double-Tailed Scorpion was just getting ready to stand up and chase after them before her body slanted suddenly while her arm ached in a fiery pain. She was almost fatally shot. A large chunk of flesh was directly removed from her right arm.

“Shit! If only the Elites hadn’t scattered themselves to search everywhere!” The higher-ranked powerhouses of her main elite force were dispersed throughout the outskirts to search the entire area. If her manpower was focused in one place, the sniper would not have a chance to act so brazenly at all.

Double-Tailed Scorpion stared blankly as Mind Reader escaped. Meanwhile, her right leg stopped moving slightly when she stepped on the ground lightly.

Bang bang bang!

Three consecutive gunshot noises could be heard when she fired three shots towards her right instantly. All three shots struck the same area and formed one bullet hole. The bullets flew upwards toward a slant. The sniper’s rifle turned silent suddenly.

Several years worth of instincts told Double-Tailed Scorpion that her opponent had been shot.

Currently, Mind Reader had already run across a great distance and disappeared at a street corner after making a turn. Meanwhile, Double-Tailed Scorpion’s subordinates who were hiding earlier had yet to respond, they were now looking on as she charged out of the house.

“Go! We can’t let them escape!” Double-Tailed Scorpion had a fierce expression on her face. This was a key factor that was related to whether she could retire successfully! She would not tolerate failure at all!

During the instantaneous battle earlier, she could sense that, if she was aware of the sniper earlier, she could have used her modified detection abilities to locate them and kill her opponent easily even if the other party was hidden while she was exposed. Unfortunately, it was too sudden!

Several of the people in black clothes separated themselves from the group immediately to pursue Mind Reader, while two of them stayed behind to get rid of the corpses.

********************

“Someone rescued him?”

Garen furrowed his eyebrows while standing on top of the skyscraper. The cool night breeze blew his hair and lifted it slightly, giving him a free and relaxed feeling. However, his current mood was far from being relaxed or happy.

“Someone who could seize another person from your hands must have been pretty skillful. Do you know where they were from?” He clutched the railing behind him that fenced the top of the building while leaning against it closely.

Double-Tailed Scorpion stood there and gritted her teeth while speaking.

“Don’t worry, I’ve already sent my brothers to seize them. We won’t let anyone escape. White Hound has followed me out this time as well.”

“I’m not worried about his tracking abilities. However, what are the opponent’s powers like?” Garen asked in a muffled voice.

“Other than the sniper who was more experienced, the other female talent was only average. As long as we find an opportunity to stop them, the sniper won’t have any chance to escape!” Double-Tailed Scorpion felt that this was the most humiliating experience in her life!

“My Lord, if I may put it bluntly, there are definitely spies within the team. Otherwise, they couldn’t have determined our location beforehand and ambushed us even though I had already dispersed the teams to search everywhere! This is unrealistic!” Double-Tailed Scorpion said coldly.

“I’ve requested for the assistance of the Lan Hai, the psychologist.”

“Lan Hai?” Garen’s eyebrows were slightly furrowed. Lan Hai was ranked at number twenty-six in Vulture. Neither his close nor distant combat abilities were extraordinarily powerful. However, his greatest weapon was not his combat skills but instead, his mind and strategies. He would consider his enemies while strengthening his own side simultaneously.

“Are you sure that you don’t need any other support?” He repeated.

“I don’t need it! As long as Lan Hai comes along, there won’t be any problems at all! I was attacked to the point where I could not react promptly this time. Moreover, since the Elites were not by my side, it would be impossible that accidents would not occur,” said Double-Tailed Scorpion firmly.

The results of her quest assessment would determine whether she could retire this time. According to the rules, once an individual had requested for the support of more than two ranked powerhouses, the quest would not be considered as an individual quest anymore. Even if it was completed, the quest reward would be decreased by 80%.

“I’ll give you five days,” said Garen indifferently.

“Five days… Understood! I will definitely complete this quest!” Double-Tailed Scorpion replied resolutely.

Garen ended the call before gazing out at the night-time scenery of the faraway Lily of the Valley. His emotions were somewhat complicated.

“Spies? Ha… It seems the Transmigrator organization Lighthouse has various selfish motives as well…”

Other than the Transmigrators, it was highly unlikely that anyone else could find Mind Reader before his identity was revealed.

He placed the incident aside for now as he was probably waiting for the right moment. Once Mind Reader was fully aware of his abilities, he would undertake the task resolutely to reproduce the Sacred Sigil. However, no one had expected Garen to openly dispatch troops and seize him forcibly.

“If another Transmigrator the combat abilities of the Nine-tailed Fox arrives, everything would definitely become more troublesome.”

Garen pondered for some time.

He descended the stairs hastily and returned to his office. He opened a drawer and looked at several rows of names there that were illuminated with white light.

There were fifteen people among the top twenty ranks that were illuminated with the white light. This indicated that they were unoccupied.

Garen glanced through a circle of names before pausing on one person’s name quickly.

Butcher Angelo. Rank eleven.

Those who were ranked in the top ten were ultimate combat forces who could defend a large province because they were extremely fierce and tough. Despite the standard of their danger level that was given to them by Night Water, Garen guessed that those who were ranked within the top ten had achieved A-Class levels. The only difference between them was their relative superiority or inferiority within the A-Class.

The subordinates of powerhouses like these could form powerful Elite groups of various sizes. Nonetheless, there were also rebellious but influential forces throughout the entire Slann.

However, Butcher was an exception. He was the only one whose actual strength could reach the top ten. However, since his influence was not strong enough, he could not become one of the top ten powerhouses.

Eighty percent of his entire body was modified into machinery installations, making him comparable to the Terminator in the movies on Earth. Moreover, his personality was violent and bloodthirsty and he had an affinity for the strongest defenses and armor. His own defensive ability was considered to be among the top ten while there were only two others who could compare to him.

He pressed the name lightly.

Garen straightened out his emotions briefly.

“Angelo, do you want to accept this quest?”

“It’s No. 3, huh?” A rude male voice echoed from the other side. “If you have something to say, say it quickly. I’m planning to go fishing right now.” He was not talking about literally going fishing but was referring to a deadly underground battle arena instead.

Butcher was not very respectful toward Garen. In his eyes, having a little worm like him, who was not even ranked among the top twenty yet had the audacity to crawl on his head, was equivalent to the greatest insult to him.

However, after being easily defeated by Garen during several challenges, he could at least remain respectful towards Garen on the surface despite still being unconvinced. After all, the other party had cut one of his legs off cleanly. Subsequently, he could only substitute it with a prosthetic limb. Crushing defeats like this would be etched in his memory for a lifetime.

“Double-Tailed Scorpion was obstructed by someone else when she was hunting an important figure. Her opponent is an extremely troublesome individual who might possess a more familiar understanding of you and Double-Tailed Scorpion’s abilities. Moreover, they are already very familiar with Vulture. Hence, I thought of hiring you this time…”

“Enough with this nonsense! What’s the reward?!” said Butcher impatiently.

Garen smiled faintly.

“The reward will definitely satisfy you.” He paused on purpose before continuing. “Weren’t you thinking of purchasing one of Casla’s hydropower stations? I can help you.”

“…” Butcher did not reply immediately but his breathing had clearly become much heavier.

“Are you serious?!” He lowered his voice instantly.

The price of that hydropower station was secondary while the primary factor was that its background relations were very intricate. They were related to one of Butcher’s previous great enemies and his own revenge plan as well. Therefore, he could not help himself from being perturbed.

This was because, once Garen made a move, his identity and status as No. 3 would perhaps end up helping Butcher’s enemy, despite his potential influence not being exceptionally great.

“I’m serious,” Garen said flatly, although his actions would cause him to suffer some losses in his social connections. However, it did not matter. The heart of this matter was the strengthening of the Soul Ring while everything else could be put aside.

If he was not too busy to attend to anything else because he had to control the overall situation now, he had actually planned to take charge of this matter personally.

“Alright then! I’ll accept this quest!” said Butcher decisively. He began to inquire about the specific objectives, relevant information, and other news immediately.

Despite being a loner, he had his own circle of social connections. Thus, he quickly arranged everything properly before Garen turned off the communication connection.

“The only thing that I have to do now is to wait.” He sat on the chair while the corner of his mouth curled upwards slightly.

Butcher moved out and so did Double-Tailed Scorpion. Unless Nine-tailed Fox or another powerhouse of the same level went up against them, it would be unlikely that anyone else could resist them.

Moreover, since Nine-tailed Fox’s current whereabouts were within his grasp, it would be impossible for her to rush over.

He was only worried about the other Transmigrators. However, how many other powerhouses, who were of the same level as Nine-tailed Fox, were there?

Chapter 1208: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clang!

Yuria held a long saber and struck the robot’s arm in one go. Among the two of them, one was larger while the other was smaller. Their forces pressed against one another and collided violently. Despite only being slightly inferior to the robot, Yuria was sent flying for several meters before he landed on the ground lightly.

Within the forest, both of them resumed their confrontation once again, as sweat trickled down from Yuria’s sideburns endlessly.

His current strength could already be compared to Garen’s in his regular condition. However, the fellow on the opposite side of him had actually almost rendered him helpless.

When the robot was defending itself, Yuria’s saber could neither cut it nor pierce inwards. Meanwhile, every time the robot simply waved its hand when it attacked, Yuria needed to block its explosive force with all of his strength. Moreover, it was possible that he would suffer a fracture directly if he was even slightly distracted.

Just like the two other people who were lying on the side.

Bat and Egret were leaning closely against the bottom of a tree on the side. Both of them had suffered broken limbs that made it difficult for them to move. They could only stare blankly while Yuria and the robot fought directly.

Three days had passed since they encountered the robot. Within these three days, it seemed as though their opponent was murderously pursuing them unceasingly without any intention of showing mercy. Moreover, he did not have any worries about his own safety or mortality like normal people, instead, it acted unscrupulously.

“We’ve already requested for backup! Hold on!” Egret said while gritting his teeth. He was using both of his hands to assemble a thin, skateboard-like thing in an experienced manner. It seemed like some sort of transportation tool. They relied on these playthings to escape the robot’s murderous pursuit during these past few days.

Yuria did not reply. He pounced on the robot again and fought messily with it instead. The body of his saber struck various parts of the robot’s body continuously. It even left cracks on certain parts of its body but they were unfortunately ineffective. Even the connected parts inside the cracks remained unusually solid as there was an internal protective layer.

Hydra!

He suddenly released this ability quietly before the robot’s speed decreased instantly while his own speed increased abruptly.

Clang clang clang clang!

Four consecutive noises could be heard when his blade hit the same part of the robot’s nape suddenly.

Shh!

A thin crack appeared on the robot’s neck. The great impact force shook his body and forced him to take two steps backward.

“Fine!” It was apparently completely unconcerned about its own injuries. It joined both of its arms in the middle and attempted to grab Yuria’s waist firmly when Yuria was striking it rapidly. The robot tried to hold him tightly the same way a man would embrace a woman around her waist.

However, the Hydra’s abilities had absorbed the robot’s speed to strengthen Yuria instead, allowing his current speed to greatly surpassed his expectations. He recoiled his body and evaded capture immediately after he finished striking before his blade pierced the robot’s abdomen again. He used all of the strength in his body when he stabbed it. His skin reddened when he used all of the strength that he had borrowed from everyone else through the Savior’s special ability.

“Single Person’s Strength.”

Yuria turned around and spun rapidly while his blade rotated speedily like a deadly tornado.

Shh shh shh shh!

Endless cutting noises rang out from the robot’s body.

“Dragon Spine Leap.” The robot’s right arm pressed downwards firmly before a vaporous shroud of driving force exploded from its right shoulder suddenly. The robot increased the speed of its arm’s movements quickly while moving it downwards. The speed of its entire robotic arm instantly shot up several times while it came right in Yuria’s face to oppress him.

“Upwards!”

Yuria’s spinning sword move condensed into one movement suddenly before moving upwards.

Clank!

The blade and the robotic arm clashed violently. There was a brief clashing noise before the blade broke immediately and bounced away quickly.

Yuria’s expression changed and he retreated quickly. However, he had failed to react in time now. The explosion of the vapor increased the speed of the robot’s arm and allowed it to crash forward violently.

Bang!

He suffered a direct hit to his chest. A series of bone-breaking noises could be heard while Yuria was sent flying far away.

“Go!” Egret had finished making the skateboard some time ago. He brought Bat with him to pick Yuria up from afar before escaping into the distance speedily without even turning back.

Along the way, light traces of blood that were left behind on the grass could be seen faintly.

Bat could see the robot catching up to them quickly. “Its long-range attack measures have been exhausted, so there should be no problem as long as it doesn’t close the distance between us. Are you alright, Yuria?”

“I’m fine!” Yuria answered while his complexion turned paler. He spat out a mouthful of blood just as he finished speaking.

“This thing has the same strength as those in the top ten, at the very least! Although my injuries have healed perfectly, I couldn’t unleash the Savior’s power to its full potential, instead, I could only use the Single Person’s Strength. It was so strong that my body couldn’t take it.”

“Don’t worry, I’ve already requested for backup so the powerhouses will be arriving soon. We just need to stall for some time and we’ll be fine,” said Egret hastily.

“Here! Here!” A series of frantic shouts echoed from the front suddenly.

Joyful looks appeared on Egret and Bat’s faces instantly. “They’re here!”

The trio rode the skateboard forward quickly and weaved through the forest. Soon, they saw a group of people in black clothes in front of them who were getting down from black motorcycles. One of them, who was leading the group, wore half of a golden mask that covered the left side of their face.

This person was actually a woman. There were several people behind her who were assembling a certain weapon for her now. That weapon looked like a longer and thicker version of a super sniper rifle.

The body of the entire rifle was silvery white; it almost resembled a small-scale cannon.

“Duck!”

The woman took the weapon and carried it on her shoulder before aiming it at Yuria and the other two people accurately.

The three of them immediately lowered their heads as much as they could.

Boom!

They merely heard a dull, thunderclap-like roar above their heads before the trio’s ears were completely muffled at once. They could not hear anything and could only feel their entire bodies turn numb while their ears were filled with a series of chaotic humming noises.

Boom!

They felt intense light and heat behind them instantly. Another violent shock wave shook the trio vigorously, making them fall off the skateboard. Fortunately, they were carefully caught by the soft net that was prepared by the people in black earlier.

The woman in black put the gigantic gun down and looked at the depths of the forest from afar where flames were soaring into the sky.

“We’ll use carpet bombing. Dispatch the Falcons.”

“Understood.”

“Request for Falcon Bombing.”

The person behind her relayed the command quickly.

The shrill noise of bombers echoed above the heads of the crowd instantly. Numerous white lines whizzed through the sky before exploding in the center of the large fire. The violent explosions piled up on each other vigorously before the flames and smoke dispersed. The surroundings of the forest were almost completely covered in flames, making it difficult for anything to be seen clearly.

“Is it dead?” The woman asked quietly.

“Its ideal radioactive energy level has decreased by more than forty percent. It’s currently retreating and has probably fled temporarily,” answered one of the subordinates behind her quietly while he was looking at a scanning device on his arm.

“Pursue and kill it with another round of carpet bombing! Destroy it.” The woman dangled a cigarette in her mouth gently before lighting it and taking a puff. Next, she held it with her fingers and removed it before shifting her attention towards Yuria and the other two people.

“Egret, long time no see. You look like you’re in a sorry state, huh.” The woman’s laughter echoed behind the mask.

“Big Sister!” Egret was standing up while being supported by someone else. He was too weak to stand because of his fractured leg. Thus, he could only lean on his other leg to support himself while standing on the ground. “It’s a good thing that you came over this time. Otherwise, we would be in deep trouble a little while longer.”

“Your opponent is one of White Whale’s people. Our superiors allowed us to wait for you nearby earlier. I didn’t expect to actually be sent to the battlefield.” The masked woman was ranked eighth in Vulture and she was an expert in long distance indiscriminate firing. The previous explosions were not simply normal serial bombings. In reality, each target was controlled by the masked woman. She could even determine each of the bombing targets and make sure that continuous strikes were aimed at the same target while her opponent was sent flying and bouncing off due to the explosion. That one specific target was the crack in the robot’s nape that was carved out by Yuria’s saber earlier.

“We’ve already reached the first steps of determining the identity of the opponent,” said the woman calmly, “the business alliance has already released the official command to arrest the White Crab Army.”

“White Crab Army?!” Yuria stood up despite the pain throughout his entire body. When he was violently hit earlier, his internal organs were shaken up and would not heal in less than one and a half hours.

“How did you manage to hear about them prior to this?” The woman asked while looking at him.

“Be careful!” Yuria pounced forward suddenly and collided against the masked woman violently.

Simultaneously, a spot of silver light hissed and passed through the initial position of the masked woman’s head while releasing an ear-piercing screech.

The silver light hit the head of one of the subordinates behind the woman directly. There was a popping noise before that person’s brain exploded and bits of red and white splattered everywhere.

Without having to wait for any shouts or orders, everyone returned fire immediately because they were ultimately the Elites. More than ten grenades flew out and fell in the direction where the silver light was being shot.

Bang bang bang bang!

Exploding noises echoed unceasingly while bullets made clanging noises, striking the metallic ground as if they were being defiantly blocked by something.

Yuria supported the woman slowly and helped her crawl back up.

“Thanks!” The woman’s face was solemn. “I owe you my life.”

“That won’t be necessary! You came here to support us anyway.” Yuria turned around and looked in the direction from which the silver light was being fired.

Within the raging fire and smoke, a gigantic body that was three meters tall walked out of the burning flames slowly. It was the robot from earlier!

Its body was larger and heavier now as if it was twice as broad as its initial size. A gash that resembled an eye had split open in the center of the robot’s body. This opening was filled with little eyes that were blinking with specks of green light.

There was previously a large hole in the area where the robot was injured. However, only a thin white scar remained there after the robot had healed itself speedily now.

“It’s useless. Unless you’re one of the top five powerhouses, the rest of you don’t even have the right to stand before me.” The robot’s deep voice echoed through the forest. It was tinged with the intense, static-like noises of everything that was burning.

“Threefold Super Electromagnetism.” The masked woman’s face turned colder while she carried the gun.

Bang!

A white light pillar lit up suddenly and hit the center of the robot’s chest at a speed that was faster than lightning.

Unexpectedly, the robot managed to grab the light pillar single-handedly. It held it in its palm tightly. The light beam remained in the robot’s palm for a few good seconds before it disappeared.

Shrouds of white smoke were escaping from the robot’s palm now. It was also slightly red and appeared to be at a very high, burning temperature.

“It ends now.” The robot smiled viciously before its large and heavy body exploded from the back suddenly, turning it into a great driving force that rushed violently toward Yuria and the two others who were gravely injured.

Whoosh!

The silver light flashed. At that moment, Yuria removed the body of a gleaming, slender silver saber from behind himself.

It was merely a normal saber, yet he used it to strike the robot’s body.

Boom!

There was a thunderclap-like noise before intense metallic fireworks exploded violently when the blade clashed against the metallic outer shell of the robot’s body.

It seemed as though the robot had suffered a lightning strike throughout its entire body. The robot flew backward like a cannonball while humming noises echoed from the inside of its body. The noises resembled a large clanging bell with sound waves that reverberated and surged through the insides of its body endlessly.

Ahh!

The robot let out an anguished scream while its body flipped over in the sky quickly. Flames spluttered from the boost motor on its back as it fled into the distance.

Chapter 1209: Gather 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A silhouette made a brief whooshing noise as it brushed the ears of Yuria and the other two people. It was faster than a supersonic fighter plane. It caught up to the robot in the blink of an eye before striking it with another normal slaying assault.

Boom!

The robot moved directly downward when it was smashed into the ground violently. The vibrations caused the surrounding flames and smoke to travel out of the large hole on the ground immediately before the fiery blaze was instantly extinguished by the intense tremors. Endless clouds of smoke exploded everywhere as if another new explosion had burst forth.

A black silhouette was standing beside the large pit where the robot was lying. It was carrying a long saber that was more than two meters long backward while gazing into the bottom of the pit quietly.

Shh!

The robot burst out of the depths of the pit suddenly. It charged towards the silhouette vigorously with its weight and tremendous impact force.

Clang!

The silhouette simply moved its saber once.

A crashing noise could be heard. That saber did not merely resemble a saber anymore. Instead, it was practically a Super Iron Hammer. It struck the robot’s body firmly and sent it flying suddenly. The robot flew sideways and hit more than ten large trees, felling them down in the process. It was barely able to bump against the front of one tree trunk and turn around before crouching on the ground.

“Ahh… Ahh!” the robot yelled furiously.

It suddenly realized that another silhouette had appeared before itself now.

“You!” It raised its head and was about to speak.

Bang!

The long saber struck the robot violently like a whip and sent it flying before it somersaulted more than ten meters away. The robot’s entire body was clearly badly damaged now. There were large wounds everywhere that were dripping with silver liquid while eighty percent of its outer shell was covered in various scars.

“Ga… Garen!” The robot seemed weaker now. It seemed like its vocal chord was damaged in the fight as well because it was making strange overlapping noises. “Weren’t you supposed to be in… the Red Nation?! How is this… possible?!!”

The silhouette appeared before the robot again but did not dash toward its opponent this time.

“The Red Nation? It looks like someone’s been tipping you off.” Garen’s expression was calm. Numerous shrouds of Soul Energy Aura were leaking from the robot in front of him, making it obvious that it possessed Slayer’s Forged Sacred Sigil as well.

Clap!

He reached out and grabbed the robot’s neck immediately. He lifted it straight upwards and raised it in mid-air.

Now that he had absorbed the Soul Seed’s Soul Energy, his qualities had equally broken through the six-point mark recently. This allowed him to achieve an average standard of seven points. He was already upgraded into a terrifying realm now. Even though the robot weighed over a thousand kilograms, it did not affect him at all.

“Who is the mastermind behind the White Crab Army? Tell me.” Garen suspended the long saber before the robot’s chest directly. The tip of the blade was aimed precisely at the robot’s chest. If Garen willed it, he could turn the robot into a barbecued skewer instantly.

“Hahaha…” sneered the robot. “You won’t find out… You’ll never find out… Oh!”

He stabbed the saber straight into the robot’s chest.

The robot’s body lit up in red quickly as if he could explode at any moment. However, it jolted after being extinguished by a strange liquid immediately. It seemed like cold water had been poured on fiery red charcoal before the robot’s entire body cooled down rapidly.

Both of the robot’s eyes became dimmer instantly.

Not far away, Yuria stared blankly at Garen. This was an unprecedented incident and the very first time he had truly seen Garen attack at full throttle. He had initially assumed that the disparity between them was not that far anymore. However, when he looked at it now, that guy was simply a frightening existence that could rip dinosaurs apart bare-handedly!

He did not require any martial arts moves. Instead, a mere hit from his saber allowed him to pound a person to death with nothing but brute force. Wasn’t that how he killed the robot earlier?!

“It’s truly… too insane!” said Yuria softly, unable to suppress a surge of emotion.

Egret and Bat were frantically dripping with cold sweat on the sidelines. They nodded in agreement continuously. They could not distinguish whether the sweat was caused by the pain of their injuries or being shocked by Garen.

The woman in the silver mask was much calmer. She took long strides and walked over.

“Minister, it’s fortunate that you arrived in time. This robot’s strength is equivalent to the top five levels. If you had not rushed here in time, we were afraid that we could only withdraw much earlier.”

Garen sheathed his saber and nodded to indicate his response.

“The White Crab Army’s technology has surpassed our expectations. Yuria, you must be careful. I merely attacked them while they were caught unaware this time. A robot like this would definitely cost a lot and I’m sure that the loss of one robot would be an extremely serious matter to them. Thus, you pay more attention to your safety when you confront them again next time.”

Yuria let out a deep breath.

“Don’t tell me you’re saying that they have more than one of these deviants?!” When he thought of the overpowered state of the previous robot, his heart trembled faintly. No matter how he hit or cut it, his saber was useless to the point that it broke.

“Of course,” Garen said certainly, “I have another matter to attend to so I won’t be able to be by your side as I wish. Therefore, you can only depend on yourself for everything else. Judging from your opponent’s intentions, your sister is probably safe. Moreover, they don’t seem to harbor any murderous intentions towards you, so you don’t have to worry about that either.”

“Is that so?” Yuria recalled the scenes that had occurred previously. Indeed, even though he had fainted because of his serious injuries, the robot did not take the opportunity to kill him at that time.

Garen looked at this important figure in the Plot while his hand started searching for something on the robot’s body again. He took something out from the injury in its chest.

It was actually a glittering and translucent hexagonal crystal jewel.

“One Soul Crystal has been obtained.”

Garen began to absorb its Soul Energy swiftly.

The Soul Energy of one Soul Crystal was equivalent to one-third of the lowest-valued Soul Seed. Absorbing three of these crystals would allow the average qualities of his body to be upgraded by one point quickly. This was the best type of nourishment or growth-enhancing substance for Garen. Moreover, it would produce excellent replenishing effects for his Soul Ring as well.

As long as he upgraded himself and achieved the Five-Soul-Seeded Soul Ring Phase, he would enter the next stage and obtain new increments of his Soul Energy. Garen had deduced a specific situation that would occur at that time. His Soul Energy would probably become even purer while his own upgrades would happen quicker as well. Simultaneously, the Soul Seed’s special abilities would progressively begin to appear too.

***********************

Two months later…

“We’ve lost control of the Plot.”

Nine-Tailed Fox had recovered from her injuries. The first sentence that came out of her mouth when she arrived at Garen’s office was a serious question.

“What do you mean?” Garen was currently pouring tea for two people. When he heard this, his movements unconsciously slowed down faintly. “Wasn’t Yuria just fine?”

“It’s not him. Rather, Mind Reader who was supposed to appear did not appear according to the Plot,” said Nine-Tailed Fox sternly, “I’ve just received this news. You sent people to find Mind Reader too, right? Is that correct?” Both of her palms were pressed firmly against the table surface while her eyes glared directly at Garen’s as if she was trying to determine whether he would lie.

“How would that be possible?” Garen furrowed his eyebrows and denied it immediately. “Why would I send people to look for him? Mind Reader is meaningless to anyone if he has yet to become fully aware.”

Nine-tailed Fox stared at Garen while she remained silent.

Meanwhile, Garen had finished pouring the tea. He pushed one cup towards the other party while lifting another cup and sipping from it slowly.

“Why are you looking at me like that? It’s true that I sent some people to investigate Mind Reader before this, but they could only return and call it a day when they were unable to find his whereabouts,” Garen explained. He could tell that something was amiss with Nine-tailed Fox’s gaze and smiled immediately because of that.

“Don’t tell me that you suspect that I’ve started working on Mind Reader already?”

“You have those motives,” said Nine-tailed Fox indifferently, “Night Water once revealed that your exact intentions are too profound… I had initially assumed that you were a normal Mother Stream System powerhouse, yet the truth has proven me wrong.”

“But it’s true that I’m merely a normal Mother Stream System powerhouse. Which part of that is wrong?” asked Garen doubtfully.

“Are you really that normal?” A mocking look appeared on Nine-tailed Fox’s face. “In less than two years, you’ve managed to secure the seat of the No. 3 position in Vulture. Your moves are experienced and you managed to clean up the internal members to the point where everyone was won over. Is that what you call ‘normal’?”

She sat down on the chair gently.

“If that’s considered normal, the other truly normal Transmigrators like us should not even be alive. The rest of us should just buy a block of tofu to smash our brains in and kill ourselves ^1 .

“Are you doubting me?” Garen shook his head. “I don’t have any reason to mess up the Plot.”

“Of course. Thus, the only thing we can do is to doubt you,” said Nine-tailed Fox calmly, “The passage to Lighthouse has been opened so you can return anytime. The main reason why I came here this time was to inform you about this.”

“Understood.” Garen nodded.

“That’s right, I have something to tell you.” Nine-tailed Fox stood up and walked toward the exit. “Mind Reader is fully aware now. He’s become friends with Yuria just like in the original Plot. However, unlike the original Plot, the realization of his powers have made them much stronger than before which caused great changes throughout the Plot. I’m warning you not to provoke him anymore. Otherwise, your relations with Yuria will not be able to protect you either. Many people have already expressed dissatisfaction with this.”

Garen sat in his seat and did not move or speak. He merely looked on quietly while Nine-tailed Fox opened the door and left.

Double-tailed Scorpion walked out of the side door. She was dressed in a tight black office wear skirt suit over black stockings that made her look gorgeous and sexy. Her silver hair was tied back in a high ponytail and it swayed gently when she moved. After the failure of her previous quest, she had requested for Butcher’s support. However, Mind Reader managed to escape anyway, and both of them suffered defeat at the last hurdle despite killing many of Mind Reader’s mysterious protectors.

As the punishment for failing the quest, Double-tailed Scorpion applied to be Garen’s personal secretary on her own. Her initial retirement plans had become an illusion which caused her to fully detest Mind Reader’s mysterious companion who hindered her quest. She swore to take revenge for this initial grudge.

“There’s a new situation. You should take a look.” Double-tailed Scorpion placed the document in her hands in front of Garen. “Aside from that, hasn’t Nine-tailed Fox become too reckless recently? Should I discipline her?” She asked probingly.

She could not retire and had already divorced her husband as well. Therefore, her inability to retire meant that it was completely impossible for her to break away from the underworld. Furthermore, it meant that she could not resume her life as a normal person either. She decided to simply remove herself from her normal life and focus wholeheartedly on finishing her opponent off instead.

“That won’t be necessary.” Garen shook his head. “Just attend to your own matters and that’ll be fine.”

“Yes.”

Nine-tailed Fox left. Although Double-tailed Scorpion did not know the exact things that she had said, the actions that Nine-tailed Fox had done in private during the countless times when she had come over had rather disrespectful motives toward Garen. This made her extremely displeased.

“Butcher, come over and see me. This is about the previous quest,” Garen lifted the phone and said.

“You have news about Mind Reader?! I’ll come right over!” One of Butcher’s arms was accidentally broken off previously but he managed to survive and return despite being on the brink of death. He had been waiting for revenge for a long time.

Someone had hindered Mind Reader’s movements the last time, but Garen could not assist him because he had gone to the Forest Capital to find Yuria personally. However, he planned to dispatch more manpower this time. If it was necessary, he would take the field personally.

His current self was becoming stronger at every moment. His strength, speed, vitality, and intelligence were becoming more terrifying at all times because of the Soul Energy’s nourishment.

“I’ll try and see if I can snatch the Sacred Sigil Soul Ring directly. If I can’t do that, I’ll absorb as much Soul Energy as possible and go to Lighthouse after that.” Garen had decided already. He could not stay in this world any longer. He needed to gather enough resources as soon as possible and left after that.

Chapter 1210: Gather 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It’s actually him!”

Nine-tailed Fox looked with a solemn expression on her face as Kong Xinxue put down the little device that she was holding earlier.

“I’m afraid that Garen himself has yet to think of this. Ah Xue, you have the powerful ability of eavesdropping on information within a radius of more than a thousand meters in your surroundings at any time! It’s fortunate that you didn’t inform him directly in the beginning,” said Nine-tailed Fox gladly.

“He will probably take drastic measures soon. However, it won’t be a serious issue as long as it doesn’t affect Yuria,” Kong Xinxue said sincerely.

“I couldn’t see through Garen all this while. I sensed a hazy fog around his body before this, but it feels like the fog has thickened now,” Nine-tailed Fox said softly.

“Then what are you planning to do?” Kong Xinxue looked at her helplessly. “I think that you might be worrying too much?”

“Everyone has their own plans and so do we, right?”

“Of course, I know that. It just seems like he’s broken away from everyone and is acting independently now.”

“He was never close to us, no?” Kong Xinxue was unconcerned.

“I’m afraid that the exact details regarding him are too terrifyingly powerful. He’s clearly gathering the Forged Sacred Sigil. If he manages to snatch it first, our chances will decrease significantly. Aren’t you worried that we won’t be able to obtain the Sacred Sigil in the end?” Nine-tailed Fox was somewhat angry.

“What is there to be worried about? After being rescued by him recently, it seems that I owe him a favor now. Helping you gather this information is somewhat disloyal.” Kong Xinxue was somewhat dull towards this matter.

“You!” Nine-tailed was helpless. “Whatever, I’ll do it myself if you’re not going to take this seriously!” She got up and rushed off to find someone else to contact.

Kong Xinxue was not as inclined as her. She merely wanted to live through this world leisurely and did not want to destroy her own life for things that solely resembled power.

*********************

Forest Capital

Yuria rode a motorcycle alone and sped through a vast forest of trees. He traveled along a little winding road and diverged off the path occasionally before riding toward another area.

He simply decided to set off on the journey alone because of the issue with the spy. Nonetheless, it would be fine as long as he maintained contact with Vulture at all times.

He met the Mind Reader again after being saved by Garen in the nick of time previously. As the second of the Four Great Cornerstones, that mature man who resembled an older uncle had even brought his own young son along. This man had formed a connection between them by contacting Yuria in the first instance. The Mind Reader’s ability allowed him to read the surface memories of anyone within a hundred meter range from himself. Thus, he was thoroughly familiar with the information which stated that Yuria was the Savior. Moreover, he also possessed a certain amount of understanding of Yuria’s personality and his past achievements.

Yuria was rushing off in the direction of the Ocean Capital this time. It was also a large-scale port in Slann.

Over there, the Mind Reader told him that he had information regarding Yurijie and Light Path. He would give him this information on the condition that he protected him this one time.

Yuria agreed resolutely and made a beeline for the Ocean Capital on his motorcycle.

Vroom…

The motorcycle’s thick tires rubbed against the ground at full speed while releasing thunderous throttling noises.

Both sides of the forest sped behind his head when he passed them speedily. Everything was going extremely smoothly for Yuria this time because there was no any sort of ambush at all. He left the Forest Capital area without a hitch before gradually entering another province.

His motorcycle braked abruptly before Yuria turned the vehicle around, stopping sideways on the road. His gaze shifted towards a little box on the ground.

“It’s mother’s box!” He sounded slightly emotional. He got off the motorcycle quickly and picked up the box before opening it.

The box was a standard wooden box that was made of mahogany wood. There were numerous delicate patterns on the surface. The box sprung open after making a brief clapping noise.

A rectangular slip of solid white paper lay flat inside the box.

A row of words was written there.

‘Ocean Capital, Sky Cinema, 1500 hours ‘ Yakuza Race ^1 ‘. Child, be careful of the people around you…”

It was written in his mother’s handwriting!

Yuria’s heart was filled with joy before he suppressed the expression on his face and kept the piece of paper carefully.

“What are you looking at?” An unexpected voice echoed behind him suddenly. It was a female voice.

“It’s you!” Yuria turned around suddenly and saw that a girl in a white dress was actually standing behind him. It was the nameless girl who had saved him earlier.

The memories of that night flashed across his mind suddenly before he unconsciously grabbed the other party’s arm immediately.

“I won’t let you escape again this time!” he said firmly.

“Don’t believe what is on that piece of paper.” The girl looked vaguely haggard while her eyes were swollen, puffy, and lightly rimmed with red circles.

“Why?” Yuria was faintly shocked. “This is my mother’s handwriting. There’s definitely no mistake!”

“Don’t believe what is on that piece of paper,” repeated the girl.

“Why?!” Yuria furrowed his eyebrows. “What happened to your eyes?” He reached his hand out and tried to touch the girl’s eyes.

Hum!

When Yuria opened his eyes suddenly, he realized that he was still riding his motorcycle.

He had unconsciously fallen asleep earlier. The strong wind blew over from the front and pulled the skin of his face back until it hurt slightly. His motorcycle sped forward quickly and traveled straight through the road before him. Apparently, he had fallen asleep during such a short amount of time.

Yuria decreased his speed before stopping the vehicle beside the road slowly. He did not turn the engine off, instead, he merely sat on the motorcycle and recalled his previous dream carefully.

“That’s strange!”

He reached his hand out and touched his pocket before realizing that the piece of white paper was actually inside. His heart trembled slightly before he took it out and looked at it.

The words that were exactly like the ones he had seen in his dream were actually written there. He got down from the motorcycle quickly before hurriedly searching the trunk of his bike to find the wooden makeup box that his mother had always used.

“It looks like I actually found the box, but the part where I saw her was a dream.” Yuria exhaled softly.

“Don’t believe what is on that piece of paper.” A voice rang out beside his ear suddenly.

Yuria felt as if that was merely an illusion. He immediately scanned his surroundings briefly but did not see the girl’s figure at all.

“Did I actually hallucinate and hear that?” He shook his head. He felt that the long period of traveling without rest had probably caused him to hallucinate.

He got on the motorcycle quickly and started the engine. A thunderous noise could be heard as he sped off into the distance suddenly before disappearing at the end of the road quickly.

A few moments after he left, a little girl in a white dress walked out from behind a tree slowly; she stared blankly in the direction toward which Yuria had gone.

“Are you trying to hinder our Lord’s plans?” A lofty, Triangular-Headed Robot walked out of the forest on the other side slowly while its light green electronic eyes glared at the girl coldly.

“I wasn’t…” Bang!

The robot appeared in front of the girl instantly. It punched her abdomen violently and hit her until she bent forward at the waist, spitting out a mouthful of blood out of her mouth vigorously.

Suddenly, both of the girl’s hands disappeared in succession as if she was a phantom before she tapped the front of robot’s chest more than ten consecutive times.

Shh shh shh! A series of noises that sounded like balloons that were continuously leaking air could be heard before a large amount of blue electric arcs crackled out throughout the robot’s entire body.

“You couldn’t even retaliate the previous sudden attack despite its speed,” said the robot indifferently. It seemed completely unconcerned although it was about to be destroyed. “How long can you persevere?”

“That doesn’t concern you!” The girl ripped it apart with both hands.

Shh!

She actually tore the entire robot into two halves and sent both parts flying in different directions before they crashed into the soil heavily.

Barf.

The girl held her stomach. Blood flowed out of the corners of her mouth continuously when she was unable to suppress it.

“The Special Motorized Squad really thinks highly of me.” The girl’s gaze sharpened when she looked around her surroundings and discovered that three more similar Triangular-Headed Robots were walking out of the forest slowly.

“Resistance is meaningless,” the three robots said at the same time as if they were a single person.

The sound of a helicopter’s propellers echoed in the sky slowly while the noise of a large crowd moving nearby could be heard as well. It was clear that the nearby areas were surrounded by her opponent.

“You insisted on trying to betray us in vain, instead of just behaving yourself and becoming a tool for His Highness the Slayer to vent his frustrations,” said one of the robots coldly.

“It looks like we have great gains to reap.” No one had expected that Nine-tailed Fox and Li Hua would lead ten people out of the forest to surround the three robots on all sides.

“One robot for each person. No problem, right?” Nine-tailed Fox glanced at the girl. She had followed Yuria for a lengthy period of time to track down this unexpectedly mysterious girl. It was likely that she would gain a great deal of information if she could seize her now.

The girl nodded.

Other than the Special Operation Forces which comprised more than ten members, the other two helicopters had also appeared above their heads slowly while the nozzles of their machine guns were aimed directly at the robots.

“Members of the White Crab Army, I’m giving you one final chance to leave immediately.” Nine-tailed Fox sneered while looking on at the three robots. Although she was indebted to the White Crab Army for their protection, she would not be so kind this time after being heavily injured by the overpowered robots previously.

Once the robots had retreated, she would release an order to fire and take the opportunity to inflict heavy damage on these three robots. As these Triangular-Headed Robots were exorbitantly priced, it was unlikely that the White Crab Army would have a large quantity of them.

*********************

Inside a narrow office.

The five people here that consisted of Vulture No. 1, No. 2, Garen, No. 4, and No. 5 were all seated around the meeting table. They were looking at the three robots on the monitor screen at the side quietly.

The incident that Yuria encountered was also being monitored by them.

“This woman is Nine-tailed Fox?” Vulture No. 1 asked while knitting his eyebrows together. The eyebrows of this imposing man who was dressed in a white military uniform were slightly furrowed when he looked at Nine-tailed Fox’s self-confident and calm expression.

“Yes,” replied Garen, “Chief, do you have any suggestions?”

“My suggestions aren’t worth mentioning. Nonetheless, it’s quite shocking to see her taking advantage of us openly like this,” said No. 1 Chief flatly.

“This figure is an important individual. As long as we grasp her in our hands, we might be able to gain more insight into the White Crab Army,” said the old woman called No. 2 in a muffled voice. “In order to counter the White Crab Army’s intentions toward the Savior and the appearance of the Forged Sacred Sigil, I suggest that we move the specialized forces to focus on eliminating the White Crab Army.”

“We can invite the other two nations to undergo a war exercise with us to solve the issue simultaneously,” said the man called No. 4 in a lazy tone.

“Release a command to order the arrest of the terrorist organizations. The White Crab Army’s official confrontation towards the National Organizations can be used to determine the Inhuman Organizations,” said the newly-appointed female No.5 quietly.

“Since Nine-tailed Fox has hindered public affairs and obstructed governmental work, we might as well put her in the same boat as the terrorists and get rid of them all in one ago,” No. 4 continued.

“I think that’s inappropriate,” Garen opened his mouth and glanced at No. 4. “Although Nine-Tailed Fox is considered as the leader of an underground sect who cannot appear publicly, she’s still somewhat useful towards the safety and stability of Slann. I suggest that we just keep our guards up without having to waste too much effort.”

“I’ve heard that you and Nine-tailed Fox have some kind of relationship, No. 3. Is that correct?” No. 4 sounded as if he was targeting Garen slightly.

Chapter 1211: Group Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Alright, I have two more minutes. If you have anything else to discuss, please do it as soon as possible for I need to chair the intercontinental forum meeting soon,” said No. 1 quietly.

“There’s an issue regarding the mining rights of the Red Nation who are engaging in oil-drilling activities at sea. We’ve basically reached a universal agreement but we need to take an action and warn the surrounding pirates to put them in order,” said No. 5 immediately.

“Garen, I’ll leave this matter to you, alright?” No. 1 looked at Garen.

“No problem.” Naturally, Garen did not simply waste his few hundred years of living, he had a solid grasp on various rights and influences. Although he was not as influential as the others in terms of his large-scale forces, his rate of expansion was still abnormally shocking.

“Aside from that, I have a minor request,” Garen resumed speaking.

“Speak.” No. 1 nodded.

“I was recently hoping to purchase a batch of specialized metal nets, perhaps a quantity of more or less twelve tonnes. I don’t have any qualms with the price,” resumed Garen. These were his preparations to finish a product for a quest that was given to him during a forum with Lighthouse. The other side had mentioned that they wanted twelve tonnes of this specialized net. In most of the other worlds, this specialized net was a precious and rare metal. Fortunately, there was no shortage of it in this world. The only downside was that it was monopolized by the military and only the government had the right to use it, while other private forces were not allowed to possess it.

“Why are you going to use it for?” The old woman called No. 2 asked while furrowing her eyebrows.

“I have my reasons, of course.” Garen did not explain further.

Both of them stopped speaking after that. After coming into contact with them for more than a year, despite being a purely individual armed force when he joined Vulture initially, Garen later developed a powerful influence and grasped a certain sharpness. This was particularly apparent after the battle with the Slayer, where he escaped unscathed and was instantly highly praised as the strongest individual who existed in Slann. He was also depicted as the banner of Vulture’s military force which they held up high.

His speaking power had also increased significantly.

“That’s fine.” After considering for some time, No. 1 agreed swiftly while standing up. “Alright, today’s matters will end here. That woman must be grasped within our palms. Assemble the troops and capture her immediately. We can compensate Nine-tailed Fox to a certain degree.”

“Understood.” The others got up gradually and looked on while No. 1 left.

The old woman called No. 2 only left the room slowly after that.

Both of them came from powerful backgrounds and received the backing of numerous forces and high-ranking officials. They were actually the powerful foundations that were truly supporting the existence of Vulture.

Meanwhile, Garen was the people’s international banner of assurance and the foundation of their military strength as well.

“I’ll be taking my leave first, then.” Garen smiled and became the third person to walk out of the room. His secretary Double-tailed Scorpion and two other bodyguards followed him closely as he walked across the corridor which was covered in white carpet and exited the room.

After leaving the meeting building, Garen walked straight toward a luxurious black limousine while Double-tailed Scorpion walked up toward him and whispered next to his ear at the same time.

“The plane has been arranged properly already and can take off at any time.”

Garen nodded and turned back to glance at the lofty building. No. 4 and No. 5 had currently pulled open the curtains of the meeting room and were looking at him.

No. 4 and No. 5’s authorities had been significantly reduced ever since he joined the meeting between the five people. Hence, the newly-appointed No. 5 did not have a favorable impression of Garen either.

“Is there a conclusion of the investigation of the skeleton of the White Crab Army’s robot that was sent to Lawrence University?” he asked casually.

“There’s one report already. They can improve the energy consumption issues that occurred when we modified our robots. The investigation report also showed that they could save us from another two years worth of scientific research and progress,” Double-tailed Scorpion replied quickly, “I also think that the No. 1 Chief had considered this aspect before he agreed to your request so quickly.”

“That’s good.” Garen took a long stride before entering the limousine. The front and back of this vehicle were flanked by convoys that were guarding it while the secretary Double-tailed Scorpion sat in the front row next to the driver.

“The exact whereabouts of Mind Reader has been determined at the Ocean Capital. We’ve already established good relations with Chief Executive Bob Crest there beforehand,” continued Double-tailed Scorpion.

“If I’m not mistaken, that girl in the white dress probably possesses the strength of the Illusionist. Therefore, it’s better to achieve the goals one at a time. We’ll discuss this again after we’ve seized Mind Reader,” Garen replied indifferently.

He did not want to waste any more time in this world. Since he had taken sufficient rest, it was probably time for him to keep moving forward now.

He had used the influence that he had acquired to complete a significant amount of quests during this past year. Thus, he had accumulated a good amount of Contribution Points. Once he entered Lighthouse, he could simply be compared to a veteran Transmigrator who had accumulated many years of experience.

***********************

After the brief meeting, Garen spent the following week making preparations to capture Mind Reader.

There were other people from Vulture who were paying close attention to Yuria over there. Meanwhile, Garen focused on hunting Mind Reader down. The best time to surround and seize Mind Reader would be the moment when he met Yuria.

Garen was not concerned about the strength of the Sacred Sigil. In fact, he did not care about any Forged Sacred Sigils either because he was only concerned about whether he could absorb its Soul Energy and obtain it.

Within the span of a week, Yuria had rushed to the Ocean Capital. Meanwhile, Nine-tailed Fox and the others saved that mysterious girl but were later encircled by Vulture which took the girl away to be examined. Nine-tailed Fox and the rest were unimaginably furious because of that.

Garen made a phone call to explain that he was powerless, for this was what the No. 1 Chief meant earlier.

However, Nine-tailed Fox, Li Hua, and the others had somewhat rejected Garen as an outsider after this recent incident. They did not regard him as a companion anymore.

Garen was not the slightest bit concerned. He secretly ordered several people to disguise themselves as members of the White Crab Army to ambush Mind Reader. However, his continuous efforts to dispatch numerous powerhouses was of no help. Although Mind Reader did not have the protection of a designated armed force, he could conceal himself within the vast sea of people in the Ocean Capital fully without being captured at all.

Transmigrators were indeed the best candidates to hunt Mind Reader down since Transmigrators were not affected by Mind Reader’s abilities that could capture their surface memories. Therefore, they would not accidentally reveal their own intentions to seize them. Unfortunately, Garen had completely fallen out with Nine-tailed Fox and the others.

After a period of consideration, he decided to enter the field personally.

The Soul Energy’s nourishment allowed Garen’s qualities to nearly reach an average of eight points quickly to achieve a minor stage where his limit was increased. His current physical form did not seem to resemble that of a human anymore. As there were no unnatural powers in the laws of both this universe and world, the definitions of the basic rules here were very strict. According to the innate laws of things, since Garen had the strength and vitality to dodge bullets, he would naturally possess a larger mass to accommodate such powerful strength and vitality.

Within less than two short years, he was now over two meters tall and weighed more than one hundred and eighty kilograms. He had basically turned into an abnormally exaggerated giant.

His saber that was initially fine and slender had been smithed again into a longer and wider blade. It was over three meters long and as wide as a palm, making it look sharper and fiercer.

No one else could fully comprehend powers of this grade except Garen himself who currently could not seem to find an opponent in this world. A possible threat toward himself could only be produced if the Slayer used his trump card. Otherwise, he did not have to take anything else into account.

After making arrangements for a special plane, Garen flew straight to the Ocean Capital. He dismissed all of his other subordinates simultaneously and proceeded to look for Mind Reader on his own.

Meanwhile, the military exercises at sea between the Alliance of the Three Nations had started at the same time. They were military exercises on the surface. However, they were actually movements to counter the White Crab Army’s terrorist acts in reality.

*******************

Ocean Capital

The sky was an azure colored sea that enhanced the beauty of the sky-blue ocean.

Gigantic buildings that resembled minarets stood beside the sea. They were connected to each other and were all completely white. They formed a continuous stretch of buildings that spanned more than ten kilometers.

A colossal stone pillar that resembled a flat tray stood upright near the ocean in the very center of the area. Rows of white castles with blue army flags that fluttered in the sky were built on top of the tray. Most of these castles were shaped like three-pronged forks, while a few of them were detached units. Their doorways were all accessed from the bottom and were extended to the sea by a long suspended bridge.

The sunlight accompanied the whistling sea breeze. It would instantly feel very hot if the breeze was not blowing. White seabirds flew about in the sky, forming a flock. They were occasionally scattered everywhere when they were shaken by planes that flew past them.

Garen got down from the boat. The scenery of the distant sea from the port looked like a painting.

He inhaled a deep breath of fresh air.

“It’s truly a great place.”

“Of course. The Ocean Capital is the most popular scenic vacation destination among the Four Great Capitals. It attracts more tourists from more than thirty different countries every year,” a man with a white beard behind him said while smiling.

“Just like me,” said Garen happily.

“Yes, just like you.” The bearded man laughed. “We have the thing that you desire here, as long as you have enough of ‘this’.” He reached his hand out and made a pinching motion to hint that Garen was rich.

“I’m just a tourist who merely came here to go sightseeing. Uncle, please don’t lead me astray,” Garen laughed quietly.

“Although you’re a tourist, you’re a man first and foremost, and only a tourist after that.” The bearded man laughed nonchalantly.

A few other male tourists beside him laughed as well. Even though Garen was not interested, they gathered around him quickly to chat with the bearded man and ask him about the more private fun sites around here.

Garen stood on the deck of the boat and gazed at the Ocean Capital from afar. He did not bring his saber along this time. In fact, he did not bring anything aside from the essentials such as his identification card and bank card. He disguised himself as a normal vacationing tourist to avoid spooking Mind Reader and being discovered by him.

Garen did not know Mind Reader’s exact identity as he could even be a Transmigrator or someone else. Nonetheless, Garen had basically determined Mind Reader’s intentions. As long as he still wanted to meet Yuria, he would definitely not leave the Ocean Capital. He could surely grasp his aims as long as he seized this opportunity.

His next task was to determine whether Mind Reader was still in this city.

Perhaps this would be a great difficulty for other people. However, for Garen who had obtained the Soul Ring, detecting the forces of his Soul Energy was enough to determine whether Mind Reader was here or not.

He was looking far into the distance clearly now. He could see two intense shrouds of Soul Energy forces that were faintly dispersing from the inside of the Ocean Capital now. One of them was permeating slowly and gently. They were the Soul Energy forces of Yuria the Savior.

Meanwhile, the other one was icy cold and tinged with fear. It was obvious that this belonged to Mind Reader who was feeling afraid after being surrounded and attacked.

“The range of the Soul Energy forces is a bit too wide, so it’s slightly difficult to determine the location of a single person.” Garen stroked his chin and thought of the countermeasures.

“Mind Reader’s abilities are really troublesome. It’s best that I avoid scaring anyone and hunt him down alone. I’ve already memorized his outer appearance, height, and other characteristics. But, I’m just worried that he uses certain means to use makeup or change his looks. The current Plot has become chaotic as well. This is really difficult to handle.”

The information regarding Mind Reader swirled in Garen’s mind slowly.

As the boat moved closer towards the Ocean Capital, his mind tentatively decided on a feasible plan.

Hum…

The boat made a loud blowing noise and approached the shore slowly before starting to put the disembarkation plank down.

The tourists got down from the boat using the railing-lined disembarkation plank before walking on the pure white, squeaky clean pier.

Garen held onto the railing while walking down. He allowed a pretty golden-haired, blue-eyed little girl to go down before him while her mother smiled at Garen in a friendly manner to express her gratitude. Only then did he tread on the disembarkation plank slowly before walking towards the pier.

He took his cell phone out and made a reservation to stay in a hotel quickly. Next, he began to look for shop fronts that looked like they served delicious food in preparation to settle his dinner plans.

The time was 1600 hours now. It would be time for him to eat dinner soon.

Chapter 1212: Group Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After he disembarked, he wandered around the harbor for half a day. Garen couldn’t find a stall that sold food. Under such circumstances, he could only head deeper in and take a turn to the streets leading into the city.

There were food bars all around the street. The crowd that was coming and going was beyond massive. Couples were holding hands while many young children were held by their family members walking in and out.

Garen picked one of them and headed in. He found a place to sit and ordered a few dishes. He waited for the dishes to be served.

The person in charge of greeting the customers in the shop was a seventeen to eighteen years old young girl. She was wearing a pair of pale blue skin-tight jeans, revealing her figure in all the right places. The little white bunnies under her yellow T-shirt that were doing the hoppity hop, in addition to her pretty face, attracted quite a fair amount of male customers into the shop.

Ring ring.

Garen’s mobile phone rang. He took it out to have a look. It was a message from Double-tailed Scorpion. The position of Mind Reader had most probably been determined, and the regional location could be narrowed down to the range of neighborhood. Any more accurate than that couldn’t be achieved.

“The neighborhood range is good enough,” Garen was quite satisfied as he deleted the message.

Just as he sat down, a few young girls dressed as university students entered the shop. One of the girls was puzzled as she swept a glance at Garen.

“What’s wrong, Cammy?” Another girl patted her shoulder.

“Nothing, I think I saw someone I know.” The girl, Cammy shook her head and smiled.

The three young girls sat at the table not far from Garen and ordered a few dishes.

Cammy turned her head and seemed to recall something. She turned her head to look at Garen once again.

“Kong Xiaofei?” She called in a soft voice.

“Mm?” Garen was momentarily stunned. He didn’t think there was anyone here who would recognize him.

He followed the voice and looked over. He instantly recognized the girl.

“Cammy Ning?”

It was his classmate back in high school at Lily of the Valley. Who would have thought they would meet at such a place.

When he left the school, he announced that he was recommended another location for university and ended communication with the classmates at high school. He was, after all, not the real Kong Xiaofei.

“Why are you here?” Cammy Ning was overjoyed. She did not expect to meet an old acquaintance here.

“What about you, how did you end up here?” Garen politely exchanged the topic.

“I go to the university here. Where else, if not here?” Cammy Ning replied with a smile.

Her two besties immediately giggled as they moved closer.

“Who is he? Your old boyfriend?”

“No way! Do you think of anything else other than that kinda stuff?” Cammy Ning rebutted with a laugh.

“Then he must be your current boyfriend, haha. It’s no wonder you’re giving the cold shoulder to the Filt brothers. It’s because your man is here!” Another bestie chuckled.

“Nonsense. We’re just normal classmates.” Cammy Ning had a good impression of Garen. He was an honest lean boy, but now he had grown tough in such a short time.

The two tables were naturally combined together.

Garen sat by the three girls.

“What are you doing here? Holiday?”

“Yes, I heard that Ocean Capital is a world-renowned tourist spot, so came to check it out,” Garen smiled as he responded. “You’re attending Ocean University of Lance Royal Family, right?”

“How do you know?” Cammy Ning was baffled.

“Isn’t she wearing the school emblem?” Garen pointed at one of the girl’s chest. There was a delicately-made, silvery white mermaid emblem pinned there.

“What about you? Where are you studying?”

“I’m no longer attending,” Garen casually replied.

“Not attending?” Cammy Ning was stupefied. It should be true, as it wasn’t a semester break yet Kong Xiaofei had the time to travel. There must have been some issue.

Hearing these words, the other two girls were struck. Although they did not immediately put on the display, their faces became slightly dull.

Initially, when they heard that Garen was here to travel for leisure, he must be well off to be able to travel alone with ease. However, now that he was a dropout, their enthusiasm had dampened.

“Did you drop out?” One of them asked in a low voice.

Garen nodded. How could an old fart that lived a few hundred years not see the change in the attitude of the two girls? He wasn’t the least bit bothered. He was way past the stage of flaunting.

The dishes that they ordered were quickly served. They ate together. Garen kept his head down as he swiftly pigged out, clearing the dishes in a few gulps. The dishes’ load was quite small, so he swept them clean without leaving any scrap.

This made the two girls look down on him even more.

Cammy Ning was speechless. However, judging by Garen’s large build, she could understand his huge appetite.

******

“I have a bad feeling,” In a coffee shop not far away, a man dressed in a black windbreaker whispered to a lady beside him.

The woman was also dressed in the same black windbreaker. Wearing windbreakers on a hot day was definitely something eye-catching. The woman had purple hair while her purple iris and pale white skin set her apart from the crowd.

“Your ability of premonition can’t be wrong. I suspect we are being watched,” The woman calmly mentioned, “it could be those dregs from Vulture. They didn’t dare go after Slayer, yet they came to play the bully and look for us instead.” She gave a scornful look.

“No… This time, the feeling is stronger than previous times,” Mind Reader spoke in a low voice. “I suspect it may be someone more troublesome on the go.”

“It could be from Lighthouse. Only they can avoid your mind reading to get close to us!” The woman knew of Lighthouse and told Minder Reader frankly.

“Why would Lighthouse seek me out! Why won’t you tell me in full?” Mind Reader frowned.

“You only need to know that there’s a really really bad organization and they’re after your Sacred Sigil,” The woman took a sip of coffee.

“Then what do you say we do?” Mind Reader asked in a low voice.

“Now, there are the three forces, Black Federation, Vulture and White Crab, which are after us. We will remain here for a few weeks to lure these three forces over. Now, as long as we play our cards right…”

“I know what you mean.” Mind Reader nodded.

“Don’t worry, everything will be alright. You can take your son to a place where nobody knows who you are and live. Relax.” The woman patted Mind Reader on the shoulder.

“I hope so…” Mind Reader forced himself to nod. He was about to take a sip off the coffee in his hands before his face stiffened, “They’re here!”

Pretending to act normal, he stood up and walked toward the washroom.

The woman took out her mobile phone to have a look. It was getting late. She placed some money on the table to settle the payment and got up to walk out with her handbag.

The two cooperated tacitly without attracting any attention and left through two exits respectively.

Those at the coffee shop did not find them out of the norm.

Not even a minute after they had departed, the door was swung open. A group of men and women wearing white hats walked in. Their sharp gaze swept around the scene. After an exchange of whispers, they found they were not around. The group scanned and checked from table to table.

Outside the streets by a lamp post, the two gathered and looked at the coffee shop from afar.

“It’s White Crab,” the woman whispered. She took out a lighter to light herself a cigarette.

“Can you sense their thoughts?”

“They’re here to capture me just as before. This time, they’re doing a blanket search. I wouldn’t know more details than that. They’re preventing their minds from being read by me.” The man was in a dilemma.

“Do you still have any premonition after avoiding them?” The woman casually asked.

“It’s stronger now!”

“Direction.”

“Behind us.”

The woman turned back and looked but did not find anything. She only saw crowds going and coming on the streets.

“Let’s go,” She led him to walk at the side, onward to a little alley.

The two halted once they entered the alley.

“Have you forgotten our dreams?” A young man stood in the alley with his back facing them. “Seasnake?”

The man shifted his head back; his dark brown eyes struck a dead stare at the woman.

A sharp white card appeared between his fingers.

“King of Hearts!” The woman’s body tensed up.

Mind Reader could see the man’s other distinct features.

“Black Federation…” His pupils shrunk and his body sunk backward. He couldn’t detect the person’s thoughts before. He was from the Lighthouse!

“Come with me, Seasnake and Mind Reader. Big brother has awaited you for a long time now,” King of Hearts smiled.

“If they were to follow, you then wouldn’t that make us come for nothing?” A cold voice was heard coming from behind Mind Reader and Seasnake.

******

“Soul Energy Force?” Garen was having his after-meal tea when he suddenly felt a tremble. He sensed that there was a slight chaotic Soul Energy Force oscillating over not far away.

Cammy Ning and her friends were whispering about the interesting news here when they saw him on his mobile phone.

“What’s wrong? Got something you need to do? Go take care of it if you do,” It was rare for Cammy Ning to bump into her classmate, so she was in quite a mood and opened up more.

“Just a small matter,” Garen smiled. “I have to go now. Continue with your meal,” He got up as he spoke and came to face a person standing by the shop’s entrance.

That person was two meters tall and was wearing a white western suit. He was wearing a pair of sophisticated, golden metal spectacles. His blond hair reflected a soft bright glow under the sunlight. He was standing by the shop’s entrance and smiled as he gazed at Garen.

“Sword Master Garen?” The man was brazen and calmly revealed Garen’s identity.

Garen’s smile slowly wiped off. he threw a glance at Cammy Ning and her friends behind him.

“You plan to make a move here?”

“I have long wanted to meet the number one Kendo genius of Slann, named the strongest saber art in three thousand years. Now that I’ve encountered you by chance, wouldn’t I be wasting off my good luck if I don’t seek your advice?” The smile of the man’s face deepened.

“They, are acting, right? Exchanging lines?” Someone couldn’t help but laugh out loud, “What a show.”

Cammy Ning and her two friends turned to look at the duo, feeling rather strange

Wham!

A troop of solider in black military wear kicked open the entrance of the shop. Over ten armed soldiers charged in, encircling Garen.

They unlocked the guns’ safety with a click. All firearms were aimed at Garen.

“It’s a show, right? There’s no need to be… Bang,” One of the customer was about to open his mouth when a shot was fired on his chest. Blood drenched his back as he collapsed to the ground.

All customers in the shop fell silent.

The serving waitress dropped and broke a plate. Someone was covering their mouth tightly.

Ah!

A woman screamed out of fear and wanted to make a dash out.

Boom.

Another shot was fired.

She immediately crashed onto the ground next to Garen. Blood from her back oozed out. Her body slowly collided on the ground, trembling it a bit. She rumbled over and settled over Garen’s foot.

Clang!

Garen’s palms clapped and made an ear-piercing thunderous sound. He lurched forward with his bent lower body and his palms arching straight ahead.

Chapter 1213: Attainment 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Wham!!

The blond man crossed his arms over his chest to defend but Garen was just too fast. Before he could react or even bulge his muscles, Garen was already in front of him striking him with his palms.

“This speed!!?” His pupils shrunk. Bam bam bam bam!!!

The surrounding soldiers opened fire but hit a blank. Bullets shot at where Garen originally stood, but it all hit a blank spot and fell on to the ground. Some of them ricocheted, hitting the soldiers, clanging as it echoed metal sounds. It was obvious that the soldiers were wearing bulletproof armors made from steel, metal plates.

The shop was in total chaos with bullets ricocheting everywhere. People were screaming as they crouched down with their heads in their hands, some cried out loud from fear.

Garen and the blond man exchanged blows at close combat. Like a phantom apparition, their four arms rammed against each other as they fought, giving out loud, crashing sounds.

The ramming sounds were like dull thunders, detonating at every strike. Each time their arms interlocked, the blond man’s face would pale a shade further and sounds of bones fracturing could be heard faintly from his arms.

He retreated in succession out of the shop.

Kaboom!

With a loud crash, the blond man was blown up into mid-air, smashing into a bronze statue in the town square and causing the scatter of white debris as he fell to the ground.

“It’s been a while since I met an expert who can face me off.” Garen relaxed his arm and walked out of the shop, watching the blond man struggling to get up. His current physical fitness was more than a monster. It was hard to imagine that there would be someone who could hold up a fight with him without collapsing in an instance.

“You!…” The blond man’s face was full of disbelief. He tried to get up using his arms as support, but they were badly contorted to the point of not being able to support his body.

Seeing the soldiers crumbling down in the shop in a blink of an eye, the man felt chills. He could not believe that this current state was real.

As Military Flag, he was the second strongest in the Black Federation yet he could not survive for more than half a minute with this man. It was only over ten moves when those specially enhanced, high-intensity arms fractured his bones.

If one were to tell him a day before that someone in this world would be able to face him off and defeat him in half a minute with brute body techniques, he would have thought that the person was joking.

And now, he had to believe it as the truth was laid before his eyes.

“Everyone… underestimated you…” Military Flag spurted blood. His skeletal bones seemed to have fallen apart as he could not even get up.

Garen strolled out of the shop, leaving behind him a sea of corpses with their blood flowing like a river.

Miraculously, only a few customers in the shop suffered paper-cut wounds from the stray bullets while the rest were unharmed.

Seeing Military Flag, the blond man lying on the ground, and the soldiers in their outfits, he could guess who this party was. Vulture’s intelligence has detailed records on the Black Federation.

He walked towards Military Flag.

Bam!!

Suddenly, a bullet fired at his foot. It was half a meter distance of the step he was going to take but for some reason, Garen shortened the length of this particular step by three quarters, as though he coordinated with the sniper which evidently enabled him to avoid being shot.

White smoke and debris emitted from the pit on the ground struck by the bullet.

Garen’s placed his right foot gently on the ground. The tip of his foot flipped up and a stone took flight, gliding into the air before him.

He flicked his right index finger.

Swoosh!

The stone shot through the sky, making a screeching, sharp howl.

A faint sound of a stone hitting on metal and a person shouting in pain came from afar.

Military Flag stared at Garen as though he had seen a ghost. This was way beyond any human limit. Just a stone to take care of a sniper hidden far away with such accuracy and strength was too skillful beyond the boundary.

Even Slayer couldn’t do so!

The crowd on the streets now realized that what happened in the shop was not a film shooting but it was a real deal. Screams were everywhere as people ran for their lives, hiding in places which they thought would be safe though most were escaping as far as they could.

There were a few who were bold beyond death, hiding and recording the scene with their mobiles phones.

In mere minutes, the densely packed streets were emptied. Passing vehicles sped off for their lives and cars from afar detoured away.

The area where Garen and Military Flag occupied was now deserted. The surroundings were empty without a single person in sight.

Majority of the people in the shop took the opportunity to escape. At first, there was one who took flight courageously, and when the remaining people saw him leaving unscathed, they followed suit and rushed out of the shop. Cammy Ning and her two best friends were amongst the crowd and were being tugged and pulled by the escaping, scattered crowd.

While running for their lives, they turned back to look at the direction of Garen and Military Flag.

Cammy Ning and her friends felt their brains were still in a mush. They had yet to gather what was going on. How did a high school classmate become a killer and terrorist in a blink of an eye?

Recalling the fallen armed soldiers, Cammy Ning could not help but shiver.

“Just how many people did the Black Federation send?” Garen and Military Flag were just a meter apart when he questioned. Garen had jarred his opponent’s bones out of its place to the point that he would not be able to move, thus he was not worried of any sudden counter-attacks.

“You can join our Black Federation. We have the best technology to help you enhance your body. We have the best in service, finances, authority, beautiful ladies, whatever you want we have it! As long as you join us, coupled with the support from me and Battle Flag, you will definitely be the strongest Sword Master in history!!” Military Flag tried to convince Garen in turn.

His eyes flickered with a bright glow.

“What can you obtain from Slann? Even if you’re number three at Vulture’s, you wouldn’t hold much authority in quota, right? But it’s different in our Black Federation. You can have your private troops, private island, under the law of Slann, it is forbidden to traffic human but our Black Federation’s unspoken rules, you can have up to four slaves of your own!”

Military Flag tempted.

“Think about it. We are the unrestrained, social world where the strongest survive!! You are best suited in Black Federation! Join us and you will get all that you imagined!”

He was soliciting Garen!

Garen smiled as he looked at him.

“Everything? If I want the Sacred Sigil, will you give it to me?”

“Sacred Sigil?” Military Flag was stunned. “As long as you want it, we will do our best for you! As long as you join us, your power will grow stronger and even if you’re not up to it, we will not take away the resources for your power gaining! Just say the word and you will be the Black Federation’s number three and not just a measly number three in Vulture organization! Think about it, riches, power, beautiful women, as long as you want it, anything is possible!!”

Garen must admit, that Military Flag’s offer and bargain was extremely tempting and he himself was starting to be moved by it.

Compared to Slann, Black Federation was all about the strength. The environment of survival of the fittest suited him. If it weren’t because he has decided to leave this world to head to Lighthouse, he might even agree to it.

But it was a shame that…

“Unfortunately,” Garen shook his head, “although it’s very tempting, I… have no interest.”

He lurched forward and stomped onto Military Flag’s forehead. Boom.

Red blood seeped through Military Flag’s forehead, spewing out red and white liquid that looked like oil.

Without turning back, Garen strode to the direction of the Soul Energy Force. It was obvious that Black Federation was trying to delay time by sending a general like Military Flag. His last speech was probably a tactic in an attempt to save his life and delay time too.

These major characters have plenty up their sleeves with various trump cards emerging one after another. If not because Garen was prepared to leave this world, he may be convinced by Military Flag to rebel.

Glancing at the surrounding empty streets, Garen went forward in the direction of the Soul Energy Force.

As he made his way, sounds of windows closing came from both sides of the street. As Garen speed up passing several streets, crowds gradually emerged. Many did not know who he was. Some were discussing with passersby about the noise heard earlier while others were describing the happenings vividly.

Garen blended into the crowd and walked swiftly towards an alley by the street.

The moment he stepped in, sounds of swooshing laser beams could be heard.

Looking disheveled, Mind Reader was being chased by a man holding a laser welding machine. He skimmed out the exit opposite the alley.

Without wasting another second, Garen dashed out of the alley into another narrow lane. He saw that Mind Reader and his pursuer were reaching the end of the lane and about to make a turn.

Garen was about to chase after them when suddenly heavy footsteps came from behind him. A team of armed personnel caught up to him from the back alley.

Seeing Garen standing there, the men in black aimed their guns on him

“Don’t move!!”

The words had not barely complete when Garen stomped his right foot on the ground.

Kaboom!!!

With a loud crash, the surface of the small lane turned and crumbled. A ripple of quake with Garen’s right foot in the center had overturned front and back.

The soldiers shook from side to side in the continuous loud rumbles. The tremendous quake swept them off their feet and collided with one another. Majority of the soldiers with weaker vitality lost consciousness in a blink of an eye while a stronger minority held on from fainting.

Garen couldn’t be bothered with these people and continued his chase.

“It’s Sword Master Garen! Surround him!!”

A voice shouted from the side.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!!

Muffled gun shots fired at Garen’s side. Some of the bullets hit the wall beside him, leaving hole marks. Some hit him but were blocked effectively by his tough muscles.

Garen snorted coldly. He was not in his best mood given that he was ambushed the moment he charged out of the lane. He waved his arm on the wall and gripped ahold a large block of cement from it, before flinging it onto the soldiers who were lunging to him from the right side of the crossway.

The cement block flew at a high velocity, swooshing through countless people and hitting on the last wall surface. Instantaneously, more than ten people in the small alley lane were penetrated at the chest, no one life was spared.

The lane had fresh blood splattered all over, and smelled sweet and pungent as blood flow like a river from the bodies.

Garen did not bother to stay back and look and headed straight for Mind Reader.

More and more people were getting in his way. In the beginning, it was the men in black from Black Federation, thereafter were some local police and law enforcers. The police were quickly replaced by armed police and finally, soldiers in white appeared. Many of the soldiers had a pattern of a white crab imprinted on their chest.

Chapter 1214: Attainment 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

No one was able to stop Garen from going forth.

As they were in a city, high explosive bombs could not be used while small explosives were no better than snipers against Garen.

Charging ahead, Mind Reader who was in front finally stopped at a field in a small area.

Garen caught up with the man holding the laser welding machine from behind. He stared at Garen with caution.

“Don’t come over!” The man holding the laser welding machine was dressed in a formal suit. Sweating profusely, he was holding Mind Reader as hostage and looking at Garen in panic.

“Come any closer and I’ll kill him!” He tried to mean business and dangled the laser welding machine at Mind Reader’s neck, scaring the latter to paleness.

Garen left behind bloody footprints. It was unknown how many he killed on the way. He killed anyone on sight and anyone who blocked his path, no matter young, old, male or female, was taken care of.

No matter the forces behind, nobody was spared.

Immediately, an army of white soldiers came crashing onto the field through another entrance with their weapons all aimed at Garen. Their leader wore a silver, metal helmet. Gender unknown, this person had long, silver hair and was gazing intensely at Garen.

“Military Flag of the Black Federation was killed by him!” The long, silver hair person said in a dreaded voice.

Two persons walked out from the alleyway behind Garen. They stared at Garen, and shared the same, dreaded fear in their eyes.

“Where’s the woman? Mr. Garen, we have no intention to be enemies. Our aim is that woman!” The two were from a different organization unlike Black Federation nor White Crab, nor any other countries’ forces for that matter. They were the transmigrators’ forces, an organization with the woman who protected Mind Reader as well as the snipers. The plan was that whoever protected Mind Reader would gain the most benefit. With Garen stepping into the picture, they got Military Flag to restrain and delay Garen but nobody expected that Military Flag and his soldiers were taken down in less than ten minutes.

Military Flag and Garen should be experts at the same level. They were elite fighters that once challenged Slayer yet it hasn’t been ten minutes that the defeat was imminent. It was like a dream.

Garen’s combat power severely caused the imbalance between forces.

Hence the remaining parties started discussions to get rid of Garen, the variable element that was a threat to all.

But unfortunately, efforts to encircle and annihilate Garen on the way ended up with the slaughtering of over a hundred elites. There weren’t any more subordinates who were willing to try as it will be suicide.

Under such circumstance, the two could only come out to talk to Garen in the hope he would give up the fight for Mind Reader.

“I don’t really care about your matters,” Garen couldn’t be bothered with these people. “I only want Mind Reader. The rest is up to you.”

He killed everybody who was in his path, regardless if they were from White Crab, Black Federation or even this secret organization. Mind Reader was a key element for him to absorb the Soul Seed Soul Power. Even if Vulture number one was to arrive, it would not pose any difference. No one could stop him from getting Mind Reader.

But now Mind Reader was being held hostage. If he was killed, then all his efforts would be in vain. He would have to head to another venue to seek the reborn Mind Reader. It would be a massive pain in the ass.

“That’s easy, hehe.” The man holding Mind Reader hostage smirked. “Honorable Sword Master, as long as you vanquish these people from White Crab and the two over there, I will release Mind Reader to you. I promise you!!”

The silver-haired person from White Crab was shaken. The person holding Mind Reader was from Black Federation. His fear was realized.

The Sword Master in this city was undefeatable unless he could get Lord Slayer over for help or else no one would be able to stop Garen.

Nobody knew where the two mysterious forces were from, but they were definitely understaffed. Now that they were being threatened, their faces changed, looking nervous.

“Kill two parties of different forces, do you think I’m stupid?” Garen smirked.

“Too bad then. If you don’t follow suit, I will kill Mind Reader,” the man smiled coldly.

“How dare you threaten me?” Garen’s last ‘me’ word dropped sharply.

With a boom, a short sound wave sent a quake. The man holding Mind Reader was hit. The massive sound wave in the shape of a stick struck his head. He instantly saw stars and became sluggish.

In that split second that the man was distracted, Garen stomped his foot, exploding a pit in the cement surface. The counter force saw Garen being pushed to an extreme speed.

Bam!

Garen swept past the hostage-holder and stopped short behind Mind Reader.

Rip!!…

The hostage-holder’s body was torn apart. A large amount of blood flowed endless, dying his clothes red.

“You…!” The hostage-holder did not manage to finish his sentence as he collapsed on his back slowly.

Garen extended his arm and dabbed gently on Minder Reader who was trying to escape.

Mind Reader lost energy in his whole body, Garen carried and tucked him under his armpit and walked out.

Garen chose to leave through the same lane which he came from.

The two persons from unknown forces could only watch Garen leave with eyes wide open. They dared not make any sudden movements.

“Let’s go!” One shouted at the other. The two consciously made way for Garen to walk through before retreating swiftly.

White Crab tactfully chose to retreat at the very beginning. They were different from the rest. White Crab shared a conflict with Garen. If it was not for Garen focusing on capturing Mind Reader, they may not see the light of day again.

Garen’s combat power was far from what they had predicted, beyond anyone’s imagination.

“Lord Slayer will remember your grace,” the silver-haired person from White Crab marked his words before leaving.

“If he is displeased, he can look for me anytime.” Garen did not bother to turn back. He headed straight to where he came from. He needed to depart from here as soon as possible. He has caused quite a negative impact from his killing spree in the city, those from Vulture were already rushing over to receive him.

There was even a high official of the enemy in the local Ocean Capital that could instruct the armed police to stop him. This was Slann, not any other place and the Vulture’s influence should be the largest and strongest here.

Carrying Mind Reader, Garen took large strides leaving the field.

He was quickly met with the incoming troops of special-uniformed army. A team of ten or more people charged over and encircled Garen.

Two mechanized vicious figure dashed over. Their faces changed at the first sight of Garen.

“Sir Sword Master! Please forgive us for coming late to support!!” The two got down on one knee. Both of them started knocking their heads on the ground, causing a string of banging noises and making people jump with it.

The encircling army that wanted to lock and load had now realized that the person before them was the country’s symbol of highest force, Sword Master!

They all took down their weapons.

“Late support?” Garen smiled, “No, it hasn’t been ten minutes from when it happened until now. For you to have such speed and assembly is very good. I am satisfied.”

It was true, he was telling the truth. He did not inform anyone of his trip to Ocean Capital. He quietly joined in the fight and for the local forces in Ocean Capital to react quickly under such circumstance was quite impressive.

“Thank you, sir!” Both of them gut-wrenchingly got up. The Sword Master’s reputation was quite positive among the public but quite the opposite amongst the internal personnel. Those who knew the inside story would know of Garen’s cruelty. In a short time frame of a year, Garen and his subordinates had slaughtered people by the hundreds to strengthen his position and name. Anyone who dared go against him would be wiped off by him, including the local nobles who grew to ranks in a hundred years but destroyed by Garen in three days.

“From now on, all the armed forces of the city are under my instruction.” Garen gently knocked Mind Reader out cold as he said calmly to the duo on their knees.

“Yes!”

The duo answered together.

Garen nodded in satisfaction.

“Ocean Capital is still Vulture’s territory. You can’t just come and go as you please. Don’t you think you should leave something behind?”

He turned to look behind him.

“All troops to take down all soldiers hired by White Crab. Take heed of my instructions! Seal every entrance and exit of the sea and inform the navy to look out and halt any suspicious looking vessel!”

“Yes!!” The two generals responded loudly. They swiftly mobilized to another direction, taking out their mobile phones to communicate the order.

Garen took out his mobile phone to dial Double-Tailed Scorpion’s number.

“It’s time for action.”

He only said one sentence.

“Understood,” Double-Tailed Scorpion had already arranged everything.

Far away, a few black vessels were floating on the ocean surface. The fish-shaped black vessels had a white symbol on them. It was a savage-looking white skeleton.

Slann’s strongest fleet — Skeleton Sea.

Six Skeleton Sea submarines emerged. Their tops broke open and pilotless fighter jets over ten meters long each were lifted up one by one.

Titter titter! Swoosh swoosh swoosh!!

With sounds of taking off, the pilotless fighter jets took flight towards the direction of Ocean Capital. White shuttle-shaped missiles hung below the jets.

In a hidden shipyard somewhere in Ocean Capital, a ship disguised as a merchant ship slowly navigated out of the harbor, blowing its horn loudly.

White Crab’s people were disguised as regular tourists, staring at Ocean Capital from afar. They suffered a major loss this time but Lord Slayer would definitely avenge them!

But this was unrelated to Garen now. Carrying Mind reader, he got in a car prepared earlier to head to Vulture’s branch. Mind Reader was emitting an aura of massive Soul Power. This had Garen finally understanding the core attribute of the Four Great Cornerstones.

It was a Soul Ring that was the same as his!!

Chapter 1215: Soul Ring 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Not bothered with the continuing slaughter, the fighting submarine battleships took off. These were now unrelated to Garen. What he needed to do now was to bring Mind Reader to a safe place for use.

“…” Garen felt this statement was weird but it didn’t matter. His goal was achieved.

The car he was in drove towards Ocean Capital’s airport.

Looking outside the car window, he could see crowds of people gathering to see what the fuss was all about. The people seemed to be oblivious of the danger, thinking that it was far and not exercising any awareness of it. They gathered around to have fun, and it was so packed that there was no end to it. His ears were filled with noises of discussion.

“How unafraid of death,” Garen sighed.

“The people of Ocean Capital have lived in peace for too long plus being one of the vital cities of Slann, they wouldn’t think they will meet with any danger,” the driver smiled as he commented. “Who would have thought that there’d be a killing spree less than a thousand meters away?”

While the driver was talking, he looked through the rear mirror at Garen with respect. Thanks to Garen, Slann’s reputation has grown internationally in recent years.

Slann’s national policy was focused on defense. They would not respond when provoked by other countries but with the birth of a Sword Master, with a support on combat power on the right matters, Vulture could be more forceful.

Almost any event involving the Sword Master would have the enemy at a major loss. The completion of tasks was more than eighty percent. His vicious name was spread far and wide merely in a year.

Garen shook his head and said no more. Beside him lay the unconscious Mind Reader.

He shifted his head to look out the window. The car was moving through the streets at a steady speed. Although crowds were densely packed on both sides of the street, no one was actually pushed out onto the roads as everybody displayed good citizen virtue.

As the car moved forth and was about to leave the jam-packed path, Garen saw the shop which he was having a meal earlier. At the shop’s entrance, a group of youngsters was being questioned by over ten police officers and amongst them were Cammy Ning and her two friends.

Still in a state of shock and with emotions still running high, the trio was describing to the police officers of what happened.

The driver noticed Garen’s line of gaze and followed through.

“Sir, is there a need for an arrangement?”

Garen did not say a word.

******

“I really do not know anything!” Cammy Ning argued. “Please, let us go. We need to go to class. We are students of Ocean University!” She tried to convince the police officer to let them off in advance.

Nobody would want to be dragged into a troublesome matter like this. This sort of event usually meant trouble for there would be endless questioning, harassment from the media and continuous requests for media interviews. Their studies were held up, her personal plans were held up, she had not even recovered from the pant-wetting emotions when she was stressed beyond exhaustion by the judgmental interrogations.

Cammy Ning really wanted to return and rest. It was not only her. Her three best friends were equally exhausted and in fear of the police officers’ constant interrogation. They were unable to leave this place until they were cleared of being suspects of soliciting conspiracy.

“… Alright, inform your family and friends to come over. There are a few items to verify.”

In the midst of full on interrogation, Cammy Ning only seemed to register this last sentence.

Inform family and friends!!??

Hearing this, Cammy Ning and her friends froze.

Once matters reached this level, what difference did it make with those who broke the law and were told to inform their family members to bail them out?

If this were to spread to school, even if they were victims, gossip was a fearful thing. In the course of gossip spreading, they may as well end up as suspects and there may be a record on her file.

“Couldn’t you bend the rules?” Feeling fragile, Cammy Ning hadn’t finished her request when the police officer cut her off.

“I’m sorry, as your involvement concerned national security so you cannot leave police surveillance before you are cleared of any suspicions.” The police officer was apologetic. “But don’t worry, once we confirm that you have no involvement, we will then…”

Cammy Ning and her friends couldn’t bring themselves to listen to what he had to say. They felt their ears buzzing a blur and felt only chill in their hearts.

The only thing that came to mind: They were doomed.

It was then a police supervisor in black walked over. Sizing up the three ladies from top to bottom, he frowned slightly and spoke reluctantly.

“Alright, let them go.”

The police officer was stunned while the three girls thought they heard wrong. They stared at the police supervisor in surprise.

“I do not wish to repeat myself,” the police supervisor blurted coldly with a straight face. He sized the three girls from top to bottom again before striding away with his hands crossed behind his back.

The investigating police officer was dumbfounded but obeyed the instruction and started to process the release procedure.

Cammy Ning was stumped by the sudden change of events.

“Quick, look over there!” Her female companion’s sudden shriek had her returned to senses. She looked towards her bestie’s direction of gaze and saw a black, fancy sedan slowly driving away.

The window was half opened and in it sat a man. He was smiling at her direction, bidding a farewell gesture to her.

“It’s Kong Xiaofei!?” Cammy Ning stared blankly at the man inside the car, feeling the drama of life. At first, she thought that he was a young jobless vagrant and now he was an important person, a personnel of high ranking.

The three girls stopped talking. For a moment, she felt down in the dumps but the other two became ecstatic.

“See that? That Kong Xiaofei is a hidden big shot!”

“We initially thought that he was… These big shots like to act weak? Must they give others a scare?”

“I think he probably is into Cammy, they are high school classmates after all, maybe…”

Her two besties started to discuss enthusiastically. They tossed aside their earlier decadent and worry and started to guess Garen’s identity and background.

The sedan was quick to drive out of sight. Cammy Ning slowly watched the car leave without saying a word. She felt an indescribable odd feeling as if life was a dream, a peculiar yet absurd dream.

“Ai ya!” One of her besties suddenly exclaimed.

“What’s wrong?”

“We forgot to ask Kong Xiaofei for his contact number!”

Cammy Ning suddenly felt that her two best friends were of poor taste yet she could not help feeling a tinge of regret.

She stared at the exaggerated car plate number at the rear of the sedan from afar.

“Perhaps we will never see each other again.” She suddenly had this feeling.

******

Vulture Headquarters.

In a specially sealed secret room.

Throwing Mind Reader into the secret room, Garen entered the room himself and started to undress.

“What is this odd feeling?” He felt chills on his back.

He turned his head and saw his secretary, Double-Tailed Scorpion, staring at him with an odd expression.

“I… I did not see anything!” Double-Tailed Scorpion quickly turned his head and muttered under his breath.

“…” Garen’s face grew black.

He thought about it.

“Bring the low-temperature cooler box over.”

“Understood,” Double-Tailed Scorpion immediately left and ordered his subordinates.

The low-temperature cooler box was moved in and connected to power supply. He dismantled the surveillance camera in the secret room at the same time.

The heavy metal door to the secret room was shut. Garen threw his top away and looked at Mind Reader who was unconscious on the ground.

“Soul Ring…” Soul Power poured into his eyes and he could clearly see the revolving structure of Soul Ring on Mind Reader.

It was a complete Soul Ring structure of five Soul Seeds! Much stronger than his current Soul Ring by a large margin.

“Such an envious sight. I struggled so long to only obtain four Soul Seeds and here the Four Great Cornerstones naturally has a Soul Ring of five Soul Seeds!” Garen shook his head.

Through thorough observation, he realized that Mind Reader’s Soul Ring was not his to control. The Soul Power that emitted was scarce. Mind Reader’s Soul Ring of five Soul Seeds on many levels was structured naturally. The nature of the Soul Power did not share one bit of Mind Reader’s soul characteristics.

“In other words, the supposed Four Great Cornerstones was the house of the Soul Ring. They are like a vessel that housed a terrifying Soul Power that could impact an entire planet. Just by the little Soul Power emitted naturally by the Soul Ring, produced many extraordinary phenomena. From that, one could see how horrifyingly scary this sort of natural Soul Ring could be.”

Garen came to a conclusion.

The Soul Ring of the Four Great Cornerstones could not be controlled as liberally as his but it was far more powerful and terrifying than his Soul Ring. Just the reserves of the Soul Power were five times his Soul Ring. It really was a huge monster!

“No wonder the Four Great Cornerstones is the core of this world. They bear the weight of four different origins of this world,” Garen quickly established the most likely model mechanism of the Four Great Cornerstones.

“Then how could the Soul Power be absorbed?” Obtaining an outline of the situation, Garen started to venture into ways to absorb the Soul Ring within Mind Reader.

“If it’s just slowly absorbing the wandering Soul Power, then over a hundred years wouldn’t be enough to finish it up,” Garen struggled to analyze. “There are a few ways. One is to stimulate the Soul Ring so that a large amount of Soul Power would be released for me to absorb. This way has its certain risk. If the degree of strength is not pre-determined and its force was overstimulated, then it may possibly cause Minder Reader to die and reborn elsewhere, losing the chance to absorb.”

Garen was quick to deny this method.

“Then the second type, pollute,” he walked one round around Mind Reader. “My Soul Power is mixed with traits of the Hellfrost Peacock Mother and could pollute the Cold Chaos. Moreover, the Hellfrost Peacock Mother and Nine-Headed Dragon shared an engulfing characteristic. It could, at a certain level, pollute the other Soul Power to one with a characteristic closer to its own and at the same time, lessen the digestive burden of engulfing and absorbing. This may take around half a year.”

Chapter 1216: Soul Ring 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This fella was a ticking time bomb. If the Soul Ring exploded by any chance, not only would he end up with nothing, his own Soul Ring may be damaged too.

So Garen knew that he must play it cautious.

“There is another way, that is to engulf between the Soul Rings as a whole. This would be the fastest but also most dangerous method. The natural Soul Ring has no awareness control but my Soul Ring has awareness and could execute engulfment. It’s just like two troops of armies, one is a wandering ten thousand men without a leader while the other has only two thousand men but a strong leader. With the right strategy, it should be possible to engulf. There must not be any disruption in between otherwise the two Soul Rings will erupt together. My generations of effort would come to waste.”

Garen used the Energy Machine Imprint to roughly estimate the time needed. It would be around forty-five days.

“So to say, this is the risk that I have to take…”

Looking at Mind Reader before him, Garen’s eyes were decisive.

“If that’s the case, then I should nip all trouble in the bud and absorb the Soul Ring.”

The only thing that could threaten him in this world would be Slayer. As he wasn’t going to absorb the Soul Ring right away, Garen sat beside Mind Reader with his legs crossed, absorbing part of the Soul Power spread by him.

Even with such minimal absorption, Garen could sense his body strengthening obviously.

Boundless energy was surging and tiding in his body. Garen slowly closed his eyes to feel the comfortable sensation from the Soul Power surging into his body.

Even in an unconscious state, Mind Reader’s face became pale.

******

“Negotiate with Garen now and have him release Mind Reader. The Four Great Cornerstones are not for a country or a party to monopolize. He simply can’t! Nobody can!!”

Black Federation’s highest administrative office — Rock Colossus Building.

In the top levels of the black building sculptured as a giant, a few speakers were in a heated debate.

“Lord Military Flag is murdered and now we’re left with Battle Flag as our strongest. The Black Federation has lost a world-class general and cannot sustain a bigger loss! Otherwise, our national security will face a threat,” one of the speakers representing the north region solemnly spoke.

“But if we don’t avenge this, it’s a national humiliation!” Another coldly blurted.

“Out of all people, we would very much want Sword Master Garen to give him up but what do we have to pressure him to do so? This is the key.” Black Federation’s highest leader was a black man with tanned skin. He had his hands crossed behind his back and had shoulder-length black hair. His strong body physique gave a sense of tough and no-nonsense feeling.

“We can use the import policy to restrict Slann’s export, aiming their commerce.”

“We can deploy security forces in the region and establish a base to enforce military clamp down.”

“What do you think, Battle Flag?” The highest leader looked at Battle Flag who remained silent.

Battle Flag pondered for a while to tidy his train of thoughts before opening up.

“Slann isn’t monolithic. Capturing Mind Reader doesn’t bring them any actual benefits. I think issuing threats should be enough to force Garen to give him up.”

“Indeed. Vulture is only a subsidiary organization of Slann’s national security department. Compared to our special operations team, they don’t hold much say. This is possible to realize,” the highest leader nodded.

“Then who will be putting this plan into effect?”

“I will,” Battle Flag said with a low voice. “This matter began with our special operations team and should end with us.”

“Has the new Military Flag been elected?”

“Mm, King Thunderclap is in charge of Military Flag’s position,” Battle Flag answered.

“King Thunderclap…? Alright,” the highest leader and the other speakers fell silent at the mention of this name.

******

“What! Mind Reader’s been captured!? And it’s the doing of Minister Garen?!!” Yuria burst out.

Looking at the mysterious woman in front of him, he encountered her a few times so he knew that she has been on the move with Mind Reader but he didn’t think that this encounter meant major news.

He had met with Mind Reader earlier during the day and was now hearing this nightmare in the evening.

He traveled miles to Ocean Capital because he could not trace the whereabouts of his sister and mother and wanted to borrow Mind Reader’s abilities to seek them. Mind Reader agreed readily and though both parties were not in touch for long, he could feel his sincerity.

He could sense that brother Mind Reader was not a bad person. He was just an ordinary person whose fate disrupted his life.

“I’m here in hope that you could contact Sword Master. What is his aim? You were once his disciple and should be familiar with his character,” the woman solemnly responded.

“Minister…” Yuria couldn’t put his finger on Garen’s personality. Now that he remembered, he felt that he was always buried behind layers and layers of fog that could not be interpreted.

The first genius for over three thousand years? The strongest existence in sword mastery and martial arts? The first expert of Slann?

Names after names were coined on him and taking apart these appealing names and glorified battle achievements, he suddenly realized that he actually never knew who Garen was.

“He… is always calm as though nothing could bother him. There’s always a certainty to him when executing matters and would not resort to meaningless issues,” Yuria sensed the situation was getting out of hand. “Minister must have his reason for capturing Mind Reader. No one could ever change or stop whatever he’s doing.”

“Any chance on finding out Sword Master’s goal?” The woman was worried.

Yuria had come in contact with Mind Reader a few times and felt that he was a pitiful man tied down by fate. Both of them could be considered friends and now his friend was captured by his teacher. His emotion was running heavy.

“I’ll try but I can’t promise anything,” he thought about it before agreeing.

******

“Lord Slayer! Only you can settle this matter.”

In a submarine in the deep ocean.

A blurry portrait with sounds was reflected on a transparent glass screen.

There was only one person in the submarine. Slayer was sitting alone in front of the screen, holding a long black sickle. This was the latest weapon technology that he had gotten ahold of. It could wield his ability by eighty percent.

“The Sword Master is strong,” Slayer was unmoved. “The remuneration you’re offering is not enough.”

“I know it’s not enough,” the person on the screen replied in a soft voice. “But this is an order from Qin.”

“Qin?” Slayer’s face changed. His originally listless stature was replaced with erecting his body straight, “are you sure?”

“The written confirmation will soon reach you. Latest by tonight,” The portrait answered.

“When do I depart?” Slayer was clear-cut.

“One week later, Wednesday noon. You’ll need to disguise yourself to get close to Sword Master. Be careful, he’s always on high alert.”

“I know,” Slayer nodded.

“Compared to a year ago, Sword Master is stronger!”

Slayer was silent. His eyes were shut as he started to rest.

******

Five days later…

“What brings you back to see me?” Garen looked at Yuria gently, who was in front of him. “Any news on Xiaojie and Light Path yet?”

Both of them were sitting in a room by a coffee table. Someone served them tea.

Yuria had an awkward look on his face.

“No, not yet.

“I heard that you have captured Mind Reader, so I was…”

“Mind Reader is well,” Garen smiled. “He has good food and good drinks. Apart from going out, he has access to the whole base and everything provided to him. Why? You wish to borrow Mind Reader’s ability?”

Yuria couldn’t bring himself to say it out loud. He lowered his head and pretended to take a sip of tea. The borrow was an excuse. The real motive was to see if Mind Reader was okay. They were friends, after all.

“I suppose you could,” Garen did not reject. Now that Mind Reader was under house arrest, he himself was under a lot of pressure. At least he knew now why other countries, organizations, and forces would rather monitor than arrest.

“Mind Reader seemed to know a lot of inside stories. A lot of valuable information could be obtained from him. It’s just that…”

“Just that what?”

“It’s just that, your matter could be a little complicated,” Garen said, weighing his words slowly.

“Complicated?” Yuria became slightly emotional. He knew that Garen must have found some new leads which led him to say as such.

Garen indeed knew some new information, some intel which had him shocked as well. He looked at Yuria before him. He did not know where to begin.

“This information was what I obtained from Mind Reader. I didn’t think the truth would turn out so I hadn’t told you…”

“Lord, Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest have arrived,” Double-Tailed Scorpion’s voice was heard from Garen’s hidden earpiece.

Garen paused what he was about to say to Yuria, “hang on, your teacher Nine-Tailed has arrived.”

Yuria calmed himself down and nodded in comprehension. His Adam’s apple wavered as he suppressed his emotions and stood up.

“I’ll excuse myself.”

“Mm.”

Garen nodded.

He knew why Nine-Tailed Fox was visiting him.

Mind Reader possessed the original Four Great Cornerstones’ Sacred Sigil and at the same time, it was one that was most wanted by many transmigrators, the ability to read minds. This included Kong Xinxue. So their purpose here must be to replicate Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil.

“The replication of the Sacred Sigil should be a Sacred Sigil stripping technique. If I could master it, perhaps I could separate the natural Soul Ring and achieve complete absorption,” Garen guessed.

Recalling the few Soul Crystals he absorbed earlier, he indistinctly felt this guesswork may be correct.

Shortly, the waiter took away the tea and served coffee.

Nine-Tailed Fox, Kong Xinxue, Li Hua and another two transmigrators strode into the room. Each of them gave a complicated look at Garen.

“Welcome.”

Garen smiled as he got up.

Chapter 1217: Absorb 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What are you planning?” Nine-Tailed Fox asked softly the moment she sat down after entering the room.

“What are you talking about?” Garen acted dumb.

“Stop playing dumb. We all know the Mind Reader is in your hand.” The red-haired lady Yuan Xing was obviously impatient as she did not beat around the bush. “Why don’t you open a price? What do you want in exchange for us to duplicate him?”

Yuan Xing was a boring uncle in her last life and she was used to speaking without beating around the bushes. Her greatest feature in this life was having a good-natured appearance but her personality was out of the bag the moment she opened her mouth. The Qi Household owned an extremely huge organization across the Red Nation and Slann and they had an incredibly huge amount of wealth.

“Tell us. How much do you need in exchange for us to duplicate the Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil.” She, again, did not beat around the bush and went straight into the main topic.

“What is your offer?” Garen questioned back. While he did not mind letting these people duplicate the Sacred Sigil, it was not to be done without any incurring cost. They had to pay a price for it.

“Money is not something you lack with your current social standing and we pale in comparison against you in terms of authority and power. However, there is one thing that you’ll definitely want.” Yuan Xing, who was from a business household knew how to capture her opponent’s desire.

“What item?” It was Garen’s first time dealing with Yuan Xing. He had only been interacting with Kong Xinxue and Nine-Tailed Fox all these while. He stared curiously at this red-haired girl in a black goth-themed tunic dress. What else could be effective against him who had already achieved so much? Furthermore, it sounded very important from her tone too.

“Contribution Points.” Yuan Xing stated the obvious.

“Unfortunately, I’ve already accumulated one year worth of Contribution Points with my current position. Are you sure you have enough Contribution Points to buy the Sacred Sigil?” Garen smiled.

“This thing is extremely useful and you’ll never think that you have too many of them. Furthermore, the Lighthouse has information related to the Origin of the Mother Stream and you can only view them if you have enough Contribution Points. The Mother Stream, which is one of the Thirteen Ultimate Origins, is one of the largest strongest existence in this limitless universe. Lighthouse is very fortunate that it had one senior recording down the related information. If you truly wish to reach the True Soul Level or beyond it, then it is a must-read.” Yuan Xing was confident.

“One of the Thirteen Ultimate Origin?” It was the first time Garen had heard of such a theory. “Are you saying that excluding the Mother Stream, there are still thirteen existences that are just as strong?!”

“It’s what we have observed thus far. These thirteen existences are categorized in a level where its true strength could not be measured and nobody knows how many of them with similar caliber are out there,” Yuan Xing explained.

“Yuan Xing is one of the hobbyists who often visit the Lighthouse’s information vault so there is no need to doubt the accuracy of her intel. You can always confirm the legitimacy of the Intel anytime.” Nine-Tailed Fox vouched for her calmly on the side.

“How many points do I need to read the record?” Garen’s interest swelled up.

“One million points.”

Garen’s heart skipped a beat.

“From the very beginning until now, you have accumulated some ten thousands Contribution Points at best. Having a glimpse of such a record would cost you a million points!”

“We are willing to pay you a hundred thousand to duplicate the Sacred Sigil once.” Yuan Xing said confidently. “This amount is more than enough to hire a powerhouse to snatch the person away from you. However, we will give you an opportunity since we are on good terms and get along rather well. We are willing to pay you to duplicate the Sacred Sigil.”

“How many of you want to duplicate it?” Garen did not mind her slightly arrogant tone and started asking the number of people wanting to duplicate it.

“Two.” Yuan Xing sat up straight as she gave a sneaky nailed-it expression towards Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue. “Ah Xue and I.”

“I will only charge Ah Xue’s duplication for fifty thousand points, but I want your Sacred Sigil’s duplication method.” Garen started bargaining.

“Deal.” Kong Xinxue nodded in conclusion. Since she was the main person who decided the overall situation, she would naturally have the authority to decide for the team.

“Do you want to duplicate it now or?” Garen stood up vigorously and effectively.

“It would be best if we can to avoid any unforeseen circumstances.” Yuan Xing smiled.

“Follow me then.” Garen, too, wanted to obtain the method as soon as he could to duplicate the Sacred Sigil. As he brought them out of the guest room, he whispered to one of the soldiers to inform Yuria to return home and come back some other time in the future.

The lot then walked through a white corridor before reaching an open-air corridor, walking deeper near the edge of the small garden.

They soon reached a spacious indoor movie theatre and saw Mind Reader watching a movie alone.

The large movie theatre which could fit up to hundreds of people only had Mind Reader in it and the rest of the seats were vacant.

The light from the movie shone on Mind Reader’s face as he was seated down with a bag of popcorn in his hand. Despite staring at the screen quietly, one could see his mind was drifted elsewhere from his gaze. At that moment, this middle-aged man gave off a lifeless vibe.

“Still worried about your son?” Garen walked in as he spoke loudly. “Don’t worry about it. I have already found some hints that would lead me to him.”

The Mind Reader looked at Garen from afar.

“Why have you come again?”

“To help you,” Garen responded with a smile on his face.

“Help me?”

“Of course. These people are here to help you,” Garen explained.

“Are they here to have an orgy with me?” Mind Reader mocked as he curled his lips.

“Go to hell!” “Filth!”

Yuan Xing, Nine-Tailed Fox, and the rests put up an atrocious expression on their face.

Perhaps it was coincidental as all of them were truly female. Nine-Tailed Fox, Kong Xinxue, Yuan Xing, Li Hua and finally Xi Yuan. They were not just any women, they were all above average as each of them had their own qualities in which those fake women whose beauty were created via makeup could hope to compare.

Garen was not affected by Mind Reader as he had already gotten used to Mind Reader’s rejection.

“They can help you to weaken and rid the Sacred Sigil out of your body.”

Skepticism could be seen in Mind Reader’s gaze after hearing those words.

“I understand that you don’t believe me at all but it will be proven to you.”

Garen leaped at least ten meters to the front and appeared beside Mind Reader before he finished speaking. He then gently tapped his head with his palm.

The latter then rolled his eyes and passed out.

“What should we do next?”

Garen looked at Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest to realize that each of them had white, long, thin needles in their hands.

“We need a quiet room.” Nine-Tailed Fox said solemnly.

**************

Inside the secret chamber.

Garen stood at one corner as he looked at these ladies undressing Mind Reader, leaving nothing behind except for a short underwear.

Then, the five ladies changed into an extremely thin, black, full body dress without wearing anything inside. These five ladies were surprisingly calm as if everything was in the norm despite Garen observing them.

However, upon closer observation, Nine-Tailed Fox was the only one among them that was not embarrassed. The remaining four were having goosebumps everywhere.

“I’ll only demonstrate it twice. It’s your problem whether you understood it or not.” Nine-Tailed Fox told Garen calmly.

“Fine.” Garen nodded as he activated the recording ability via his Energy Machine Imprint to the maximum. The Energy Machine Imprint was kept close most of the time to conserve his Soul Energy as the energy source of this item is the Soul Energy. However, it could record down Nine-Tailed Fox’s every single movement, including the change in Soul Energy’s frequency and amplitude once it was activated.

Without further ado, Nine-Tailed Fox bent over and gently aimed at Mind Reader’s forehead with the near a half a meter long white, thin needle. Then, she stabbed him without any mercy.

Pew.

A soft noise rang as Yuan Xing and Xi Yuan could not help but look away as they did not wish to witness the scene.

The thin needle instantly pierced through Mind Reader’s brain from the forehead and out from the back of his head before making another soft noise as it hit the ground.

Without any change in expression, Nine-Tailed Fox then took out another white thin needle as she calmly aimed at one of the Mind Reader’s eyes. She then pressed it down with her palm after the precise aim.

The thin needle pierced his eyeball and came out from the back of his head once more. This sent the chill down the spines for the four of them.

Xi Yuan who did not have any experience in killing could not help but to give off a cold yelp.

“The third one.” Nine-Tailed Fox took out another thin needle and aimed at the other eye.

It pierced through the other eye in a similar fashion.

A thin stream of white red blood started oozing out from the edge of the needles.

Then, Nine-Tailed Fox took out a brush and a small bottle of blood color liquid. She then opened the bottle, revealing a faint smell of plasma.

“This is a special blood plasma made from a hundred and seventy-two types of blood and you can only buy it from the Lighthouse Trades. If you wish to duplicate the Sacred Sigil as well, you’ll have to buy it yourself. I estimate that I will have a lot of leftovers, probably about five to six bottles with me after I’m done. You would exhaust one bottle with every use and you’ll probably fail at least ten times before succeeding once. Hence, despite the fact that one bottle of blood can be used a lot of times, one can typically only achieve success once per bottle. It’s very common to fail as well if luck is not on your side.”

She then took the brush and dyed it with blood as she started to draw an image on the Mind Reader’s chest.

In no time, a realistic lotus was drawn on the Mind Reader’s chest.

“I’ll start now.” Nine-Tailed Fox signaled Yuan Xing, and Xi Yuan stepped forward and step on one of Mind Reader’s hand.

Yuan Xing then stepped on the other hand while Nine-Tailed Fox and Li Hua both stepped on Mind Reader’s legs.

“Let’s start.” the five women started exchanging glances among each other.

At the same time, Nine-Tailed Fox shouted a one-word syllable.

” Li ^1 (Strength)!”

Buzz!!

In an instant, the Blood Sigil on Mind Reader’s chest started evaporating into a blood mist between Kong Xinxue’s legs.

As Mind Reader’s skin returned to its original skin tone, the black striation appeared once more in the form of a sun.

The black sun striation then popped out from the skin and glowed as it plunged into the blood mist, merging together into one.

Buzz!!

Another sun shaped striation jumped out from the Sacred Sigil and flew into the blood mist.

What followed along was the third sun, the fourth, the fifth!!

A series of striations kept entering the blood mist, which started to twist about. It then started to form into the sun-shaped striation similar to the Sacred Sigil as it levitated in the middle of the air.

Kong Xinxue then turned her back towards Garen as she pulled the zip down on her shirt, revealing her skin which was covered by a thin layer of black silk-like tight shirt.

Pew!!

The Sun-like striation which was formed from the blood mist flew into her chest and intensively imprinted on her body.

Ah!!!

Kong Xinxue screamed. She raised her head as she tried to resist the intense agony.

“Ah Xue!! Hold it together!” Nine-Tailed Fox screamed with a stern look on her face.

Chapter 1218: Absorb 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Mind Reader who was lying on the ground started twitching and jerking greatly at the same time.

The four women seemed to have a hard time trying to restrain Mind Reader’s struggle.

On the other hand, it was a completely different experience for Garen standing by the side.

A huge amount of Mind Reader’s Soul Energy gushed into Kong Xinxue’s body like a flash flood. Even Garen would be slightly frightened by the impact of such a huge amount of Soul Energy as it had almost reached the limit of how much pain he could endure. This might even cause him to be unable to digest them properly and it would be worse for Kong Xinxue who was just a commoner.

“It’s obvious that the cause of the extreme pain is not from the physical body but the direct alteration towards the soul when new energy is added in.” Garen understood fully well how intense the pain was as he had experienced it before in the past. If one were to say the pain from a physical body had an upper limit, then the pain cast upon the soul will never have an upper limit.

Time passed by as the five girls were in the situation for more than ten minutes before things gradually calmed down.

The blood mist had fully entered Kong Xinxue’s body.

Thud.

Kong Xinxue fell to the ground as her knees gave in whereas the other four were drenched in sweat as if their physical strength had been robbed away from their bodies.

“A portion of the stress cast upon Kong Xinxue from the Soul Energy has been given towards the rest of them during the extraction process.” Garen could see everything clearly. Garen, unlike the rest who could not see what actually transpired during the process, had his eyes nourished by the Soul Energy. In addition to him achieving the realm of Soul Rings, he could clearly see the changes in the Soul Energy.

The whole ritual ended swiftly.

Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest held Kong Xinxue up. She was fully drenched in sweat from head to toe. Her body’s contour was vaguely shown through her drenched shirt.

“This is your reward.” Nine-Tailed Fox took out her communication device.

Garen, too, took out his communication device. Both of them then connected their devices together, validated their passwords and Soul’s Core. Nine-Tailed Fox then transferred a hundred thousand contribution points over upon validation.

“This is the ink I have brought along. I still have two bottles left. The original plan was to duplicate two Sacred Sigil at one go but I didn’t expect the duplication process to be so exhausting.” Nine-Tailed Fox said tiredly. She then took out another two bottles of blood red ink and passed it to Garen.

“Is Ah Xue going to be fine?” Garen was worried. Despite the fact that they had distanced themselves lately, they were still siblings in this world.

“She’s fine. Don’t worry about it. Everything went along smoothly as planned.” Nine-Tailed Fox smiled. “Alright. We have to go now. I’ll come back and duplicate the Sacred Sigil another time.”

“Anytime.” Garen smiled as he looked at the five of them being led out by Double-Tailed Scorpion to change their clothes.

He then walked towards Mind Reader as he stared quietly at the Sacred Sigil on his chest.

The original Sacred Sigil was a black sun.

“The process may be complicated towards a commoner but it’s child’s play for me.” Garen grabbed hold of MInd Reader’s neck with just one hand. His hand was big enough to grab hold of Mind Reader’s neck as he held it up in mid-air without any effort.

Upon closer inspection towards the Sacred Sigil, Garen realized that this item seemed to be rooted into his skin as there were many weird black lines which spanned towards his shoulders around the black circle.

He reached out his hand to touch it and found out that there was no protrusion at all. It was not something that had grown out of his skin but something which had fused itself with his body instead.

Nine-Tailed Fox’s every action had been recorded down by the Energy Machine Imprint and Garen was able to fully replicate each and every step. However, what he wanted was not purely duplication but the theory and analysis behind it.

Garen stood there for a full thirty minutes, holding up Mind Reader by his neck. He came to his senses after Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest left.

“I’ve understood the basic theory behind it. It’s impossible to achieve it without this blood ink. Truly amazing!” Garen could not help but to praise the powerhouse who thought of this solution.

Lighthouse did have many hidden talents.

The structure of Soul Ring was similar to that of a tall building. It was similar to having an additional floor when a Soul Seed was added. The building would be more stable and massive if it had more levels.

However, the key towards the Sacred Sigil’s duplication was to make use of the blood ink’s quality as an incredibly sharp giant sword to cut off the building’s highest level while causing minimal injury towards the Sacred Sigil.

The original Sacred Sigils which the Four Great Cornerstones possessed naturally had their Soul Ring supplied endlessly by the universe. The external source would immediately heal the damage done towards it and they were basically no threat towards any injury.

They would revert back to normal by just reincarnating once if they were fully destroyed.

As he pondered, Garen was very tempted. If he were to able to safely absorb the Soul Energy from the Soul Ring, it would be the best plan for him to obtain a huge amount of Soul Energy within a short amount of time.

He decided to act immediately.

He single-handedly opened up a bottle of blood ink and pressed it on Mind Reader’s chest as he started moving it along the black sun’s striation. His precision far surpassed that of Nine-Tailed Fox’s. Similar to the most precise computer, there was not a single error and even the thickness was completely identical.

The blood ink striation was finished in seconds.

Garen recalled Nine-Tailed Fox shouting to shake the Soul Energy. He did not do so as he was able to control the Soul Energy as well. He used his Energy Machine Imprint to mimic the pulsation of the Soul Energy as he started to shake Mind Reader’s natural Soul Ring.

Boom!

In that instant, the blood mist flowed out of the Mind Reader’s chest and stopped between Garen and the former’s chest.

Kaboom!! Garen was the only one able to hear the Soul Energy flowing out tremendously within the intense trembling as it hit against his chest.

The blood mist kept changing its form, a series of Sun-like Sacred Sigil kept flying out, entering the blood mist. The one at the back kept pushing forward even the sun at the front had yet to disappear into the blood mist.

Hundreds of sun-like striations stacked together in a line, connecting the blood mist and Mind Reader together.

“Lin!” A superimposed and muddy voice rang inside the secret chamber. The voice consisted of countless of people stacking together. The voices of the young, old, male and female gave off the same note.

However, Garen did not open his mouth at all. In fact, he did not even make any noise. It was from the intense fluctuations from the air caused by the overwhelmingly powerful Soul Energy.

Pew!!

In a blink of an eye, the blood mist entered Garen’s chest.

Whoosh!! A strong air current spread about everywhere with Garen as the epicenter. The air current kept moving about within the secret chamber, blowing Garen’s hair messily.

His face was expressionless as he tried to feel the large amount of Soul Energy entering his body like a flash flood.

There was not a single trace of Mind Reader’s Soul Ring being extracted at all. This made Garen even more impressed with the transmigrator who invented this technique. One would not be able to perform such a precise surgery-like procedure without having a deep understanding and confidence towards the Soul.

Strength… An endless amount of strength…

Garen could not help but raise his head as he felt the fifth Soul Seed forming inside his Soul Ring so quickly that he could see it with his naked eyes. Although it was the weakest transparent Soul Seed, this embryonic Soul Seed was absorbing all of the Soul Energy pouring into his body. It then grew from the size of a yellow pea into the size of an egg as it solidified quickly.

He closed his eyes, ignoring the time as he appreciated the huge amount of Soul Energy entering his body which would become the fifth Soul Seed.

The fifth Soul Seed was quickly filled up to the point where it could not absorb any additional Soul Energy as it turned into a spherically transparent crystal. The additional Soul Energy then started to pour into the other Soul Seeds that had yet to be filled up.

The first Soul Seed – Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique (Blue). The Soul Seed was spinning as it gave off a faint blue glow. After absorbing a huge amount of Soul Energy, the blue glow started fading away as it turned into a transparent crystal.

The second Soul Seed – Holy Phoenix Demonic Book (Black Gold). Soul Seed with black gold color was one of the weakest Soul Seed. After absorbing a huge amount of Soul Energy, its volume increased as it became transparent.

The Third Soul Seed – Hellfrost Peacock Soul Seed (White). This was Garen’s strongest Soul Seed as it contained the inspiration and knowledge to threaten the entire planet. If a commoner were able to get his hands on this Soul Seed and entirely erased Garen’s imprint, he would instantly become a Planet Level powerhouse equivalent to the King of Crystal! He would become one of the strongest powerhouses in many other worlds even if he were not in the Mech World! He would be able to reach the allowable limits of the universe.

This Soul Seed was not absorbing the Soul Energy at all. In fact, it kept releasing a huge amount of white Soul Energy as it tried to corrupt the original Sacred Sigil’s Soul Energy.

Chirp!!

The sharp chirp of the Peacock could be heard all of the sudden in Garen’s conscience.

The white peacock queen came out from the Soul Seed as it bit onto the colorless Soul Energy. The white chill behind it then started to form into layers of wings made from ice crystals.

“Stop.” Garen manually controlled the peacock. In a sense, the peacock represented himself as its nature was to absorb all external energy coming into the body. Naturally, it would be possible to directly control such ability as well.

Hiss… the Peacock was dispersed forcibly as it turned into white gas and diluted by the colorless Soul Energy that kept pouring in.

Garen stared at the whole event indifferently.

The Soul Ring was filled up and the Soul Energy flowing out from the Soul Ring started to become more and more powerful.

His body started to obtain a huge amount of nutrient. His body which was originally lacking in Soul Energy started to obtain so much that a new Soul Seed started to form as it attempted to form a second Soul Ring!

Slap.

Suddenly, Garen forcefully cut off the Soul Energy’s channel.

He looked at the Mind Reader in his hand tiredly. He could not simply absorb everything since Nine-Tailed Fox and the others would still come and duplicate the Sacred Sigil Once more. He thought that it would be best for him to not let the others knew that he had the natural ability to absorb the Sacred Sigil before he obtained all the loot in one fell swoop.

He looked at the Sacred Sigil on the Mind Reader’s chest and he could see that it had been slightly faded.

Garen could not stop himself from smiling as he looked at his own Attribute Pane.

“It’s so much better to rob the wealth from others than rightfully collecting the inspiration on my own…” He lamented from his heart.

Chapter 1219: Lurk 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few days had passed since.

Nine-Tailed Fox and the others had come to the base for the second time. They had brought along a girl who Garen was familiar with as well – Night Water.

It was the girl he had caught sneaking around his back looking for Soul Crystals.

Night Water’s jaw dropped the moment she saw Garen. The Soul Energy released from Garen’s body was similar to the chill released when an extremely cool refrigerator was opened as it kept flowing freely from both sides.

“You… You monster!? In such a short amount of time…” Garen gave her a warning gaze before she finished speaking. It was the kind of sly smile that one would make before killing someone else.

Night Water shut her mouth the moment she realized it.

Despite being an expert in the Mother Stream System, she was technically only a Guardian Level. These five classes, the Guard, Division, General Army, and Demon Lord was the Ancient Endor’s general categorization towards the Void Creature.

Each Level would require a tremendous amount of time to train and master to achieve. If Garen did not have the Natural Attribute Ability and were to train in the traditional way, he would require at least thousands of years to train before achieving such a level.

“What’s wrong?” Nine-Tailed Fox and the others asked while they were preparing the duplication procedure.

“Nothing…” Night Water barely put on a smile. “I was just thinking how much Garen had changed. Hahaha!!” She started laughing stupidly as she found an excuse that was barely believable.

“Alright, follow me, everyone.” Garen continued giving Night Water the hypocritical smile as he brought them to the secret chamber where Mind Read was kept in.

It was the same procedure as before. However, the duplication was for Nine-Tailed Fox instead.

One could say that she had given up on the Slayer’s Sacred Sigil as the probability of obtaining it was very low. Furthermore, Mind Reader was literally in front of her and was very well within reach. There was no need to risk her life to obtain Slayer’s Sacred Sigil.

The procedure was very successful as it went much smoother than last time.

Similar to Kong Xinxue, Nine-Tailed Fox was very weak after the procedure was completed. However, she was better than Kong Xinxue as she did not faint. It seemed that she had a much stronger soul than her. Li Hua picked her up and sent her home.

The ordeal ended and the deal between Garen and Nine-Tailed Fox was considered complete. Everyone went on their way, leaving Night Water alone.

“Do you still need anything?” Garen sat down as he drank the coffee that was sent to him earlier.

Night Water gritted her teeth. “How much are you willing to pay for me to study the Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil? You know what I’m talking about. The Soul Energy releasing naturally from the Mind Reader possesses a very powerful enhancement towards us Soul Energy Practitioners.”

“The price?” Garen had already guessed that she would come for this. “Unfortunately, I need to keep Mind Reader up as a supply so I won’t be sharing his Soul Energy with you.”

“Fifty thousand Contribution Points!” Night Water gritted her teeth.

Garen shook his head. “It’s not about the Contribution Point.”

“A hundred thousand!” Night Water gritted her teeth even more.

“It’s really not about the Contribution Point.”

“Two hundred thousand points!” She was literally speaking through her teeth.

“No!” Garen cut her off. “I told you it’s not about the Contribution Points.” He had decided to completely swallow up Mind Reader so that there would be no problems surfacing in the future. He had already absorbed a sixth of Mind Reader’s natural Soul Ring earlier. If he were able to absorb everything, his Soul Ring Power would achieve a whole new level.

“Two hundred and fifty thousand points!! This is all that I have accumulated! Don’t be too greedy!” Night Water had had enough.

“…” Garen frowned as he stared at her quietly.

“You… What are you staring at!?” Night Water had goosebumps as she was being stared at. “Are you being tempted? Tell me if you are!”

“I’m thinking if I should rob you! What a rich girl,” Garen joked as he stood up. “Alright. It’s late and you should leave.”

“It’s two hundred and fifty thousand points!! Are you not tempted at all?!” Night Water stood up and shouted in disbelief.

“You won’t be leaving if you don’t leave now.” Garen snapped his fingers and Double-Tailed Scorpion entered the room to send the guest off.

“This way.” Double-Tailed Scorpion smiled as he sent the guest away.

Night Water was then sent away in dissatisfaction.

Garen stood alone for a while before ordering his underlings to lock down the entrance so that no one could simply enter or leave the area. Then he turned around and walked into the secret chamber.

It was not that he was not tempted by the Contribution Points. It was because the longer Night Water stayed by Mind Reader’s side, it would be easier for her to realize Mind Reader’s irregularity. Furthermore, he could not wait any longer as it would only be considered safe after he had achieved his plan.

Mind Reader was still unconscious inside the secret chamber and the black sun striation on his chest had yet to completely vanish.

Garen pulled him up single-handedly.

Then, a slam could be heard.

The secret chamber’s door was automatically shut off.

The Soul Energy was startled as the air current started to flow about wildly, recirculating inside the secret chamber.

A mysterious faint, white light started glowing around both Mind Reader and Garen from head to toe, gradually plating them into white color.

The air inside started to tremble, giving off a noise similar to as if there were countless of people meditating. Garen stared at the Sacred Sigil on Mind Reader’s chest while he used one of his hands to take out the blood ink and repeated the procedure.

Pew!

The black mist was formed and turned into a Blood Ball levitating in Garen’s palm.

“Lin!” As the faint noise reverberated in the background, Garen gently pressed the Blood Ball on his own chest. The Blood Ball gave off a sizzling sound before it entered into his body.

This was the first ball.

He repeated the same action once more. Unlike Nine-Tailed Fox, whose actions possessed the probability of failure, Garen did not waste a single drop of blood ink as he drew the Sacred Sigil. Two bottles of blood ink were more than enough for him to completely absorb the power of the Sacred Sigil!

The second blood ball was quickly extracted and the black sun on the Mind Reader’s chest became much more diluted than before.

He woke up, groaning as if his body was being torn apart.

“You…” Mind Reader looked at Garen with a muddy gaze as he felt the sensation of something constantly leaving his body. He did not know why but he felt rather depressed.

“Do you want… this power of mine?” Mind Reader gave a wry smile. “Take it… Take everything. This is a tragic and disgusting ability!”

Without any change in his expression, Garen started to extract the third Blood Ball. His actions were getting much more efficient over time as he aimed at Mind Reader’s chest with one hand and stabbed into it.

Thud.

The blood mist gathering by his palm turned into a Blood Ball. It looked like Garen had taken out a bloody heart out from Mind Reader’s chest from afar.

“This is the source of all nightmares…!” Mind Reader smiled. “Am I going to… die?”

“No,” Garen responded calmly. “Your Soul Ring will be extracted by me but you won’t die. I’ll leave enough soul for you to function as a normal person. It’s more than enough for you to live.”

“Is that so?” Mind Reader, who was slightly anxious was instantly relieved. “In other words, my ability will be robbed away from me, right?”

“You can see it that way.”

Garen extracted the fourth Blood Ball as he gently pressed it into his chest.

A huge amount of Soul Energy gushed into his body.

His first Soul Ring could no longer absorb any of it as the second Soul Ring started to form. Furthermore, the third Soul Seed was already forming inside the second Soul Ring. As he was extracting Mind Reader’s Soul Ring, he was also under the process of absorbing the Natural Soul Energy’s huge amount of outflow. This outflow of Soul Energy was not something a commoner could absorb as the process was incredibly fast, resulting in a ridiculously powerful impact. However, Garen was different. Technically, he was already considered a Demon Lord Level powerhouse in the Mother Stream System. Hence his soul was a few hundred times stronger than of the commoners.

Despite Nine-Tailed Fox was also a transmigrator who had transmigrated to multiple worlds, her soul was still not superior compared to his. It would still be considered modest for him to say that his soul was hundred times stronger than hers.

Garen looked at the dark space inside his soul.

Inside the pitch black space, there was a second halo on top of the first Soul Ring. The halo seemed to be made of a white gold material as it had empty slots for the Soul Seed, which seemed to be a projection from the first Soul Ring below.

The first three slots already had colorless Soul Seeds in it. Furthermore, it had already been fully filled up. The enormous amount of Soul Energy was filling up the fourth empty slot, which was like an endless abyss as it kept absorbing it.

The endless amount of Soul Energy was surging inside Garen’s body as it nourished both his soul and body. Regardless of how restrictive this universe was, he was like an unstoppable force that could not be contained as he kept pushing towards the upper limits.

Garen then looked at his status and there was a huge development.

‘Kong Xiaofei – Strength 11, Agility 12, Vitality 14, Intelligence 11. Potential 0%, Soul Limit 80’

His limit had already reached eighty points while the rest of his physical attributes had skyrocketed to an unrealistic level within a short amount of time. Physical attributes in the tens might not be something impressive in the other world. However, it had already reached the level that would flabbergast anyone in this very restrictive world.

This status was borderline cheating as Garen would not be required to exhaust a huge amount of Soul Energy every second or else he would not be able to sustain such a powerful structure. Analogically, the number of nutrients and water between a giant tree and a little sapling were drastically different. A tree that reached the clouds could only do so due to the huge amount of nutrients provided from the ground. Hence, the tree would wilt if there was not enough supply of nutrients.

A pool would not be able to sustain a sea serpent and only the sea could house an endless amount of gigantic creature. It was a universal law that was applied to every world.

The fifth ball!

Garen gently retracted his hand away from Mind Reader’s chest. A huge sun striation started to appear on his chest. The black sun striation seemed to have formed onto his body naturally. Its tone was much different than of Mind Reader’s as it was much blacker. Furthermore, it had much more surface area as it not only covered Garen’s chest, it had also covered his back as well.

**********

“Isn’t it a little bit discourteous for Lord Third to let us wait here?” There were a few black cars stopping in front of Garen’s base. An upright silver triangle emblem could be seen in front of the cars which represented the identity of the highest ranking members in Vulture.

“I’m very sorry. The minister has ordered that no one is allowed to enter this base without his permission. Please be patient.” Double-Tailed Scorpion blocked the fleet of cars with a calm expression.

Vulture No. 4 frowned as he smoked his cigarette. He was standing at the very front as he led his group. Behind him were a few mercenaries in weird looking attires consisting of males and females.

Among the crowds of men and women, a young man in a white windbreaker crossed his arms as he stared into the tall building in front of him before looking at Number Four talking towards the guard at the entrance of the building.

“I sense the Soul Energy is fluctuating.” He whispered to Number Four from behind. “We have to be quick. I’m afraid that Garen is doing something with the Mind Reader.”

“Are you confident? The Sword Master is known as the strongest martial artist in the entire history!” Number Four talked to the man behind him, while at the same time was also talking to Double-Tailed Scorpion who was standing at the entrance of the building.

“Don’t worry about it. We are professionals.” The man in white windbreaker smiled.

“I hope so. Don’t blame me if I abandon you guys if anything goes sour.” Number Four said bluntly. “After all, we are only cooperating together.”

“As you wish.” The man in the windbreaker was not surprised at all.

“Please step aside or else we will have to be rough towards you.” He took a step forward and threatened Double-Tailed Scorpion loudly.

“I want to see how rough you guys can be.” A man in a white coat appeared behind Double-Tailed Scorpion. It was the Root Doctor, Jiatai.

He had just returned from an outstation mission. He was catching up on his sleep as he was woken up by the rackets outside. Then, he heard such a rage-inducing word the moment he stepped out. This building was the Unrestricted Department’s territory, its headquarters, and a portion of Vulture’s headquarters resided here as well. How dare someone threatened to break into this place?

This was similar to someone banging your doors furiously, threatening for you to open it or else they would kill you! Anyone would have been angry after hearing such words.

Chapter 1220: Lurk 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Jiatai the Root Doctor,” The man in the white windbreaker glanced at Jiatai, immediately acknowledging his name. “People might be afraid of your Thousand Magnetic Needles, but it’s useless against me,” he snorted.

Suddenly, a fuzzy Soul Energy Force started escaping from the base, forming a translucent ring of ripples that started spreading.

“He really is absorbing Soul Energy!” A lady behind the white shirt man snorted. “Even a powerhouse of the Mother Stream System couldn’t resist the temptation of a natural Soul Ring. A more troublesome powerhouse wouldn’t be able to resist it either.”

“Something’s not right, this Soul Energy Force seems to be a little too big…” The man in white shirt frowned slightly. “Absorbing and releasing Soul Energy shouldn’t cause such a big movement, should it?”

“But it’s fine.” The lady smiled as she pulled out something that seemed to be a small humanoid toy. “No matter how mysterious Soul Energy is, it is still a form of energy. There are plenty of ways to trigger it.”

She tugged on the white doll’s head lightly.

Crack.

A light surge of Soul Energy rushed out, entering the Soul Energy ripples in the air. In an instant, all the Soul Energy that was contaminated by this surge of energy started to boil and became distorted.

Just like ice-cold water that suddenly became boiling hot water! Countless Soul Energy stirred up and rushed into the core of the ripples.

********************

“This!?” With one hand, Garen grabbed the sixth Blood Ball. He could feel that something was off as if some special force was transmitting into him. His own Soul Energy was still alright, but the massive Soul Energy escaping Mind Reader was like an aphrodisiac potion and it started to distort badly.

At this moment, his Soul Energy was still linked to the Mind Reader’s natural Soul Ring. The force instantly transmitted into his inner Soul Ring, a trace of evil tyrannical will slowly sink into his Soul Ring.

Roar!

It was a dog-like black creature with no eyes, just a white mouth with serrated edged teeth split open on the left side of its body. All of a sudden, it darted right into Garen’s inner soul ring and started howling.

“This is Sin’s Authority!!” Garen had never seen such a creature before in his life. However, not only did he heard Black Claw of Sethe brought it up more than once that this was no other than the real natural enemy of a Soul Energy creature, the strongest monster that was developed by the Void Creatures in the Mother Stream System contrary to the Ancient Endor’s Soul Ring — Sin’s Authority!

All forms of attack that consisted of Soul Energy were nutrients to it that enabled it to grow rapidly.

“Damn it!” Garen had no idea at all how he was going to deal with this Sin’s Authority that came out of nowhere.

In addition of being Soul Energy’s nemesis, it was practically vulnerable against all physical attacks. But he could not leave right now while the linking ceremony between Soul Rings was still happening. If he was to leave suddenly, he would most likely trigger a major disturbance in the natural Soul Ring, even his newly formed Soul Ring would crumble and explode as well. By then, not only would he suffer from heavy injuries, he would even lose his life!! Moreover, Soul Rings and Soul Seeds accumulated from a couple of worlds would straight away fall apart and explode along too.

Even if someone was to touch him from the outside, it could even cause the entire situation to lose control.

Sin’s Authority, the black dog, was in the black space. It simply pounced on the two massive Soul Rings that were constantly turning, biting onto Garen’s Soul Ring.

*********************

“I said it already, all of you can’t enter.” Jiatai glared at the people crowded by the door.

“As Vulture No.4, I have the rights to enter any area in the headquarters, including here!” Vulture No.4 snorted loudly, “If you really want to stop me, then don’t blame me for executing my high law enforcement power!”

The so-called high law enforcement power was just that high-ranked Vultures had the powers to carry out law enforcement punishments against other high-ranked Vultures without the verification of No.1 Vulture. This power was only possessed by the Vultures ranked top five.

“High law enforcement power?” A Steel Needle suddenly appeared in Jiatai’s hands. Instead of getting mad, he smiled. “Well then, let’s see whether you’re the stronger one. I’ve never liked you and No.5. Today shall be the perfect day for this Lord over here to show you how to conduct oneself.”

“Such big, shameless words!”

No.4 was slightly agitated too, a silver-white short dagger appearing in his hands. His eyes started glowing in a bright red shade and the electronic chip that was planted into his eyeballs started working.

Soon enough, the atmosphere between both people started to become tense. Groups of people began swarming out of the Unrestricted Department, encircling No.4 and the others. A few snipers had their aims directed at No.4 and the others, the red spots directly falling on them.

In Vulture, every high-ranked person had their own designated forces, and these forces would only listen to the commands of their Direct Supervisors. Even if they were to aim their guns at a leader of another force, there would be zero hesitation.

“Are all of you rebelling?!” No.4’s face fell as he shrieked.

“Just forcing our way!” The white shirt man smiled. Speaking softly behind No.4, he could feel that something had gone wrong inside.

A black gleam flashed beneath his eyes. It did not seem humane.

“We’ll hold responsibility, don’t worry about it.” He straight away put No.4’s mind at rest.

No.4 instantly calmed down and swept his gaze around the large group of soldiers around him. There were nearly hundreds of them.

“Who dares to stand in my way! Let’s move! Enter!!!” He roared as he made his way toward the entrance. Little did he believed that Jiatai would actually dare to kill him.

“Block him!” Double-Tailed Scorpion yelled.

These people were obviously here to mess around, and if Garen was still not out by this moment, something must have definitely gone wrong inside, there was no way they could allow their minister to be disturbed!

*********************

Crack!

The Hellfrost Peacock’s Soul Seed was bitten by Sin’s Authority. After the black dog swallowed a mouthful, it went forward and bit on the other few Soul Seeds.

As the cracking continued sounded, the originally Soul Seed that was extremely strong and powerful was easily bitten into bits and pieces, nearly falling apart.

Somewhere deep inside Garen’s soul was aching, but that ache was nothing at this moment. Staring at his own Soul Seed being destroyed, he panicked. These were the Soul Seeds and Inspiration he had spent so much effort and hard work accumulating. A bite as such was not just only a loss of Soul Energy, but more of his own inspiration of different rules and his own understandings of the universe!

The black dog simply biting him here and there was killing him!

“Die!!” He thundered as he triggered his Nine-Headed Dragon Will.

Just when the golden Nine-Headed Dragon popped its head out, the black dog immediately pounced forward and bit its neck. The black dog then swallowed the nine heads and in less than a few seconds, the golden Nine-Headed Dragon Will was completely swallowed up.

Garen did not expect this kind of change would happen so suddenly. He watched it destroy the Nine-Headed Dragon Will as he felt a painful tear in the depths of his soul.

“Ha ha ha!! Void Hunter! Aren’t you struggling? Resist it! It’s useless!” A rumble of laughter sounded from the black dog’s body. “It’s been a long time since I’ve been lurking around you from the last world, and finally, I’ve waited for this opportunity!”

Garen’s heart sank and suddenly understood who his opponent was. The foundation of the Soul Seed was still there and his memory still existed. As long as he had the sufficient Soul Energy and as long as he was not completely swallowed, the damage to the Soul Ring would not be too bad. Now that he understood clearly who his opponent was, he was really panicking.

“Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia?”

“Nadia?” The black dog blanked out for a second before laughing again, “This idiot, and they actually let you continue to transmigrate and develop and did not personally come to kill you. A huge threat you are! I’ve been given such a gift. Come to think of it, I still have to thank her… But rest assured, after eating you, I’ll go back and kill her! I won’t let you be alone.”

It sprang forward an took a bite of a Soul Seed among the first Soul Ring, intending to destroy all the completed Soul Seeds, then wait for the Soul Energy to simmer off and devour once his powers have reduced.

Crack!

Just happened that it bit on the Holy Phoenix Demon Book’s Soul Seed.

Gold!

Infinite gold gleams broke out suddenly. Perhaps it was not pure gold, but definitely something that was like black flames wrapped in gold.

Boom!

A giant, golden phoenix rushed out from the Soul Seed and surrounded the Soul Seed. With a sinister arrogance, it rushed toward the black dog.

“Holy Phoenix! Holy Phoenix!!” Voices of countless people began to sing. Numerous gold scriptures flew out of the phoenix’s body and formed chains that seized the black dog.

“What is this!?” The black dog was horrified and tried to flee, but it was useless.

Bang!

Wrapped in the countless golden light, black flames were spreading all over the chains, lighting the black dog on fire.

“No!!!” The black dog mourned with pain. “This… This is domineering!!! How is this possible!!? How can such a thing like this be allowed to exist!!”

“No!!! No!!!” Screaming, the black dog swiftly burned into ashes.

The golden phoenix’s eyes were a sleek darkness as if there were numerous black flames burning within. It stared quietly as the black dog burned completely, then it opened its wings.

The black dog turned into an overflowing black gas that rolled around. These countless gases were like nutrients, absorbed by its golden wings as if the countless black rays were trickling into its wings.

A blurry three-headed six-limbed phantom appeared beside the golden phoenix. It was the once fallen Buddha Mother.

The six different limbs were holding on to different weapons each while Buddha Mother looked down upon the golden phoenix.

At that moment, scriptures and symbols turned into a mass of golden light jades that started to circulate in the air.

Garen could feel the pain in his soul started to fade and gradually recovered. The golden phoenix danced around the Soul Seed and eventually entered the Soul Seed once again, disappearing into thin air.

In the gap where Garen’s soul was ripped out, a surge of golden Soul Energy rushed inward. The mysterious energy was gold on the outside, but black within.

But in his consciousness, this energy seemed to still be dissipating quickly. While it was restoring its own injuries, the Holy Phoenix Demon Book’s Soul Energy still seemed to be dissipating rapidly as well.

“There is no room for the existence of the universe…” Garen finally understood. The Holy Phoenix Demon Book was too extreme, it paid attention to both heaven and earth, but it was self-conceited, so even if it was considered a type of Soul Energy, it was beyond what Sin’s Authority could ever withstand. However, Sin’s Authority’s nature energy was also extreme, so both sides could finally cancel off each other. Just that the Holy Phoenix Demon Book had a higher amount of Soul Energy, it was able to sustain until this moment.

Chapter 1221: Kill 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Thank goodness the Holy Phoenix Spirit Book’s Soul Energy has an extremely short overbearing nature, or this would’ve been really dangerous,” Garen looked at the temporary yet overbearing Soul Energy that was dissipating from the Holy Phoenix Spirit Book. He was completely overwhelmed.

The unexpected change in enemy caught him unprepared, causing him to finally wake up in the world he once thought he was unbeatable.

“Void Creature is still set on me. I should’ve thought about this earlier, Void Pursuers and Void Creature attract each other like magnets. Because of the vow, I have to kill Void Creature if we ever cross paths, and it seems like the Void Creature have the similar constraints. However, where in the world did that Sin’s Authority come from?!”

Garen recounted the baffling force he felt earlier on and made some speculations.

A huge amount of Soul Energy constantly poured out of the Mind Reader and into his body, replenishing the injuries from the bites he received from the black dog earlier on. At the same time, the Holy Phoenix Demon book was recovering from the injury as well.

Bang bang bang!!

Faint gunshots could be heard from the outside and the entire Secret Chamber shook.

“Hmm?” Garen opened his eyes. “Is that… A bomb?”

Using a bomb at the Vulture Headquarter? Who would dare to break into his base?

The Holy Phoenix Demon Book’s golden energy rapidly compensated for the tormented Soul Seed and soul of Garen’s. Then, the remaining energy assimilated into his entire Soul Ring. Right then, all of the Holy Phoenix Demon’s Book golden energy disappeared completely.

“If it wasn’t for the Holy Phoenix that erupted, I’m afraid I might’ve had temporarily broken the Soul Ring already, but everything’s okay now.” The black sun pattern on Garen’s chest had completely solidified and the black lines on the Mind Reader’s chest were slowly disappearing.

Thump.

Mind Reader fell directly from Garen’s hands and fell to the ground. Though his face was pale, the fall woke him up.

Garen looked at his current situation.

His first Soul Ring had recovered and it was back to normal with just a few scars here and there on the Soul Seed but they wouldn’t make much of a difference and will go away completely after some nourishment.

The second Soul Ring had already condensed the fourth Soul Seed, all of which was colorless and transparent, not to mention full and plump. As for the fifth Soul Seed, it was already condensed for an hour an half so it was obvious that it was lacking Soul Energy.

But that was it. According to his current Status Pane, his Soul Limit had reached ninety points!!

‘Kong Xiaofei — Strength 14, agility 14, physique 16, intelligence 11. Potential 0%. Soul Limit 90.’

His average qualities had once again improved a ton.

Moreover, the two Soul Rings continued to spurt out pure Soul Energy that was at least three times stronger than the original, nourishing his entire body.

“Just one Mind Reader and I’ve gotten such huge improvements…” Garen felt good.

Boom!

A violent explosion sounded from outside once again, leaving slight tremors through the Secret Chamber.

“Harrumph!” Garen strode to the outside of the Secret Chamber.

Opening the door, the sound outside was suddenly clearer and fiercer.

Hiss!!

A sharp armor-piercing round instantly hit the space between his eyebrows from the front.

“How dare you!”

Using just one arm, Garen’s right arm moved out in an indeed horrifying speed with the afterimage held in front of the opponent’s face. His palm missed and some of the bullet fragments immediately scattered into his palms.

********************

“How is this possible!!?” The leader, the man in the white windbreaker, stood far away and stared at Garen, who just walked out of the Secret Chamber and broke the armor-piercing round into pieces with his bare hands.

“How can Sin’s Authority fail?!!” He kept his eyes glued on Garen unbelievably. There was a window in the middle of the Secret Chamber which was made of high-strength glass. At this moment, the both of them were staring at each other from afar, finally recognizing both sides’ true identity.

“Void Creature!” Garen’s voice traveled through the glass and reached the man in the white windbreaker.

The man’s black eyes immediately widened.

“Retreat!!!” He shrieked. No.4 ignored the others who already rushed inside and instead turned around and started running!

In the humongous base, the entire building was round in shape. However, Vulture No.4 and the others were like a sharp saber that pierced into the center of the circle, almost entering the main building.

Although many people around could aim Vulture No.4, nobody actually dared to take a shot. After all, he was still a high-ranked person in Vulture. Those ranked above fifth had the authority and speaking rights that were extremely intimidating. So all they did was release bombs in an attempt to use the aftershock waves to form Vulture No.4 and signal Garen who was in the Secret Chamber at the same time.

At this moment, shouts of retreats could be heard from the man in the white windbreaker and Vulture No.4 immediately blanked out.

“Retreat? Are you joking me?! We’ve reached this point already and you want us to retreat?!” Ignoring the shouts, he continued to stride toward the main building.

The white main building reflected a metallic texture under the sun.

Boom!!

The door suddenly crashed open and flew out from the inside, slamming into No.4 and the others.

The dark-eyed lady stepped forward and sneered as she held out her hand to block No.4.

“What are you afraid of? Garen was definitely tortured by that thing till…”

Bang!!

Without even finishing her sentence, the lady was knocked down by something like a locomotive. Four jet tubes opened behind her and started emitting white gas but it did not help the matter at all. The massive force continued pushing her backward.

Along the way, she knocked dozens of people onto the ground and they all started howling in pain as they injured themselves.

“This is!?!!” No.4’s expression changed as he backed away swiftly.

But it was too late.

A strong figure rushed out the door like a railway train, crashing into the front of his body.

Bang!

“You dare kill me!!?” No.4 felt as if he was just crushed by an elephant as he got hit by the massive force, not being able to resist. As his body suspended in the air, he screamed furiously before he was grabbed by the neck and pulled back by a gigantic hand.

Looking from above, the entire No.4 army could only see that he was hit by a white figure. With a boom, they were utterly routed and thrown off their feet. The strongest No.4 and the dark-eyed lady were knocked away directly, thrown away and rolled around like wooden blocks before being caught once again.

Garen was dressed in all white as he grabbed Vulture No.4 by one hand.

“Too weak!”

He shook his head lightly.

Hiss!

No.4 turned red and could not speak, but all of a sudden, uncountable Steel Balls exploded out from his body. It was as if a large number of Steel Balls were installed in his body beforehand.

With a boom, the huge amount of Steel Balls turned into a grey shadow that shrouded Garen.

Buzz buzz, all the Steel Balls seemed to connect and started a light blue arc.

“Ten Million Volts!!” No.4 started laughing wildly. “You dare to humiliate me, die!!!”

To be grabbed by the neck in front of so many people, it was an insult simply worse than a lifelong vengeance! If he did not get his face back, he would have no more face to continue staying in Vulture!

“What a boring show off,” Garen’s empty left hand disappeared as fast as lightning.

Swoosh!

The front of his body opened up like a peacock spreading its feathers. In an instant, hundreds of limbs appeared in the air and swiftly merged into one single palm.

Crack.

He then squeezed all the Steel Balls together, twisting them into a clot of steel waste before dropping it on the ground.

No.4 was stunned as his teeth began to tremble.

This sort of critical ability using just his flesh was no longer humane. This was practically the same mythical powers as the Four Great Cornerstones.

“No!! I was forced…”

Crack!

Garen straight away broke his neck, causing mists of blood to explode from his hand. He did not even care that spatters of blood sprayed onto him.

Like a duck that broke its neck, No.4’s head and body were separated right away, both pieces fell to the ground. The gleaming white tube still had a constant stream of air.

“He really killed No.4!?”

“I don’t want to die!!”

“Retreat! Retreat!” The subordinates behind No.4 had yet to react and Garen had already broken No.4’s neck alive. Disregarding No.4 or anything else, he had directly killed a high-ranked Vulture. The crowd immediately backed away frantically.

Even Garen’s direct subordinates in the base were silent and did not know what to do.

As a top-five Vulture, he killed a same high-ranked person without the approval of No.1. Was Garen trying to start a rebellion?!

Regardless of any rules or ethics, No.1 had to immediately execute Garen. Otherwise, without the application of rules, the entire organization would be a mess.

Did Garen not know about such consequence?

Of course, he knew. However, he had reached such a level, what could possibly threaten him? Even if Sea God nourished under both of his big Soul Rings, it was still not enough to surpass him.

Garen himself was already enraged by the sneak attack earlier. At this moment, he could still hear No.4’s screams. He might have used too much force accidentally, then… There was no more.

No.4 died right away. So unexpectedly fragile.

The dark-eyed lady backed away with fright, then turned around and started running.

From Garen’s appearance all the way to him killing him, everything lasted less than five seconds. The situation reversed instantly. She had suspected Garen to fail, so she must now face her anger. A Demon Lord Class Void Pursuer! The victory and loss scale was completely balanced!

“You want to leave?’ Garen turned his attention to the lady and the man in the white windbreaker.

The latter was already a distance away whereas the lady was still right before him. It was evident that she was possessed by Void Creature. As a Master-level powerhouse of controlling dreams, it was effortless for Void Creature to hypnotize a person through dreams and achieve his purpose of manipulating the person at the same time.

Stepping on his foot, he dashed forward. He was twice as fast than the lady and soon enough, appeared in front of the lady as if he had teleported.

With a stretch of his arm, he grabbed the lady’s neck directly.

“Stop!!” A loud rumble thundered in the distance. It was the voice of an old woman.

Garen’s arm shuddered slightly before reaching forward for a grab.

He suddenly saw a trace of rejoice in the lady’s eyes. Obviously, she still had someone to rely on. Just that things had reached this point already so who knew what kind of wildcard did the other person had.

“You can’t kill me!” The lady recovered slightly from the terror, allowing Garen to grab her neck. She was soon lifted into the air.

“Can’t kill you?” Garen tilted his head and looked at the brigade that just rushed in from the gate far away.

No.2, the elderly woman with her walking stick in her hand, rushed in with a brigade. They crowded around the soldiers of the base. As No.2, she was basically the absolute Ruler of the entire Vulture. At times when No.1 did not show up, she had the final say.

“I say, stop it!” No.2 shouted. “Garen, she’s not an ordinary lady! Are..”

Garen’s other hand went straight into the lady’s chest, blood spattered all over him.

He turned his head and looked at the elderly woman.

“What did you just say?” Garen responded with a slight smile on his face. It did not seem like he just killed someone, but instead, he was just watering plants.

No.2 paused with a stagnant look, her face instantly paled. The following words were suddenly cramped inside her, unable to be spoken.

Chapter 1222: Kill 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With a tear, Garen extracted his hand from the lady’s chest, drawing out a large amount of blood. At the same time, he actually dug out a heart that was still beating.

“You…!” The lady who seemed to be parasitized by Void Creature struggled as she cried out. “Someone… Will help me get my revenge…!” A mass amount of Soul Energy that could be seen even by the naked eye started emitting from her body. Garen straight away breathed in all the Soul Energy, not wasting a bit of it.

“I’ll be waiting,” Garen replied curtly.

Bang.

The lady soon stopped breathing and fell to the ground, causing a loud that that immediately woke No.2 up.

Her face was pale as she raised her arm and pointed at Garen. However, she could not speak at all, she only trembled.

Garen did not care though, his eyes glued at the lad wearing the white windbreaker who was already far away.

Whoosh.

He instantly disappeared. His moves were so swift that nobody around him could notice his movements as their eyes were not able to capture his speed. All they could see was a blur flash and Garen was already a hundred meters away, just a short distance away from the man.

With another flash, he was catching up already.

Garen could even see the frantic expression of the man in the white windbreaker. His black pupils were missing, even his eyeballs were non-existent. It was evident that Void Creature had parasitized already.

In this world, there seemed to be records of being parasitized. They were known as being possessed by demons. After being possessed, one’s eyes would turn dark and empty, which represented a bottomless abyss.

Ah!!!

Seeing that he was almost in an arm’s reach, the man started screaming.

A bat-like invisible sound wave spread wildly, forming swiftly like a tsunami and rushed towards Garen who was charging behind.

“Soul Shock?” Garen’s body trembled, suddenly realizing that he was about to catch the big fish. He was hit by the impact, flying over ten meters backward. However, instead of being furious, he started laughing.

“This is actually Soul Shock? It seems to be a General-Level above Void Creature! Perhaps it’s even Demon King Level!” In this universe, even Void Creature’s Demon King Level was extremely suppressed so it was not even that abnormal.

But after such Void Creature was killed, it definitely helped Garen a ton in raising his Void Pursuer. He even acquired a Void Crystal Core that was comparable to absorbing the Mind Reader’s Soul Ring!

“Good stuff!” Garen laughed out loud. The person before his eyes was no longer a human, but a living ginseng that was able to run!

With a look as if he was staring at food, Garen set out once again.

The man was startled. He was at the same level as Sin’s Authority, they were both Demon Lord Class, but just an elementary Demon King. Furthermore, they coincidentally lost great powers after being injured heavily. The original scheme was to successfully kill Garen after the sneak attack. Then they would not only acquire Garen’s Soul Ring but also the Mind Reader’s Soul Ring, killing two birds with one stone. Who knew the situation would change so drastically. Now, not only was Sin’s Authority dead, he even had to face Garen’s vengeance in return!

With a bit, the white-shirt lad suddenly instigated the little Demon King power that remained within him. He instantly accelerated and quickly shot into the distance.

Unwilling to be outdone, Garen upped his speed and followed suit.

Both of them seemed to just disappear from everyone’s sight in a blink of an eye.

“So what do we do now?” A field officer asked Vulture No.2.

“What to do?” From the series of accidents that just happened, No.2 had noticed something. It was obvious that the white-shirt youngster colluded with the idiotic woman along with No.4 to cook up something against Garen, but they failed. Some died while some were injured.

However, the identity of the lady who just died could not be overlooked. It was nothing if she was just an ordinary person, but she was really…

A hint of concern flashed through No.2’s eyes. She recalled Garen’s almost inhuman powers and her heart sank to the bottom.

Once the conflict between both sides broke up, it would not just be the resentment between both people anymore, but the entire Slann would lose its peace. It would still be alright if they could just kill Garen off. If he was to escape, Red Nation and Black Federation would be pleased to accept a strong leveled powerhouse like Garen.

“Investigate the identity of the man in the white windbreaker right away! Also, collect the body of… Mistress Song.” No.2’s voice lowered down. “I’ll inform No.1 immediately, and President Song Lingshan…”

The people around felt their heart go cold. The lady who was lying on the ground right now was actually Slann’s supreme leader, President Song Lingshan’s wife?!!

“But isn’t President Song’s wife Zhao Guomu?” Root Doctor Jiatai asked coldly.

They only caught up right this moment, but everything happened too fast nobody was able to react to it before everything folded out before them.

“This is his second wife…” No.2 seemed to age a few years just within seconds. Once a conflict erupted between both sides, they would have to choose to give up on Garen. Regardless of public or private, the could only give up on him. One was the supreme leader of the nation while the other, no matter how strong he was, he was just a person. Making a choice was simply a simple matter.

“Still too young and vigorous…” With a long sigh, No.2 turned and walked away.

“Release a wanted order.”

No.1’s deputy had also arrived, just getting out of the car. With an icy steel look, he opened his mouth and spoke to the No.2 in an unceremonious tone.

Jiatai and the others were already losing their minds. Everything was happening too fast and nobody could catch up at all. Everything was a foregone conclusion.

********************

At the tank maintenance site.

Two white shadows suddenly emerged at the enormous maintenance site. Some of the old veterans who were still in maintenance seemed to hear sounds and popped their heads out of the tank to have a look.

Boom!!!

A white shadow slammed into the side of a black tank and the tank was sunken immediately. A lot of the metal parts were smashed and flew out, scattering like broken glass shards.

Another white shadow rushed forward from behind and threw a punch!

Bang!!

The tank was completely smashed. It was completely mashed in like paper paste, the metal plates on both sides were crushed in and pressed together. It then collapsed over like broken chopsticks.

There was not even time for it to roll back to reduce the impact.

The person’s speed was incredibly fast that people could hardly see the punches, they thought a bomb had landed.

“You can’t kill me!” The white shadow zoomed out from the wreckage. He shrieked as he was covered in blood all over and anyone could hear the deep fear hidden in his tone.

Without a word, Garen retrieved his right fist before rushing up.

Bang, his fist had missed, hammering the ground ruthlessly. The man managed to dodge it.

Not even bothered, Garen spun around his right arm before sweeping both legs over.

Swoosh!

A round silver-white saber light appeared in the air.

A sharp scar immediately surfaced on the man’s shirt right on his chest.

“This is!!?” He looked ferocious and suspicious as he turned around and continued running.

The most terrifying thing was that any part of the body was able to bring out a blade-like lethality. This level may not be a problem in other universes, but in this place with such limited rules, it was truly remarkable to have such an achievement!

In addition to being faster than Garen, he barely had any glimmer of hope he could escape from this.

“West Valle is above! I won’t die! I definitely won’t!!” He kept praying and began to run around in a Z-shape.

At the same time, using his hands, a large number of small black particles were sprinkled all over, scattering the ground behind.

Boom boom boom boom!!!!

The continuous explosions skyrocketed. Those little things turned out to be different kinds of bombs.

Among the flames, Garen walked out unscathed.

“Little Ginseng~ Where are you planning to run to?” A grim smile appeared on his face. “Excessive consumption will affect the pharmacodynamic effect.”

All of sudden, Garen’s body was suddenly burning with a light, white flame. It was the shapeless Fire of Realm. Only one who reached a high altitude, one who surpassed the limits of the world’s existence, would have such flames.

“Game over.” As he finished he sentence, he suddenly disappeared and reappeared right in front of the white-shirt man.

He lowered the saber in his hand and chopped.

“Demon Soul!!” The man screamed wildly as his speed increased at the same time. However, his body consumed too much of Soul Energy in a short period of time so his entire body nudged slightly toward the left.

Boom!!!!

The saber fell through and went straight to the ground.

Hiss…

A crack as long as ten meters or more appeared on the ground below.

Garen’s arm repeatedly flashed in a faint red shade which was caused by the intense heat, the tremendous force, and the terrifying speed that was generated by the acute friction. It was a huge impulse that was almost abnormal.

The man seemed to only see the saber lightly brush by his nose. He did not even dare to move, it was just so close! Just so close!!

And he was cut into two pieces.

Hu… Hu… Hu…

Hot air poured out of his chest and the man was afraid to move anymore, but just stared at Garen in front of him. Garen lifted at least hundreds of his limbs and blew at the faint smoke on top. The speed of both sides instantly reversed. Apparently, the other side was still able to continue moving, but he could only explode in that very one instant. The outcome of the match was already obvious.

“I really didn’t expect this. Even at this place, you guys are still able to catch up.” Garen held his arm out and grabbed the man’s head.

Countless Soul Energy that was invisible to an ordinary person’s naked eye started to spread from Garen’s arms and entered the man’s ears, nose, and mouth.

Hiss!

The clothes on both men instantly tore apart, the massive force exploded just like a heart, tearing off the tops both men had on.

Differently patterned scars slowly surfaced both men’s chests.

Garen’s chest had a black sun pattern that represented the primal Sacred Sigil, which also represented the extraordinary of this universe.

On the other hand, the man’s chest had a dark black gigantic eyeball. A huge amount of Soul Energy continued flowing out of the eyeball and was swiftly absorbed by Garen’s black sun pattern.

The terrifying force directly cut off over ten meters of all the space around both people.

“You… Sooner or later… Will be like me!!!” The man yelled furiously as he struggled out his last words.

Chapter 1223: Prelude 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The same?” With a look of disgust, Garen quickened up his absorption of the Soul Ring.

The powerful devouring characteristic of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen brought an excellent devouring effect to his Soul Energy. Although his Soul Energy qualities were still not the Demon King leveled extremes like Black Sethe, it was still nevertheless a skillful devouring ability. Of course, there was also the basic nourishing ability.

The true opportunity to incarnate such true capabilities was this moment so that he could absorb others’ Soul Energy exceptionally smoothly.

The black eyeball on the man’s chest soon disappeared. The entire process lasted less than thirty seconds.

In the distance, dense footsteps could be heard. Crowds were swarming over from other places. Clearly, the sound of astir over here had attracted the attention of the other soldiers at the base.

Bang.

Garen released the dead body, the man had already stopped breathing. As a parasitic body of the Void Creature, his soul had long been devoured by the Void Creature and all that remained was just a shell. When the Void Creature was devoured as a representative soul, its entire body naturally dies and becomes a dead body.

Garen stood still and looked below at the changes to his Attributes Pane as he felt his body change as he became stronger and stronger. His heart felt unusually carefree.

All the while, he had always been concerned. It was odd that the Void Creature did not come to him for trouble in such a long time, but now, he could finally stop worrying.

After the Soul Ring finished absorbing the Void Creature, it started glowing an abnormally dark red shade when it was not even done digesting it. The second Soul Ring was experiencing an overflow situation whereas the fifth Soul Ring was basically condensed all of a sudden and a vast amount of Soul Energy was surging toward the structure of the third Soul Ring.

His Soul Limit suddenly broke through 100, reaching an unprecedented height.

His average physique was even at least a little above the minimum average.

‘Kong Xiaofei — Strength 15, agility 15, physique 17, intelligence 13. Potential 0%. Soul Limit 90.’

Garen immersed himself in his skyrocketing powers.

“Return and get the communication device, then straight away search for Slayer!” Garen decided on his plan. There was no point in staying in this world anymore. He had already understood the workings of the Lighthouse, he did not need Nine-Tailed Fox and the others anymore. Hell, he might even know the workings of the Lighthouse more than Nine-Tailed Fox and the others. He could even use his own Energy Machine Imprint.

The members of the Lighthouse did not bother about the damage they had caused to the universe of the worlds. Even if it was some sinful convicts, as long as they do not involve or persecute other transmigrators, the Lighthouse would not confine over the case. In other words, they view residents of other worlds as something like an NPC. They themselves were high above and not even considered as a race.

Such remarks could be seen in the forum, but there were also some people who strongly disagreed, though it was just a small number of them. The highest institution of the Lighthouse was the Dimensional Watchers, the organization that managed the entire universe, collecting various regular laws. Every once in a while, they would announce the latest news about prominent transmigrators. Their main purpose was to maintain the common interests of all transmigrators because opposed to the people of the universe, the numbers and powers of the transmigrators were too small in comparison.

Therefore, Garen knew that no matter what he did in this world, as long as he did not directly endanger the safety of other transmigrators, there would be no problem. Of course, if there were any unknown problems or direct dangers, even vendettas could happen between transmigrators.

“Absorb Slayer and set off to the Lighthouse,” Garen set the destination. Before the footsteps in the distance approached, he had already swooshed out towards the entrance of the base. His speed was almost phantom-like in the eyes of ordinary people, not visible at all.

As he traveled within the base, Garen who was already familiar with the roads quickly arrived at the entrance. Looking far away from there, he could see a huge army of black soldiers lined up. Every elite powerhouse was already mobilized here. Obviously, No.2 had already known that he would leave the base as open as the day.

Standing behind the crowd of the army, No.2 had her walking stick with her as she stared at Garen. A glimmer of helplessness and pity fleet through her eyes.

“Submit yourself to arrest, Garen.”

“I’ve never thought about it.” Garen took a step forward. “That someone would dare to ask me to submit myself to arrest?” He had a hint of a smile in his expression as if he was greeting a fellow friend.

But at this moment, both sides were not at all friends, but instead, a dense array of hundreds of elite soldiers were in a ring surrounding them.

The top twenty Vulture powerhouses, except for No.1 and several other ones who were out stationed, had all arrived on the spot. Each and every one of them had started up their own modified half-machinized armor as they stared at Garen carefully.

Most of them had their red dots aimed at Garen, it was the laser device.

“Don’t be crazy.” No.5 stood out snorting, “You’re not the only tough guy in this world. Furthermore, even if you are so strong and powerful, we have so many powerhouses here, why would we be scared of you?”

No.5 had always been dissatisfied with Garen, a cheeky young rookie, who had always pushed him around, and now he had just found his opportunity. He never thought that even though he was never able to find any flaws in Garen, Garen himself would make such a huge mistake. This made him extremely ecstatic. The same thing, after he heard about the whole process of Garen’s uprising, he was a little upset over No.4’s death. Therefore, in order to let the plan run smoothly, he gathered up a massive amount of elites nominally to encircle Garen, but in reality, it was just to protect himself and important people like No.2.

Garen was too lazy to even bother with this blockhead, they were not even at the same level at all. His gaze immediately landed on No.2, the true authority of the entire Vulture.

“Do you have anything to say?”

“Things have already reached this extent, what else can I say? No.1 and I had always thought highly of you,” No.2 sighed.

“If that’s the case, step aside then.” Garen looked at the crowd before him blocking the entrance. Almost half of these elites were personally trained by him, some of them even learned so many things from him that they took him as their master. Even Double-Tailed Scorpion and Butcher included, who had their heads low, not even daring to look at him in his eyes.

Both of them were different from the others. It was not out of respect or any feelings, but they knew the true hidden powers of Garen. They knew that this entire army was not enough to hold him down, that was why they were so afraid.

“No way we’ll step aside,” No.2 said resolutely. Once they get out of the way, the entire prestige of Vulture would be completely destroyed.

“Seems like I’ll have to make a move then,” Garen strode toward the entrance, ignoring the crowd that was blocking the entrance.

“Stand still!” One of the top-ranked Vulture powerhouse said. Perhaps it was the urge to perform in front of other high ranks, or perhaps he was looking down on Garen. He leaped out with two sickle-like weapons and darted toward Garen. Both sides of the weapons were glowing with red electricity as if it was some advanced propulsion device.

Nobody moved as an extremely bright Light Beam struck Garen’s eyes, completely dazzling his vision.

Bang!

The double-sickle landed on Garen’s right arm and broke like a piece of paper, sending millions of shards flying all over the place, whirling as they nailed into the nearby walls and ground.

Meanwhile, Garen had the powerhouse jostled up with an arm high in the sky.

For a top-notch powerhouse like Garen, not to mention such an incredible physique, even the slightly weaker body under his powerful workings would produce a miraculous effect. It was pretty normal for one slight force to have its effect multiplied by ten times.

It was definitely not a waste of extra power and the efficiency was terrifying.

“Forewind,” Garen said softly as he grabbed onto the person’s chest.

Hiss!

The man’s body instantly ripped apart and flew to two sides, his blood splattering all over the ground. Flesh, bones, and even the internal organs and half-machinized armor were all neatly torn into halves.

The ultra-close ranged forewind Saber Art had instantly ripped the person into half without any resistance at all.

Starting from Garen, the white ground before him turned into a fan-shaped red piece of ground. It was all splattered by the blood of the powerhouse after his body was mangled.

In an instant, everyone on the spot was shocked, even the ones who were preparing to aid.

“We can’t fight him close-ranged!” No.2’s face fell. She had always been unsure of how strong Garen actually was, only hearing from enemies who reflected about Garen’s terrifying combat power. She was not exactly sure to what extent were his terrifying powers.

Right in front of her eyes, a top twenty powerhouse could not even last through one round against Garen. She immediately shuddered.

“Long-ranged take aim, attack!” No.5 suddenly yelled.

Before No.2 could stop, No.5 already commanded. Once all shootings start, it might cause both sides to have faces completely torn off. He too had the firepower authority in the base.

Boom.

Overwhelming power broke out at the same time, all concentrated on Garen.

Bullets, snipers, bombs, grenades, electromagnetic bombs, lasers, poison gas grenades, poison needles, all sorts of high-risk weapons started bombarding toward Garen at the same moment. The sky seemed to lit up for a second, caused by the flash of light when all shots were fired.

In the loud noise, Garen raised his arm and his lips moved. Nobody knew what he said, but he instantly submerged in the gunfire and nothing could be seen anymore.

A blinding light appeared as the location where he was standing before suddenly exploded. As light and fire both intertwined, everything was blurry.

“Who’s the one who released so much poisonous smoke? Do you want to die?!” No.5 shrieked furiously. There were so many people here, in addition to the bomb explosions that would spread out the airflow, releasing poisonous gas at this very moment would simply kill everyone!

The disadvantage of Vulture that had never had a coordinated operation was immediately shown.

But nobody noticed Double-Tailed Scorpion and Root Doctor Jiatai who were secretly hiding the poisonous gas launcher in their hands, blending into the crowd behind. Both of them were the one who released the poisonous gas. They were particularly clear of Garen’s true powers and that this bunch of people was not capable of holding down Garen at all. Back at the Ocean Capital, Garen was able to deal with such a strong battle array already, this little bunch of people was nothing. At their levels, they were not even true elite powerhouses, they held no threat towards Garen at all.

“Instead for digging our own graves, it’s better to seek opportunities and let him go.” This was what Root Doctor and Double-Tailed Scorpion concluded in their conversation earlier on through the earpiece. Opposing the Vulture, they had more faith in Garen’s powers.

Exiting the crowd, Jiatai looked at the flashes of explosion far away. He remained silent.

“Who knows where’s Garen headed next? Do you think we can go along with him?”

“Well, I was just thinking the same thing.” Double-Tailed Scorpion laughed. Garen treated his subordinates and his own men pretty good and he was quite generous. If anything was to happen, as long as it would not oppose his own morals, he would definitely lend a hand and cover for them. On a daily basis, he would not control much either. He was practically the epitome of a true boss.

“Too bad, Vulture.” Jiatai shook his head. “Listen up, there’s going to be screams soon.”

Chapter 1224: Prelude 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen single-handedly grabbed onto No.5’s neck, it was the same posture as No.4 before. He let the various blade weapons cut his arms but it was no harm to him at all.

No.5’s elephant-like strength was currently nothing as he could not bring out any strength to even fight back.

Nobody knew how Garen broke into the crowd. All they could see was a massive pit at where he was standing earlier on and he just suddenly popped up in the middle of the crowd, grabbing onto No.5 who was hidden among them.

Everyone else backed away right away with fear. The people of Vulture were originally elite powerhouses gathered from all over the place, brought together by a similar employment method. There was no loyalty at all. At the sight of this scene, everyone was dumbfounded. Some of them knew the abnormality of Garen, and some of them who participated in the Ocean Capital operation backed away sneakily.

No.2’s face fell, she had not expected Garen to be powerful to this extent. So much firepower and it did not seem to bother him at all as he directly broke through the defense line.

“Garen!” No.2 yelled, “Don’t repeat your mistakes!!”

At this moment, she saw through it all. It seemed that all the powerful powerhouses were concealing their true abilities, they were indeed slacking. Garen had only joined the organization for a year or so, it was impossible for him to do such a thing and the only reason was that everyone here was merely afraid of him!

They were scared!

No.2 came up with such a conclusion that she herself did not believe much.

So many powerhouses and such a huge organization, and they were all terrified of a young man who was barely twenty years old!?

This was hilarious!

It would have been possible if it was Slayer’s case, he was the true enemy!

Wait! ~Slayer!

No.2 stunned for a second as she suddenly remembered the last time Garen fought against Slayer and retreated.

Looking up at Garen at the moment, she thought of a possibility.

“If Garen’s true strength is actually at Slayer’s level… Then the little people we have now… Not only are they not able to hold him down! There’s even going to many serious deaths and injuries!” At the thought of it, a chill sent down her spine.

“Let go of No.5 and we’ll let you go!” No.2 decisively shouted.

The corner of Garen’s mouth arched slightly. Truth be told, he did not want to completely tear off faces with Vulture. After all, after he leaves, Kong Xinxue and the others would still be here. They were still once companions, Nine-Tailed Fox and the others really did help him a ton. So if it was really necessary, he did not want to cut a clean slate with Vulture.

Grabbing onto No.5 right now and not killing him immediately was because No.5’s identity was slightly different. He was considered a true high-rank, and the other reason was that he was still waiting for No.2 to make a decision.

It seemed that No.2 had just made her decision.

As for the other person who had the authority to decide, No.5, was currently tugged on the chest by Garen. Under the extreme pressure, he was unable to even speak a word. Basically, he was just a waste man.

Garen turned his gaze to the crowd that was blocking his exit.

“Get out of the way!” No.2 bellowed.

Right away, the Vulture people left eagerly, all of them backing away. They were all just mercenary soldiers, not slayers. If the firepower just now did no harm to Garen, they would just be sending themselves to death.

Now that they had orders, they righteously separated and allowed Garen to leave.

“Thank you then.” Holding on to No.5, Garen strode toward the entrance of the base before simply throwing No.5 aside.

“Goodbye then,” Garen turned and smiled.

Swoosh!

He then vanished into thin air. Nobody caught sight of which direction was he headed, they could only feel a gust of wind blowing gently, and everything was back to normal, calm and peaceful.

All that remained were the giant pits caused by the fires earlier on and the burning sounds of the flames that were still combusting along the side.

Vulture Sword Master, Garen revolted.

********************

News spread throughout all continents overnight, Red Nation and especially Black Federation which once suffered all because of Garen were the first ones who received the news.

Wanted orders were issued straight away. Of course, it was a wanted order on the surface. Both nations had secretly decided that if Garen was willing to join their armed forces, they would immediately reserve a seat for him with the highest military powers.

Especially Black Federation, which straight away announced an unprecedented hundred million annual salary!

There were no more than three powerhouses in the world who were able to face Slayer alone and not fail, and Garen was one of them. In addition to his young age, he had endless potential ahead of him.

This was the sole reason all nations regarded highly of him.

Sometime later in the annual operation of Slayer’s massacre formed by the three nations, people of Black Federation even publicly sneered at people of Slan, mocking how they were not able to retain talents and that they were a sign of the nation’s decay. Both sides started fighting but everything ended with Slann’s people showing tolerance. They had become accustomed to tolerance, from the beginning to now, it had become a habit. At first, they still had Garen, but now they had lost their strongest power and everyone never felt more defeated.

After the routine joint search for Slayer ended with no results, the elite forces of the three nations each returned to their countries. The international situation returned to its original phase, Slann contracted completely while Black Federation continued expanding, whereas Red Nation was still experiencing a civil strife. Everyone went back to their own business.

As for Mind Reader, he had already been quietly rescued by Yuria when he went forward to check in on Slann. Although they lost the power of the Sacred Sigil, living the rest of his life as an ordinary person might not be a bad thing after all. However, the thing that Yuria was most concerned of was that the idea of relying on Mind Reader to seek his sister and mother was now over.

Nine-Tailed Fox and the others were not able to contact Garen in any way at all as he did not respond to any of the messages sent from their communication device and he ignored all their calls. All contact was cut off completely.

After plenty of tries, they decided to give up. After all, the Mind Reader’s Sacred Sigil was in their hands already.

********************

Whoosh…!

On the surface of the blue sea, a white speedboat was rushing into the distance quickly, leaving long white waves from its tail at the back.

Garen stood above the speedboat with a whole new appearance. He had golden hair and a pair of colorful sunglasses, topless with a pair of fancy beach shorts matched with a pair of white flip-flops. Even his height was slightly shorter than his original height.

He looked exactly like a playboy.

The speedboat was headed straight towards the horizon that was not visible. It was already a deep-sea region, but Garen was not worried about losing his way and he was just leisurely enjoying the sea breeze.

Unconsciously, an hour or so passed. Garen crouched on the speedboat as he continued looking straight ahead.

At the sea level in the distance, an equally similar small, white speedboat gradually emerged. Standing on the deck was a tall slender man who was dark all over. He was covered in the shadows, only a pair of eyes exposed on the outside with a hint of red fluorescence.

The man had a red wooden umbrella in his hands, blocking the water that was splashing around. His red eyes were glued at the direction of Garen far away.

He gently removed his black mask, revealing a pale face that was even more beautiful than a lady. It gave off a weak and delicate feeling that begged for pity.

“Slayer.” Garen stood up, drawing out a three-meter-long narrow blade from behind. “So this is your true appearance?”

Far away, his voice traveled through the waves directly to Slayer’s ears.

“You and I are the strongest people in the world,” Slayer’s flat voice also traveled all the way to Garen’s ears. “This is my respect for you.”

“Strongest?” Garen laughed, “What about Sea God?”

“I used ten sabers and decapitated a wing.”

Stunned, Garen went silent.

He knew the ins and outs of Sea God as well, and the fact that Slayer could chop off a wing proved that he had underestimated Slayer’s powers.

“After this battle, one of us shall become the one and only in the world,” Slayer gently placed down his pink wooden umbrella with a calm look on his face.

Garen smiled and remained silent. He then leaped up and the speedboat beneath him exploded with a boom. He fell straight into the waters and started running swiftly as if the water was just a flat surface. He darted straight towards Slayer!

Thump! Thump! Thump!

As his footsteps landed on the surface of the water, drum-like sounds of impact could be heard.

The distance between both of them closed in.

Swoosh!

Garen suddenly drew his saber out of the sheath and held it tightly in his hands.

********************

The gigantic silver-white cylindrical metal instrument rotated slowly.

The machine was located in a huge underground space in the base and there was a clean snow-white bed right in front of it.

A naked girl had a quilt in one hand covering most of her skin, her hair as white as snow cascading down her shoulders and all over the quilt.

The girl was sitting on the big bed with her eyes closed as the cylindrical machine behind her slowly started up. It was slowly opening toward the girl’s position, revealing an oval-shaped screen that clearly displayed a man’s figure.

“Yuria… Brother.” The girl turned to her side and opened her eyes, staring at the man on the screen.

“The world is going to change. Are you ready, Zhi Jinqin?”

An old and voice sounded from the machine.

“You’re not dead?” The girl stared blankly at the metal instrument above her. The gentleness in her eyes was completely different when she looked at Yuria.

“Dead?” The voice started laughing.

“If I haven’t witnessed your death, how can I myself die!?”

Swish!!

A long spiky, silver-white metal suddenly extended from the top of the instrument and pierced into the girl’s body.

Puff.

Zhi Jinqin’s weak body was pierced right at her right chest but the strange thing was that there was not even a trickle of blood at the wound.

“How sad! Even blood can’t flow out anymore? You’re just an empty shell,” the old voice sneered.

Zhi Jinqin was expressionless. She could not feel anything from the spike that pierced through her body as if it was not even stabbed into her body.

“Since that year, hasn’t my blood drained long ago?” She whispered.

“Immortal Body! Why can’t you die? Why would you rather be tortured yet still want to suppress me!?” The old voice felt unwilling as his mood seemed to change. “Let everything go, and go keep your brother company, isn’t that better? For so many years, you have weaved such a wonderful dream for your brother, parents, relatives, family, peace, serenity! You have all the pleasant things already, so what more do you want!?”

Zhi Jinqin did not answer. Instead, she lowered her head and quietly closed her eyes.

Chapter 1225: Battle to the Death 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!

Garen’s long saber slashed down hard on Slayer’s umbrella, and the red paint was jolted off by the impact, revealing the black metal underneath.

With a whoosh, Slayer’s arm spun, and the umbrella began to spin at high speeds. Just like that, it parried Garen’s blade.

“You’ve grown stronger again…” He leaped backward lightly and retracted his round umbrella, using the movement to reduce the impact of Garen’s vicious force.

The two of them were equal in speed. Slayer used to be faster, but thanks to his average attribute points, Garen’s speed was now equal to Slayer’s.

Without an ounce of hesitation, Garen dashed forward, his blade transforming into a circular whirl of silver that aimed straight at the enemy. At the same time, he lifted his leg, kicking up a wave of seawater that crashed at his enemy like a solid attack.

Considering how powerful his Strength was, even simple old seawater could be converted into a terrifying murderous weapon under its influence.

“Lunar Eclipse.”

Slayer’s eyes flashed with a red light, and his umbrella began to spin madly at high speeds, just in time to fend off the silver whirling blade. At the same time, he sliced downward with the edge of the umbrella, and perfectly cut through the wave of seawater pouncing at him.

Psst psst psst!!

Instantly, more than ten invisible air current blades shot out of the umbrella, attacking Garen from the left. All the air current blades gathered together, leaving clear white traces on the surface of the ocean. Although they were obvious, they were also very fast. Slayer also took advantage of the moment when Garen was most vulnerable. Since he had just made his move and used up all his power, he was completely helpless and unable to fight back.

“Are you trying to beat me in move transformation?” Garen’s blade turned slightly and shot out a blast of saber wind that crashed directly into the air current blade. The saber wind cut straight through the air current blade, and made sure the air currents had completely scattered before it faded away naturally. This was a demonstration of Garen’s surgical precision in the way he applied his strength; not a single ounce of power went to waste.

“Explode!”

Slayer closed the distance between them in an instant. The red umbrella began to spin crazily, crashing into Garen like a large screen. The muscles in his left arm had abruptly expanded to almost twice their original size, so thick they barely looked human.

Before the surface of the umbrella reached him, Garen could already feel an intense pressure descending upon him. Somehow, in complete contrast with Mind Reader or Yuria, Slayer was already a peak-level expert in his utilization of the Soul Ring. Garen had no idea how long he had to live in order to accumulate such vast experience.

This explosive power was rooted in the instantaneous expansion of his muscles, causing the power behind the move to at least double in magnitude. At the same time, there was a powerful spinning force behind it. The slightest mistake would mean that Garen’s defenses would be easily broken through.

Garen had just completed his move and had yet to recover his strength, so the only thing he could do was tilt his body slightly to evade this attack.

“Eroded Moon Shadow!” Slayer’s umbrella gave a jolt, and with an abrupt tearing sound, the surface of the umbrella immediately split into more than ten pieces. These pieces turned into more than ten flitting shadows that darted into the ocean, surrounding Garen from all sides like swimming fish.

“Four Directional Winds.” Garen’s blade spun, and at the same time, silver light rose all around his body, blocking off the black shadows. The silver light and the black shadows collided and canceled each other out.

Boom!!!

On the surface of the ocean, a giant tidal wave, more than ten meters tall, exploded over the area where the two crashed into each other.

The tall wave fell down as a spray of rain, each droplet splashing into the ocean around them.

Whoosh, whoosh. There were two clear sounds, and more waves rose around both Garen and Slayer as they dashed at each other. The blade left trails of intense light as it crashed into the red-black umbrella handle, unleashing golden sparks of different sizes.

The long saber immediately became an afterimage, each slash brought with it strong winds and new waves.

The tip of the umbrella handle was sharp, so Slayer used it as both a spear and a staff.

“Dragon Steed.” Slayer’s spear jolted and quickly spun around him once, swimming nimbly on the water around him like a living snake. At the same time, he himself constantly dodged Garen’s barrage of blade slashes with great agility.

Swoosh!

A gigantic circle appeared on the ocean around Garen and Slayer, and an oval-shaped hole opened up slowly in its center, biting at Garen like a deep black abyss. It was a giant whirlpool!!!

“Hmph!”

Garen was completely fearless, and did not shrink away in his assault. He and Slayer fell into the eye of the giant whirlpool at the same time.

In the deep blue whirlpool, they were surrounded by the deep-blue, almost-black walls of water. At the very center of it, the two of them were falling straight downward. It was like falling into a bottomless abyss.

Strangely, the giant whirlpool was actually still expanding, growing larger and deeper. The enormous hole in the center continued to deepen, as though it was an abyss that led straight to the ocean floor.

There was immense pressure everywhere, and the walls of dark-blue, almost-black seawater were all that could be seen. Other than the tiny pricks of white light above their heads, there was no other source of illumination.

Garen could clearly feel that, under these circumstances, Slayer’s strength and speed were both increased to almost 1.5 times their original value. He could instantly sense the pressure on him piling on.

“So you’re creating an advantageous terrain for yourself, huh?” Garen’s expression was cold, his attacks gradually slowing down.

Swoosh!

The long spear narrowly swept past his throat, missing by mere millimeters. Garen’s feet trod down hard on the water wall, and with an audible ‘bam’, he borrowed the momentum from the high-speed spinning. Instantly, man and blade turned into a saber wheel. He quickly landed behind Slayer, and spun toward the latter’s back.

Clang!

The umbrella handle and saber crashed into each other. Slayer did not turn around, blocking Garen’s attack backhandedly. His entire body was sent out flying, straight into the wall of water.

“Garrotte,” Slayer murmured softly. The sound waves seemed to come with an accompaniment, some tremors of power.

Barroom. White snake-like waves instantly darted out of the countless water walls, rushing at Garen as though by magic!

Garen’s attack was blocked, and he leaped back lightly, landing on the whirlpool water wall behind him. The soles of his feet vibrated at high speeds, neutralizing the immense spinning force of the whirlpool’s walls of water. As a result, he stood as steady as he would on flat land.

“Now that you’re all warmed up, isn’t it time to bust out the big guns?” His spear immediately vanished, leaving an afterimage, and his whole person lit up with white flames.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh. All the waves were easily slashed apart, vanishing. The spear appeared again instantly, and Garen held it in his hand, pointing it diagonally downward.

Slayer’s eyes darkened. He stood on another wall of water, completely motionless. The two of them stood off against each other, with more than ten meters between them.

“As expected, you truly have gotten considerably stronger.” He threw away the umbrella handle off-handedly.

“Looks like I can’t hold back any longer… If you die, I hope she… won’t blame me for it.”

“?” Garen frowned. Evidently, Slayer had yet to use his true power until now.

“I once killed a strange creature.” Slayer lifted his right hand, his palm facing upward, as though he was holding something up. “His eyes were pitch black and gave me a very strange feeling.”

Garen’s heart gave a jolt, and he immediately knew that Slayer was talking about a Void Creature.

“And then?”

Slayer’s palm began to expand slowly.

“I sense that your scent is very similar to theirs…”

Psh-sha!

His right arm began to swell up, from the shoulder up to the palm. A sharp white bone jutted out of his shoulder.

At the same time, Slayer’s whole body began to change in shape. He grew from 180 centimeters to more than two meters, and all the muscles on his body grew tougher and stronger. Even his head began to swell quickly. The muscle on the back of his head grew into a strange triangular shape, as though he had a flesh-colored triangle hanging from his nape.

His chest sunk inward, revealing a neat circular hole.

Psst!

The circular hole actually went completely through Slayer’s chest, revealing the dark blue wall of seawater behind him. It formed a hole that penetrated his chest completely.

Things like fins appeared on Slayer’s palms, connected to the backs of his hands. His toes all grew sharper, and these came with long, black, dagger-like nails.

Within a few short seconds, Slayer had changed from a pretty boy into a powerful monster that barely looked human.

“The First Original Sin.” He abruptly gathered immense Soul Energy into the middle of his palm, condensing them into a ball, a small red ball. Its center was distorted and jutted out slightly, as though there was an insect or something trying to worm its way out of the red ball.

Garen narrowed his eyes. This strange situation was beginning to reach beyond his understanding.

To think that this World could contain such a high level of distortion and mutation. Slayer’s Soul Energy Forces were already dense enough to shock Garen. Although he clearly only had one Soul Ring, Slayer had clearly already honed his utilization of it to the extreme. This level of power activation had even surpassed Demon Lords who were two Soul Ring Levels higher than him,

They were both Demon Lords, but Garen knew he could reach such an extent of power! As expected of the main character of this universe! And the leader of the Four Cornerstones.

Wisps of dangerous aura began to emanate from Slayer, circling around Garen like ice-cold poisonous snakes.

Evidently, the Slayer right now was already strong enough to pose a threat to his life. This was no longer a simple battle that did not involve the soul, this was a battle to the death between Demon Lords. If they were to fall here, even their Soul Rings and the will of their Souls would be completely destroyed.

Chack.

Garen held the saber in front of him, his eyes narrowing and the white flames on his body growing more intense.

“Thunder.”

There was a soft sound, and Garen suddenly felt his vision blur. The previously dark center of the whirlpool lit up abruptly, and countless bolts of blue lightning filled his field of vision.

All he could feel was countless bolts of lightning crashing toward him. It was as though the whole whirlpool had instantly turned into Slayer’s electricity-conducting tool.

There was nowhere to hide!!

He was completely surrounded by the walls of water and the whirlpool, so Garen had nowhere to hide. All he could do was hunker down and take it on.

Boom!!

Torrents of electricity crashed into his body, and Garen’s hair began to rise from the tips. As soon as the electricity made his hair stand up, his own Soul Energy would fix it again, so the two forces remained at a delicate balance.

But his Soul Energy was now being consumed at twice the rate.

“Era.” Slayer’s iguana-like blood-red eyes opened abruptly, and he disappeared from the spot.

The next time he reappeared, he stood behind Garen. Soundlessly but viciously, he pressed the red ball in his hand into Garen’s back. There was a difference in their speeds again!

Garen just managed to turn around and only had time to hold his blade in front of him.

Ka-chak!

There was a sound of metal breaking. In a world invisible to outsiders, the Soul Energy Ball in Slayer’s hand crashed into the blade. The temperature fluctuated from high to low, and the amplitude of the electric currents changed several dozen times in the same instant. Even if the blade was made of a special metal, it still could not handle such rapid changes. One last palm hit, applying more strength to it.

The saber snapped.

That powerful palm hit struck Garen straight in the chest.

Barroom!!!

There was a terribly loud sound, and the enormous whirlpool collapsed completely. Garen was sent out flying backward like a rocket, breaking straight through the entire whirlpool.

But he did not fly out fast enough to surpass the speed of Slayer’s continued chase. Instead, he was blocked by the vast volume of seawater, which kept reducing his speed.